let questions = [
{'numb': 1, 'question': 'Xizmat qilish', 'answer': 'Serve', 'options': ['Wake', 'Handshake', 'Serve', 'Should']} ,

{'numb': 2, 'question': 'Bir qancha', 'answer': 'Several', 'options': ['Expensive', 'Diabetes', 'Several', 'Hot']} ,

{'numb': 3, 'question': 'Hayratda qoldiradigan', 'answer': 'Shocking', 'options': ['Shocking', 'Nephew', 'Experiment', 'Hairdresserãšâ¼s']} ,

{'numb': 4, 'question': 'Gazak', 'answer': 'Snack', 'options': ['Worker', 'Narrow', 'Snack', 'Vegetarian cookbook']} ,

{'numb': 5, 'question': 'Nordon', 'answer': 'Sour', 'options': ['Wardrobe', 'Lesson', 'Carry', 'Sour']} ,

{'numb': 6, 'question': 'Gazli suv', 'answer': 'Sparklingwater', 'options': ['Sparklingwater', 'Journalist', 'Meeting', 'Apple']} ,

{'numb': 7, 'question': 'Ziravorlar', 'answer': 'Spice', 'options': ['In fact', 'Spice', 'Sweet', 'Theme']} ,

{'numb': 8, 'question': 'Achchiq', 'answer': 'Spicy', 'options': ['Road', 'Shovel', 'Torch', 'Spicy']} ,

{'numb': 9, 'question': 'Ismaloq', 'answer': 'Spinach', 'options': ['Fun', 'Spinach', 'Loud', 'Ban']} ,

{'numb': 10, 'question': 'Qulupnay', 'answer': 'Strawberry', 'options': ['Towel', 'Strawberry', 'Waterfall', 'Shirt']} ,
{'numb': 11, 'question': 'Tagin', 'answer': 'Tagine', 'options': ['Guy', 'Carpenter', 'Tagine', 'Search engine']} ,

{'numb': 12, 'question': 'Tami', 'answer': 'Taste', 'options': ['Traffic', 'Children', 'Taste', 'Type']} ,

{'numb': 13, 'question': 'Tam kurtaklari', 'answer': 'Taste buds', 'options': ['Taste buds', 'Ironing', 'Breakfast', 'Intercom']} ,

{'numb': 14, 'question': 'Tekstura', 'answer': 'Texture', 'options': ['Less', 'Luggage', 'Texture', 'Between']} ,

{'numb': 15, 'question': 'Qalin', 'answer': 'Thick', 'options': ['Reduce', 'Thick', 'Comedian', 'Advice']} ,

{'numb': 16, 'question': 'Qalay', 'answer': 'Tin', 'options': ['Post office', 'Sandwich', 'Tin', 'Confident']} ,

{'numb': 17, 'question': 'Tamaki', 'answer': 'Tobacco', 'options': ['Tobacco', 'Ending', 'Indian', 'Food processor']} ,

{'numb': 18, 'question': 'Pomidor', 'answer': 'Tomato', 'options': ['Raspberry', 'Characteristics', 'Tomato', 'Take photos']} ,

{'numb': 19, 'question': 'Tish pastasi', 'answer': 'Toothpaste', 'options': ['Marathon', 'Toothpaste', 'Businesswoman', 'Engineer']} ,

{'numb': 20, 'question': 'Transport', 'answer': 'Transportation', 'options': ['Fridge', 'Fair', 'Transportation', 'Rich']} ,

{'numb': 21, 'question': 'Quvur', 'answer': 'Tube', 'options': ['Tube', 'Profit', 'Marathon', 'Cleaner']} ,

{'numb': 22, 'question': 'Tomonidan foydalaning', 'answer': 'Useby', 'options': ['Mixed', 'Useby', 'Advice', 'Embarrassed']} ,

{'numb': 23, 'question': 'Isrofgar', 'answer': 'Wasteful', 'options': ['Forehead', 'Season', 'Wasteful', 'Maze']} ,

{'numb': 24, 'question': 'Faol', 'answer': 'Active', 'options': ['Active', 'Beauty', 'Souvenir seller', 'Tie']} ,

{'numb': 25, 'question': 'Allaqachon', 'answer': 'Already', 'options': ['Already', 'Quarter to', 'Intercom', 'Nobody']} ,

{'numb': 26, 'question': 'Dalil', 'answer': 'Argument', 'options': ['Butter', 'Organize', 'Burger', 'Argument']} ,

{'numb': 27, 'question': 'Topshiriq', 'answer': 'Assignment', 'options': ['Marathon', 'Young', 'Assignment', 'Agree']} ,

{'numb': 28, 'question': 'Ishon', 'answer': 'Believein', 'options': ['Soup', 'Cloudy', 'Railway station', 'Believein']} ,

{'numb': 29, 'question': 'Tegishli', 'answer': 'Belongto', 'options': ['Belongto', 'Self catering', 'Uncle', 'Ironing']} ,

{'numb': 30, 'question': 'Zarba', 'answer': 'Bump', 'options': ['Dish', 'Garage', 'Bump', 'Development']} ,

{'numb': 31, 'question': 'Saraton', 'answer': 'Cancer', 'options': ['Camping', 'Free time', 'Boxer', 'Cancer']} ,

{'numb': 32, 'question': 'Marosim', 'answer': 'Ceremony', 'options': ['Paint', 'Ceremony', 'Save up', 'Sugar']} ,

{'numb': 33, 'question': 'Yonoq', 'answer': 'Cheek', 'options': ['Diabetes', 'Cheek', 'Agreement', 'The uk']} ,

{'numb': 34, 'question': 'Kokrak qafasi', 'answer': 'Chest', 'options': ['Uncle', 'Bread', 'Planner', 'Chest']} ,

{'numb': 35, 'question': 'Iyak', 'answer': 'Chin', 'options': ['After school', 'Ocean', 'Chin', 'For me']} ,

{'numb': 36, 'question': 'Qarsak chalish', 'answer': 'Clap', 'options': ['Nobody', 'Painkiller', 'Burger', 'Clap']} ,

{'numb': 37, 'question': 'Tabriklamoq', 'answer': 'Congratulate', 'options': ['New', 'Scooter', 'Homeless', 'Congratulate']} ,

{'numb': 38, 'question': 'Dan iborat', 'answer': 'Consistof', 'options': ['Berry', 'Make a list', 'Consistof', 'Choise']} ,

{'numb': 39, 'question': 'Velosport', 'answer': 'Cycling', 'options': ['Cycling', 'Connection', 'Brilliant', 'Memory']} ,

{'numb': 40, 'question': 'Ga bogliq', 'answer': 'Depend (on)', 'options': ['Cash', 'Shop display', 'Agree', 'Depend (on)']} ,

{'numb': 41, 'question': 'Tushkunlikka tushgan', 'answer': 'Depressed', 'options': ['Sauce', 'Close', 'Depressed', 'Giraffe']} ,

{'numb': 42, 'question': 'Qandli diabet', 'answer': 'Diabetes', 'options': ['Finish work', 'Diabetes', 'Leave', 'High']} ,

{'numb': 43, 'question': 'Parhez', 'answer': 'Diet', 'options': ['Diet', 'Natural', 'Young', 'Bad manners']} ,

{'numb': 44, 'question': 'Kasallik', 'answer': 'Disease', 'options': ['Driver', 'Midday', 'Disease', 'Dark']} ,

{'numb': 45, 'question': 'Orzu qilish', 'answer': 'Dream of', 'options': ['Book your flight', 'Bother', 'Dream of', 'Class']} ,

{'numb': 46, 'question': 'Oson', 'answer': 'Easy', 'options': ['Even', 'Account', 'Supermarket', 'Easy']} ,

{'numb': 47, 'question': 'Tirsak', 'answer': 'Elbow', 'options': ['Elbow', 'Favorite', 'Purple', 'Habit']} ,

{'numb': 48, 'question': 'Tajriba', 'answer': 'Experiment', 'options': ['Experiment', 'False', 'Useful', 'Dirty']} ,

{'numb': 49, 'question': 'Musht', 'answer': 'Fist', 'options': ['Frightening', 'Modern', 'Fist', 'Grow up']} ,

{'numb': 50, 'question': 'Fitnes', 'answer': 'Fitness', 'options': ['Hero', 'Fitness', 'Close', 'House sit']} ,

{'numb': 51, 'question': 'Peshona', 'answer': 'Forehead', 'options': ['Minute', 'Forehead', 'Often', 'T-shirt']} ,

{'numb': 52, 'question': 'Muloyim', 'answer': 'Gentle', 'options': ['Small', 'Lips', 'Advantage', 'Gentle']} ,

{'numb': 53, 'question': 'Germs', 'answer': 'Germs', 'options': ['T-shirt', 'Ban', 'Shawl', 'Germs']} ,

{'numb': 54, 'question': 'Bitiruv', 'answer': 'Graduation', 'options': ['Slowly', 'Virus', 'Graduation', 'Play area']} ,

{'numb': 55, 'question': 'Salomlashish', 'answer': 'Greet', 'options': ['Greet', 'Soda', 'Map', 'Yoghurt']} ,

{'numb': 56, 'question': 'Salomlashish', 'answer': 'Greeting', 'options': ['Backwards', 'Beet', 'Greeting', 'Checkout']} ,

{'numb': 57, 'question': 'Qol siqish', 'answer': 'Handshake', 'options': ['Recognize', 'Sister', 'Handshake', 'Organize']} ,

{'numb': 58, 'question': 'Sodir bolmoq', 'answer': 'Happen', 'options': ['Recognize', 'Respond', 'Happen', 'They']} ,

{'numb': 59, 'question': 'Salomatlik', 'answer': 'Health', 'options': ['Stepmother/father', 'Health', 'Dream of', 'Answer']} ,

{'numb': 60, 'question': 'Quchoqlash', 'answer': 'Hug', 'options': ['Hug', 'Abandon', 'Lightning', 'Portuguese']} ,

{'numb': 61, 'question': 'Taassurot', 'answer': 'Impression', 'options': ['Behind', 'Businessman', 'Impression', 'Carefully']} ,

{'numb': 62, 'question': 'Spirtli ichimliklar', 'answer': 'Alcoholic drinks', 'options': ['Soap', 'Aunt', 'Alcoholic drinks', 'Science']} ,

{'numb': 63, 'question': 'Olma sharbati', 'answer': 'Apple juice', 'options': ['Atmosphere', 'Bare feet', 'Singer', 'Apple juice']} ,

{'numb': 64, 'question': 'Pishirmoq', 'answer': 'Bake', 'options': ['Take photos', 'Bake', 'Famous', 'Bad manners']} ,

{'numb': 65, 'question': 'Saqlash muddati', 'answer': 'Best before', 'options': ['Best before', 'Gift', 'Explain', 'Statement']} ,

{'numb': 66, 'question': 'Achchiq', 'answer': 'Bitter', 'options': ['Around', 'Dress', 'The usa', 'Bitter']} ,

{'numb': 67, 'question': 'Qaynatilgan', 'answer': 'Boiled', 'options': ['Common', 'Starter', 'Well', 'Boiled']} ,

{'numb': 68, 'question': 'Butilka', 'answer': 'Bottle', 'options': ['Bottle', 'Student card', 'Kitchen', 'Athletic']} ,

{'numb': 69, 'question': 'Quti', 'answer': 'Box', 'options': ['Box', 'Truck', 'Afternoon', 'Evening']} ,

{'numb': 70, 'question': 'Qila olmoq', 'answer': 'Can', 'options': ['Alphabet', 'Glue', 'Take up', 'Can']} ,

{'numb': 71, 'question': 'Karton', 'answer': 'Cardboard', 'options': ['Fog', 'Grey', 'Bowl', 'Cardboard']} ,

{'numb': 72, 'question': 'Karton', 'answer': 'Carton', 'options': ['Tell', 'Carton', 'Family', 'Team']} ,

{'numb': 73, 'question': 'Zaryad', 'answer': 'Charge', 'options': ['Charge', 'Granddaughter', 'Basic', 'Tie']} ,

{'numb': 74, 'question': 'Shokolad', 'answer': 'Chocolate', 'options': ['Learn a new language', 'Chocolate', 'Change', 'Chocolate']} ,

{'numb': 75, 'question': 'Istemolchilar', 'answer': 'Consumer', 'options': ['Fare', 'Consumer', 'Suitcase', 'Boxer']} ,

{'numb': 76, 'question': 'Kori', 'answer': 'Curry', 'options': ['Curry', 'Sleep', 'Reply', 'Armchair']} ,

{'numb': 77, 'question': 'Shirinlik', 'answer': 'Dessert', 'options': ['Dessert', 'Tuesday', 'First name', 'Ill']} ,

{'numb': 78, 'question': 'Farq', 'answer': 'Different', 'options': ['Sidewalk', 'Watch a film', 'House', 'Different']} ,

{'numb': 79, 'question': 'Taom', 'answer': 'Dish', 'options': ['Possible', 'Dish', 'Cousin', 'Spice']} ,

{'numb': 80, 'question': 'It sumkasi', 'answer': 'Doggybag', 'options': ['They', 'Talk', 'Doggybag', 'Touch']} ,

{'numb': 81, 'question': 'Shakl', 'answer': 'Figure', 'options': ['Figure', 'Lonely', 'Shelf', 'Worst']} ,

{'numb': 82, 'question': 'Lazzat', 'answer': 'Flavour', 'options': ['Flavour', 'Disappointed', 'Transportation', 'Sandwich']} ,

{'numb': 83, 'question': 'Muzlatilgan', 'answer': 'Frozen', 'options': ['Frozen', 'Ice skater', 'Railway', 'Stairs']} ,

{'numb': 84, 'question': 'Qovur', 'answer': 'Fry', 'options': ['The day after tomorrow', 'Fry', 'Think', 'Student card']} ,

{'numb': 85, 'question': 'Kulgili', 'answer': 'Funny', 'options': ['Bathroom', 'Funny', 'Mess', 'Public transport']} ,

{'numb': 86, 'question': 'Ot', 'answer': 'Herb', 'options': ['Wait', 'Jewellery', 'Thin', 'Herb']} ,

{'numb': 87, 'question': 'Asal', 'answer': 'Honey', 'options': ['Honey', 'Saxophone', 'Soil', 'Goose']} ,

{'numb': 88, 'question': 'Banka', 'answer': 'Jar', 'options': ['Cap', 'Jar', 'Uniform', 'Jumper']} ,

{'numb': 89, 'question': 'Kabi singari', 'answer': 'Kindof', 'options': ['Factory', 'Kindof', 'Kiss', 'Studio flat']} ,

{'numb': 90, 'question': 'Qozichoq', 'answer': 'Lamb', 'options': ['Swap', 'Dirty', 'Lebanese', 'Lamb']} ,

{'numb': 91, 'question': 'Tark eting', 'answer': 'Leave', 'options': ['Social media', 'Leave', 'Philosophy', 'Unnecessary']} ,

{'numb': 92, 'question': 'Chap', 'answer': 'Left', 'options': ['Left', 'Airline', 'Characters', 'Duvet']} ,

{'numb': 93, 'question': 'Belgi', 'answer': 'Mark', 'options': ['First', 'Night', 'Translator', 'Mark']} ,

{'numb': 94, 'question': 'Zaytun', 'answer': 'Olives', 'options': ['Olives', 'Europe', 'Still', 'Expensive']} ,

{'numb': 95, 'question': 'Paket', 'answer': 'Packet', 'options': ['Vietnamese', 'Code', 'Packet', 'Wedding']} ,

{'numb': 96, 'question': 'Oddiy', 'answer': 'Plain', 'options': ['Against', 'Gym', 'Ironing', 'Plain']} ,

{'numb': 97, 'question': 'Saqlash', 'answer': 'Preserve', 'options': ['Wear', 'Coach', 'Massive', 'Preserve']} ,

{'numb': 98, 'question': 'Yoqimtoy', 'answer': 'Pretty', 'options': ['Famous', 'Pretty', 'Jam', 'Client']} ,

{'numb': 99, 'question': 'Norasmiy', 'answer': 'Informal', 'options': ['Rent', 'Informal', 'The uk', 'Apply']} ,

{'numb': 100, 'question': 'Nosoglom taom', 'answer': 'Junkfood', 'options': ['Adopt', 'Journey', 'Junkfood', 'Waste']} ,

{'numb': 101, 'question': 'Opish', 'answer': 'Kiss', 'options': ['Lonely', 'Kiss', 'Flatmate', 'Belongto']} ,

{'numb': 102, 'question': 'Lab', 'answer': 'Lip', 'options': ['Depressed', 'Lip', 'Label', 'Progress']} ,

{'numb': 103, 'question': 'Tibbiy', 'answer': 'Medical', 'options': ['Go clubbing', 'Begin', 'Gorilla', 'Medical']} ,

{'numb': 104, 'question': 'Ruhiy salomatlik', 'answer': 'Mental health', 'options': ['Remote', 'Assignment', 'Badly', 'Mental health']} ,

{'numb': 105, 'question': 'Tabiiy', 'answer': 'Natural', 'options': ['Natural', 'Leave', 'Relaxed', 'Swap']} ,

{'numb': 106, 'question': 'Boshirgadi', 'answer': 'Nod', 'options': ['Nod', 'Celebrate', 'Bedroom', 'Interesting']} ,

{'numb': 107, 'question': 'Ogriq qoldiruvchi', 'answer': 'Painkiller', 'options': ['Thermometer', 'Goose', 'Daughter', 'Painkiller']} ,

{'numb': 108, 'question': 'Tinchlik', 'answer': 'Peace', 'options': ['Peace', 'Hold', 'These', 'Entrance']} ,

{'numb': 109, 'question': 'Falsafa', 'answer': 'Philosophy', 'options': ['Founder', 'Mistake', 'Sorry', 'Philosophy']} ,

{'numb': 110, 'question': 'Bosing', 'answer': 'Press', 'options': ['Fourth', 'Machine', 'Press', 'Giraffe']} ,

{'numb': 111, 'question': 'Zaxira', 'answer': 'Reserve', 'options': ['Work freelance', 'Cleaner', 'Argument', 'Reserve']} ,

{'numb': 112, 'question': 'Hurmat', 'answer': 'Respect', 'options': ['Respect', 'Benefit', 'Bathroom', 'Watermelon']} ,

{'numb': 113, 'question': 'Kulgili', 'answer': 'Ridiculous', 'options': ['Bored', 'Ironing', 'Sleeper', 'Ridiculous']} ,

{'numb': 114, 'question': 'Qopol', 'answer': 'Rude', 'options': ['Rude', 'Bathroom', 'Choise', 'Repetitivestraininjury']} ,

{'numb': 115, 'question': 'Qol silkitish', 'answer': 'Shake hands', 'options': ['Organize', 'Food processor', 'Shake hands', 'Swimming']} ,

{'numb': 116, 'question': 'Yelka', 'answer': 'Shoulder', 'options': ['Shoulder', 'Maybe', 'Put on', 'Retired']} ,

{'numb': 117, 'question': 'Yeng', 'answer': 'Sleeve', 'options': ['Reader', 'Hairdresser', 'Consistof', 'Sleeve']} ,

{'numb': 118, 'question': 'Tabassum', 'answer': 'Smile', 'options': ['Smile', 'Have a baby', 'Fishing', 'Death']} ,

{'numb': 119, 'question': 'Tayoq', 'answer': 'Stick', 'options': ['Drink', 'Mistake', 'Father', 'Stick']} ,

{'numb': 120, 'question': 'Muvaffaqiyatga erishmoq', 'answer': 'Succeed in', 'options': ['Move house or flat', 'Succeed in', 'Beautiful', 'Among']} ,

{'numb': 121, 'question': 'Bosh barmogi', 'answer': 'Thumb', 'options': ['Basic', 'With', 'Clap', 'Thumb']} ,

{'numb': 122, 'question': 'Til', 'answer': 'Tongue', 'options': ['Tongue', 'Town', 'Relationship', 'Fry']} ,

{'numb': 123, 'question': 'Teginish', 'answer': 'Touch', 'options': ['Stomach', 'Touch', 'Driver', 'Computer skills']} ,

{'numb': 124, 'question': 'Trend', 'answer': 'Trend', 'options': ['Kiss', 'Progress', 'Trend', 'Unfriendly']} ,

{'numb': 125, 'question': 'Virus', 'answer': 'Virus', 'options': ['Even', 'How', 'Use', 'Virus']} ,

{'numb': 126, 'question': 'Qurol', 'answer': 'Weapon', 'options': ['Weapon', 'Mp3 player', 'Resident', 'Gloves']} ,

{'numb': 127, 'question': 'Ogirlikni kotarish', 'answer': 'Weight litfing', 'options': ['Convenient', 'Leader', 'Location', 'Weight litfing']} ,

{'numb': 128, 'question': 'Uchun ishlash', 'answer': 'Work for', 'options': ['Skirt', 'Village', 'Land', 'Work for']} ,

{'numb': 129, 'question': 'Bagaj', 'answer': 'Luggage', 'options': ['Shawl', 'Luggage', 'Toy', 'Accident']} ,

{'numb': 130, 'question': 'Asosiy yol', 'answer': 'Main road', 'options': ['Main road', 'Tiny', 'Motorbike', 'Salad']} ,

{'numb': 131, 'question': 'Benzin', 'answer': 'Petrol', 'options': ['Petrol', 'Ill', 'Seventh', 'Cycle lane']} ,

{'numb': 132, 'question': 'Rejalashtiruvchi', 'answer': 'Planner', 'options': ['Look', 'Computer skills', 'Planner', 'Entrance']} ,

{'numb': 133, 'question': 'Ifloslanish', 'answer': 'Pollution', 'options': ['The day after tomorrow', 'Pollution', 'July', 'Class']} ,

{'numb': 134, 'question': 'Bashorat qilish', 'answer': 'Predict', 'options': ['Island', 'Predict', 'Make things', 'Bottle']} ,

{'numb': 135, 'question': 'Haqiqat', 'answer': 'Reality', 'options': ['Breakfast', 'Object', 'Hardship', 'Reality']} ,

{'numb': 136, 'question': 'Royxatga olish shakli', 'answer': 'Registration form', 'options': ['Least', 'Stressed', 'Can', 'Registration form']} ,

{'numb': 137, 'question': 'Muntazam', 'answer': 'Regular', 'options': ['Pollution', 'Have a bath', 'Regular', 'Month']} ,

{'numb': 138, 'question': 'Tinchlandi', 'answer': 'Relaxed', 'options': ['Beef', 'Feature', 'Relaxed', 'Thermometer']} ,

{'numb': 139, 'question': 'Damolish', 'answer': 'Relaxing', 'options': ['Please', 'About', 'Quite', 'Relaxing']} ,

{'numb': 140, 'question': 'Ishonchli', 'answer': 'Reliable', 'options': ['Dish', 'Reliable', 'Awake', 'Lie in']} ,

{'numb': 141, 'question': 'Masofaviy', 'answer': 'Remote', 'options': ['Remote', 'Old', 'Healthy', 'Loudly']} ,

{'numb': 142, 'question': 'Almashtiring', 'answer': 'Replace', 'options': ['Tax', 'Queue', 'Replace', 'Fridge']} ,

{'numb': 143, 'question': 'Oziga xizmat korsatish', 'answer': 'Self catering', 'options': ['Winner', 'Self catering', 'Cheese', 'Tie']} ,

{'numb': 144, 'question': 'Suvenir', 'answer': 'Souvenir', 'options': ['Valuable', 'Comedian', 'Worse', 'Souvenir']} ,

{'numb': 145, 'question': 'Hayron', 'answer': 'Surprised', 'options': ['Necessary', 'Surprised', 'Have', 'Replace']} ,

{'numb': 146, 'question': 'Hayratlanarli', 'answer': 'Surprising', 'options': ['Tour', 'Love', 'Think', 'Surprising']} ,

{'numb': 147, 'question': 'Termometr', 'answer': 'Thermometer', 'options': ['Pensil', 'Recommend', 'Thermometer', 'Benefit']} ,

{'numb': 148, 'question': 'Charchatuvchi', 'answer': 'Tiring', 'options': ['Regular', 'Hobby', 'Tiring', 'Learning skills']} ,

{'numb': 149, 'question': 'Trek', 'answer': 'Track', 'options': ['Cut', 'Compute', 'Track', 'Relationship']} ,

{'numb': 150, 'question': 'Harakat tirbandligi', 'answer': 'Traffic jam', 'options': ['Song', 'Traffic jam', 'Share', 'Journalist']} ,

{'numb': 151, 'question': 'Tashvishli', 'answer': 'Worried', 'options': ['Worried', 'Kettle', 'Access', 'New']} ,

{'numb': 152, 'question': 'Tashvishli', 'answer': 'Worrying', 'options': ['Karate', 'Worrying', 'Deal with', 'Comfortable']} ,

{'numb': 153, 'question': 'Erishish', 'answer': 'Achieve', 'options': ['Impression', 'Vacation', 'Achieve', 'Begin']} ,

{'numb': 154, 'question': 'Maktabdan keyin', 'answer': 'After school', 'options': ['Kindof', 'After school', 'Spinach', 'Copybook']} ,

{'numb': 155, 'question': 'Sanat', 'answer': 'Art', 'options': ['Art', 'Object', 'Thick', 'Clearly']} ,

{'numb': 156, 'question': 'Atmosfera', 'answer': 'Atmosphere', 'options': ['Fare', 'Advantages', 'Theatre', 'Atmosphere']} ,

{'numb': 157, 'question': 'Gullash', 'answer': 'Blossom', 'options': ['Speak', 'Chef', 'Blossom', 'Drink']} ,

{'numb': 158, 'question': 'Aloqa maxorati', 'answer': 'Communication skills', 'options': ['Developing world', 'Purse', 'Communication skills', 'Cleaner']} ,

{'numb': 159, 'question': 'Ulanish', 'answer': 'Connection', 'options': ['Connection', 'Business', 'Holiday', 'Paint']} ,

{'numb': 160, 'question': 'Kurs', 'answer': 'Course', 'options': ['Course', 'Play video games', 'This', 'Swimmer']} ,

{'numb': 161, 'question': 'Ijodiy', 'answer': 'Creatively', 'options': ['Floor', 'Creatively', 'Calmly', 'Pumpkin']} ,

{'numb': 162, 'question': 'Qaror', 'answer': 'Desicion', 'options': ['Degree', 'Desicion', 'Exactly', 'Several']} ,

{'numb': 163, 'question': 'Daraja', 'answer': 'Degree', 'options': ['Last name', 'Take', 'Sneeze', 'Degree']} ,

{'numb': 164, 'question': 'Diplom', 'answer': 'Diploma', 'options': ['Diploma', 'Title', 'Warm', 'Judo']} ,

{'numb': 165, 'question': 'Iqtisodiyot', 'answer': 'Economics', 'options': ['Leader', 'Economics', 'Wife', 'In the week']} ,

{'numb': 166, 'question': 'Talim', 'answer': 'Education', 'options': ['Beautiful', 'Key', 'Education', 'Waiter']} ,

{'numb': 167, 'question': 'Hissiyot', 'answer': 'Emotion', 'options': ['Emotion', 'Stranger', 'System', 'Lamp']} ,

{'numb': 168, 'question': 'Kirish imtihoni', 'answer': 'Entrance exam', 'options': ['Nephew', 'Entrance exam', 'Bank account', 'Cycle']} ,

{'numb': 169, 'question': 'Tushuntirmoq', 'answer': 'Explain', 'options': ['Jumper', 'Alone', 'Bridge', 'Explain']} ,

{'numb': 170, 'question': 'Toliq malakali', 'answer': 'Fully qualified', 'options': ['Picture', 'Table', 'Fully qualified', 'Fine']} ,

{'numb': 171, 'question': 'Daraja', 'answer': 'Grade', 'options': ['Community', 'Ice cream', 'Surface', 'Grade']} ,

{'numb': 172, 'question': 'Tarix', 'answer': 'History', 'options': ['History', 'Work', 'Milk', 'Coin']} ,

{'numb': 173, 'question': 'Tasavvur', 'answer': 'Imagination', 'options': ['Accountant', 'Food processor', 'Bring', 'Imagination']} ,

{'numb': 174, 'question': 'Dazmollash', 'answer': 'Ironing', 'options': ['Many', 'Gloves', 'Spanish', 'Ironing']} ,

{'numb': 175, 'question': 'Tillar', 'answer': 'Languages', 'options': ['Light', 'Achievement', 'Organization', 'Languages']} ,

{'numb': 176, 'question': 'Organish qobiliyatlari', 'answer': 'Learning skills', 'options': ['Learning skills', 'Worried', 'Negotiation', 'Time']} ,

{'numb': 177, 'question': 'Adabiyot', 'answer': 'Literature', 'options': ['Russian', 'Buy a house', 'Some', 'Literature']} ,

{'numb': 178, 'question': 'Xaritanioqish', 'answer': 'Map reading', 'options': ['Boss', 'Map reading', 'American', 'Milk']} ,

{'numb': 179, 'question': 'Magistrlik darajasi', 'answer': 'Masters degree', 'options': ['Safe', 'Masters degree', 'Dream', 'Clean']} ,

{'numb': 180, 'question': 'Matematika', 'answer': 'Math', 'options': ['Vegetables', 'Spanish', 'Math', 'Clean']} ,

{'numb': 181, 'question': 'Xato', 'answer': 'Mistake', 'options': ['Mistake', 'Buy', 'Social media', 'Great']} ,

{'numb': 182, 'question': 'Afsona', 'answer': 'Myth', 'options': ['Myth', 'Oasis', 'Apricot', 'Live with']} ,

{'numb': 183, 'question': 'Yaqin qarindosh', 'answer': 'Next of kin', 'options': ['Next of kin', 'Elderly', 'Thought', 'Outdoors']} ,

{'numb': 184, 'question': 'Organ', 'answer': 'Organ', 'options': ['Taste buds', 'Organ', 'Event', 'Bored']} ,

{'numb': 185, 'question': 'Tashkil qilish', 'answer': 'Organize', 'options': ['Newspaper', 'American', 'Festival', 'Organize']} ,

{'numb': 186, 'question': 'Jismoniy tarbiya', 'answer': 'Pe', 'options': ['Pe', 'Jog', 'Fall', 'Snowboarding']} ,

{'numb': 187, 'question': 'Fotokopi', 'answer': 'Photocopy', 'options': ['Noodles', 'Photocopy', 'Come', 'Comfort']} ,

{'numb': 188, 'question': 'Amaliy konikmalar', 'answer': 'Practical skills', 'options': ['Practical skills', 'Entrance exam', 'Denmark', 'Divorced']} ,

{'numb': 189, 'question': 'Xususiy maktab', 'answer': 'Private school', 'options': ['Essential', 'Private school', 'Trainee', 'Still']} ,

{'numb': 190, 'question': 'Ehtimol', 'answer': 'Probably', 'options': ['Lawyer', 'Bright', 'Probably', 'Often']} ,

{'numb': 191, 'question': 'Ragbatlantirish', 'answer': 'Promotion', 'options': ['Present', 'Happy', 'Promotion', 'Have a shower']} ,

{'numb': 192, 'question': 'Fan', 'answer': 'Science', 'options': ['Science', 'Careful', 'Sixth', 'Help']} ,

{'numb': 193, 'question': 'Qidiruv tizimi', 'answer': 'Search engine', 'options': ['Mixed', 'October', 'Enjoy', 'Search engine']} ,

{'numb': 194, 'question': 'Signal', 'answer': 'Signal', 'options': ['French', 'Hot', 'Lamb', 'Signal']} ,

{'numb': 195, 'question': 'Hal qilish', 'answer': 'Solve', 'options': ['Italian', 'Solve', 'Karate', 'Ice skater']} ,

{'numb': 196, 'question': 'Imlo', 'answer': 'Spelling', 'options': ['Ending', 'Aunt', 'Thank you', 'Spelling']} ,

{'numb': 197, 'question': 'Davlat maktabi', 'answer': 'State school', 'options': ['State school', 'Soon', 'Bakery', 'Noun']} ,

{'numb': 198, 'question': 'Qattiq', 'answer': 'Strict', 'options': ['Son', 'Location', 'Hobby', 'Strict']} ,

{'numb': 199, 'question': 'Organish', 'answer': 'Study', 'options': ['Garage', 'Math', 'Study', 'Wrist']} ,

{'numb': 200, 'question': 'Muvaffaqiyat', 'answer': 'Success', 'options': ['Gues house', 'Success', 'Location', 'Equipment']} ,

{'numb': 201, 'question': 'Tizimi', 'answer': 'System', 'options': ['App', 'Huge', 'Those', 'System']} ,

{'numb': 202, 'question': 'Gamhorlik qilmoq', 'answer': 'Take care of', 'options': ['Plant', 'Take care of', 'Fit', 'Meeting']} ,

{'numb': 203, 'question': 'Hazil aytib', 'answer': 'Tell jokes', 'options': ['Purse', 'Bridge', 'Walk', 'Tell jokes']} ,

{'numb': 204, 'question': 'Qorqinchli', 'answer': 'Terrible', 'options': ['Lonely', 'Photograph', 'Eleventh', 'Terrible']} ,

{'numb': 205, 'question': 'Poyezd', 'answer': 'Train', 'options': ['Quickly', 'Train', 'Low', 'Up']} ,

{'numb': 206, 'question': 'Tushunish', 'answer': 'Understand', 'options': ['Perform', 'Feeling', 'Understand', 'Takeof']} ,

{'numb': 207, 'question': 'Qabul qilish', 'answer': 'Adopt', 'options': ['Adopt', 'Jog', 'Debt', 'Father in law']} ,

{'numb': 208, 'question': 'Yomon xulq atvor', 'answer': 'Bad manners', 'options': ['But', 'Soup', 'Group', 'Bad manners']} ,

{'numb': 209, 'question': 'Eng kop sotilgan', 'answer': 'Best selling', 'options': ['Do', 'Best selling', 'Delicious', 'Guilty']} ,

{'numb': 210, 'question': 'Xususiyatlari', 'answer': 'Characteristics', 'options': ['Characteristics', 'Wine', 'First floor', 'Length']} ,

{'numb': 211, 'question': 'Oziga ishongan', 'answer': 'Confident', 'options': ['Rat', 'Need', 'Church', 'Confident']} ,

{'numb': 212, 'question': 'Juftlik', 'answer': 'Couple', 'options': ['Begin', 'Jumper', 'Actor', 'Couple']} ,

{'numb': 213, 'question': 'Ijodiy', 'answer': 'Creative', 'options': ['Excited', 'Creative', 'Charity', 'Main course']} ,

{'numb': 214, 'question': 'Insofsiz', 'answer': 'Dishonest', 'options': ['Relationship', 'Body', 'Factory', 'Dishonest']} ,

{'numb': 215, 'question': 'Tartibsiz', 'answer': 'Disorganized', 'options': ['Certainly', 'Scarf', 'Disorganized', 'Uncle']} ,

{'numb': 216, 'question': 'Ekstrovert', 'answer': 'Extrovert', 'options': ['Spring', 'Medical', 'Extrovert', 'Hour']} ,

{'numb': 217, 'question': 'Adolatli', 'answer': 'Fair', 'options': ['Fair', 'Organize', 'Grade', 'Bent']} ,

{'numb': 218, 'question': 'Qaynota', 'answer': 'Father in law', 'options': ['Miss', 'Father in law', 'Hotel', 'Factory']} ,

{'numb': 219, 'question': 'Kvartiradosh', 'answer': 'Flatmate', 'options': ['Safe', 'Driver', 'Consequence', 'Flatmate']} ,

{'numb': 220, 'question': 'Dostona', 'answer': 'Friendly', 'options': ['Best', 'Friendly', 'World', 'Stairs']} ,

{'numb': 221, 'question': 'Ajrashmoq', 'answer': 'Get divorced', 'options': ['Permit', 'Get divorced', 'Mosquito', 'Deal with']} ,

{'numb': 222, 'question': 'Tirishqoq', 'answer': 'Hard working', 'options': ['Wire', 'Hard working', 'Task', 'Rise']} ,

{'numb': 223, 'question': 'Halol', 'answer': 'Honest', 'options': ['But', 'Honest', 'People', 'Circumstances']} ,

{'numb': 224, 'question': 'Sabrsiz', 'answer': 'Impatient', 'options': ['Impatient', 'Suchã‚', 'Vietnamese', 'Supermarket']} ,

{'numb': 225, 'question': 'Qopol', 'answer': 'Impolite', 'options': ['Impolite', 'Forwards', 'Stepfather', 'Real']} ,

{'numb': 226, 'question': 'Zarur', 'answer': 'Necessary', 'options': ['Chemist', 'Heel', 'Quickly', 'Necessary']} ,

{'numb': 227, 'question': 'Sabr', 'answer': 'Patient', 'options': ['Look after', 'Black', 'Patient', 'What']} ,

{'numb': 228, 'question': 'Mumkin', 'answer': 'Possible', 'options': ['Married', 'Possible', 'Menu', 'Tuesday']} ,

{'numb': 229, 'question': 'Bogliq', 'answer': 'Related', 'options': ['Right', 'Related', 'Well', 'Big']} ,

{'numb': 230, 'question': 'Romantik', 'answer': 'Romantic', 'options': ['Pull out', 'Romantic', 'Cold', 'Lamp']} ,

{'numb': 231, 'question': 'Alohida', 'answer': 'Separate', 'options': ['Win', 'Eat', 'Get ill', 'Separate']} ,

{'numb': 232, 'question': 'Uyatchan', 'answer': 'Shy', 'options': ['Glass', 'Turn', 'Shy', 'Receive']} ,

{'numb': 233, 'question': 'Toplanish', 'answer': 'Clurp', 'options': ['Key', 'Left', 'Season', 'Clurp']} ,

{'numb': 234, 'question': 'Aqlli', 'answer': 'Smart', 'options': ['Thursday', 'Reading glasses', 'Smart', 'Start']} ,

{'numb': 235, 'question': 'Xushmuomala', 'answer': 'Sociable', 'options': ['Toilet', 'Orange', 'Marathon', 'Sociable']} ,

{'numb': 236, 'question': 'Ogay ona/ota', 'answer': 'Stepmother/father', 'options': ['Dish', 'Seat belt', 'Stepmother/father', 'Clever']} ,

{'numb': 237, 'question': 'Ahmoq', 'answer': 'Stupid', 'options': ['Correctly', 'Neighbor', 'Wait', 'Stupid']} ,

{'numb': 238, 'question': 'Egizaklar', 'answer': 'Twins', 'options': ['Amazed', 'Beautiful', 'Repetitivestraininjury', 'Twins']} ,

{'numb': 239, 'question': 'Adolatsiz', 'answer': 'Unfair', 'options': ['Musician', 'Head', 'Public transport', 'Unfair']} ,

{'numb': 240, 'question': 'Dostona emas', 'answer': 'Unfriendly', 'options': ['Unfriendly', 'Widowed', 'Stupid', 'Switch']} ,

{'numb': 241, 'question': 'Shafqatsiz', 'answer': 'Unkind', 'options': ['Unkind', 'On theinternet', 'Ask', 'Retirement']} ,

{'numb': 242, 'question': 'Omadsiz', 'answer': 'Unlucky', 'options': ['Attack', 'Student', 'Unlucky', 'Peace']} ,

{'numb': 243, 'question': 'Keraksiz', 'answer': 'Unnecessary', 'options': ['Plastic', 'Postcard', 'Unnecessary', 'Vegetables']} ,

{'numb': 244, 'question': 'Murosasiz', 'answer': 'Unsociable', 'options': ['Dentist', 'Bathroom', 'Unsociable', 'Annoying']} ,

{'numb': 245, 'question': 'Tartibsiz', 'answer': 'Untidy', 'options': ['Queue', 'Untidy', 'Jumper', 'Artist']} ,

{'numb': 246, 'question': 'Odatiy', 'answer': 'Usual', 'options': ['Dining room', 'Usual', 'Clean', 'Benefit']} ,

{'numb': 247, 'question': 'Ish joyi', 'answer': 'Workplace', 'options': ['Guitar', 'Chips', 'Workplace', 'Link']} ,

{'numb': 248, 'question': 'Turar joy', 'answer': 'Accommodation', 'options': ['Accommodation', 'Live with', 'Cruel', 'Menu']} ,

{'numb': 249, 'question': 'Afzalliklari', 'answer': 'Advantages', 'options': ['Advantages', 'Since', 'Athletic', 'Best selling']} ,

{'numb': 250, 'question': 'Hayratda qoldi', 'answer': 'Amazed', 'options': ['Hard working', 'Amazed', 'Marathon', 'Fair']} ,

{'numb': 251, 'question': 'Bezovta', 'answer': 'Annoyed', 'options': ['Ball', 'Annoyed', 'Shovel', 'Go to the theatre']} ,

{'numb': 252, 'question': 'Bezovta qiluvchi', 'answer': 'Annoying', 'options': ['Try', 'Recommend', 'Exercise', 'Annoying']} ,

{'numb': 253, 'question': 'Murojaat qiling', 'answer': 'Apply', 'options': ['Forehead', 'Imagination', 'Apply', 'Shocking']} ,

{'numb': 254, 'question': 'Asosiy', 'answer': 'Basic', 'options': ['Basic', 'Thank', 'Cancer', 'Can']} ,

{'numb': 255, 'question': 'Oldindan bron qiling', 'answer': 'Book in advance', 'options': ['Painter', 'Book in advance', 'Match', 'Grandson']} ,

{'numb': 256, 'question': 'Parvozingizni bron qiling', 'answer': 'Book your flight', 'options': ['Airport', 'Book your flight', 'Tennis', 'Sleeping bag']} ,

{'numb': 257, 'question': 'Zerikkan', 'answer': 'Bored', 'options': ['Rooftop', 'Sugar', 'Spinach', 'Bored']} ,

{'numb': 258, 'question': 'Avtobus chiptasi', 'answer': 'Bus pass', 'options': ['Honey', 'Interested in', 'Bus pass', 'Next']} ,

{'numb': 259, 'question': 'Kod', 'answer': 'Code', 'options': ['Code', 'Chief', 'Organ', 'Life']} ,

{'numb': 260, 'question': 'Chalkash', 'answer': 'Confusing', 'options': ['Several', 'Sleeping bag', 'Confusing', 'Comfort']} ,

{'numb': 261, 'question': 'Qulay', 'answer': 'Convenient', 'options': ['Lazy', 'Convenient', 'Romantic', 'Online']} ,

{'numb': 262, 'question': 'Valyuta', 'answer': 'Currency', 'options': ['Feeble', 'Ban', 'Currency', 'Really']} ,

{'numb': 263, 'question': 'Velosiped yolagi', 'answer': 'Cycle lane', 'options': ['Cycle lane', 'Clear', 'Knee', 'Thick']} ,

{'numb': 264, 'question': 'Rivojlanish', 'answer': 'Development', 'options': ['Development', 'Best before', 'Wine', 'Kitchen']} ,

{'numb': 265, 'question': 'Dizel', 'answer': 'Diesel', 'options': ['Goodbye', 'Location', 'Diesel', 'Maximum']} ,

{'numb': 266, 'question': 'Samarali', 'answer': 'Efficient', 'options': ['Economy', 'Efficient', 'Flower', 'Go']} ,

{'numb': 267, 'question': 'Sharmandali', 'answer': 'Embarrassing', 'options': ['Name', 'Embarrassing', 'Book in advance', 'Pretty']} ,

{'numb': 268, 'question': 'Hayajonli', 'answer': 'Exciting', 'options': ['Statistic', 'Exciting', 'Personal', 'Hungarian']} ,

{'numb': 269, 'question': 'Yolhaqi', 'answer': 'Fare', 'options': ['Invitation', 'Fare', 'Mixed', 'Advantages']} ,

{'numb': 270, 'question': 'Maftunkor', 'answer': 'Fascinating', 'options': ['Move abroad', 'Extrovert', 'Flatmate', 'Fascinating']} ,

{'numb': 271, 'question': 'Maftunbolgan', 'answer': 'Fascinated', 'options': ['Walk', 'Clever', 'Collection', 'Fascinated']} ,

{'numb': 272, 'question': 'Suzmoq', 'answer': 'Float', 'options': ['Sheet', 'Float', 'Leg', 'Est']} ,

{'numb': 273, 'question': 'Xorijiy', 'answer': 'Foreign', 'options': ['Bare feet', 'Another', 'Real', 'Foreign']} ,

{'numb': 274, 'question': 'Qorqituvchi', 'answer': 'Frightening', 'options': ['Cloudy', 'Pizza', 'Interesting', 'Frightening']} ,

{'numb': 275, 'question': 'Yoqilgi', 'answer': 'Fuel', 'options': ['Country', 'Clear', 'South africa', 'Fuel']} ,

{'numb': 276, 'question': 'Yashilroq', 'answer': 'Greener', 'options': ['Complete', 'Speed', 'Greener', 'Acquaintance']} ,

{'numb': 277, 'question': 'Qollanma', 'answer': 'Guidebook', 'options': ['Guidebook', 'Sink', 'Sandwich', 'Dry']} ,

{'numb': 278, 'question': 'Yuqori tezlik', 'answer': 'High speed', 'options': ['Read', 'Letter', 'Tropical', 'High speed']} ,

{'numb': 279, 'question': 'Yollash', 'answer': 'Hire', 'options': ['Hire', 'Real', 'Long', 'Self catering']} ,

{'numb': 280, 'question': 'Yotoqxona', 'answer': 'Hostel', 'options': ['Winter', 'Name', 'Employee', 'Hostel']} ,

{'numb': 281, 'question': 'Oldindan', 'answer': 'In advance', 'options': ['In advance', 'Paint', 'Bakery', 'Useful']} ,

{'numb': 282, 'question': 'Sugurta', 'answer': 'Insurance', 'options': ['Possession', 'Insurance', 'Kettle', 'Sell']} ,

{'numb': 283, 'question': 'Oxirgi daqiqa', 'answer': 'Last minute', 'options': ['Last minute', 'Finger', 'Oasis', 'Question']} ,

{'numb': 284, 'question': 'Chiziq', 'answer': 'Line', 'options': ['Line', 'A day off', 'Stairs', 'Trainers']} ,

{'numb': 285, 'question': 'Qabulqilish', 'answer': 'Receive', 'options': ['Avoid', 'Parking space', 'Receive', 'Living']} ,

{'numb': 286, 'question': 'Takroriy kuchlanish shikastlanishi', 'answer': 'Repetitivestraininjury', 'options': ['Repetitivestraininjury', 'Suitable', 'Hate', 'Lemon']} ,

{'numb': 287, 'question': 'Nafaqaga chiqish', 'answer': 'Retire', 'options': ['Stop', 'Retire', 'Ice skater', 'Walk']} ,

{'numb': 288, 'question': 'Korib chiqish', 'answer': 'Review', 'options': ['Light', 'Sheet', 'Review', 'Begin']} ,

{'numb': 289, 'question': 'Dengiz qirgogi', 'answer': 'Seafront', 'options': ['Call', 'Seafront', 'Stockings', 'Nobody']} ,

{'numb': 290, 'question': 'Bahamkoring', 'answer': 'Share', 'options': ['Share', 'Stockings', 'Baseball', 'Sidewalk']} ,

{'numb': 291, 'question': 'Onlayn xarid qilish', 'answer': 'Shop online', 'options': ['Shop online', 'Angrily', 'Bucket', 'Stockings']} ,

{'numb': 292, 'question': 'Ijtimoiy tarmoqlar', 'answer': 'Social media', 'options': ['Introduce', 'Award', 'Maiden name', 'Social media']} ,

{'numb': 293, 'question': 'Egallash kirishish', 'answer': 'Take up', 'options': ['Afternoon', 'Love', 'Take up', 'Lovely']} ,

{'numb': 294, 'question': 'Gapirish', 'answer': 'Talk', 'options': ['Helmet', 'Talk', 'Paper clip', 'Scientist']} ,

{'numb': 295, 'question': 'Osmir', 'answer': 'Teenager', 'options': ['Little', 'Funny', 'Swim', 'Teenager']} ,

{'numb': 296, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Travel', 'options': ['Travel', 'Communication skills', 'Vacant', 'Luggage']} ,

{'numb': 297, 'question': 'Tvit', 'answer': 'Tweet', 'options': ['Play area', 'Tweet', 'North', 'Camping']} ,

{'numb': 298, 'question': 'Yangilash', 'answer': 'Update', 'options': ['Bear', 'Plastic', 'Update', 'Hand']} ,

{'numb': 299, 'question': 'Foydalanish', 'answer': 'Use', 'options': ['Self catering', 'Use', 'Old', 'Hard working']} ,

{'numb': 300, 'question': 'Vaza', 'answer': 'Vase', 'options': ['Most', 'Make plans', 'Exercise', 'Vase']} ,

{'numb': 301, 'question': 'Vegetarian taomlari kitobi', 'answer': 'Vegetarian cookbook', 'options': ['Trouser', 'Vegetarian cookbook', 'In front of', 'Minimalist']} ,

{'numb': 302, 'question': 'Maslahat', 'answer': 'Advice', 'options': ['What a pity', 'Moon', 'Advice', 'History']} ,

{'numb': 303, 'question': 'Imkoniyatiga ega', 'answer': 'Afford', 'options': ['Interested in', 'Afford', 'Grandmother', 'What a pity']} ,

{'numb': 304, 'question': 'Antiqa', 'answer': 'Antique', 'options': ['Sleep', 'Illnes', 'Son', 'Antique']} ,

{'numb': 305, 'question': 'Muvozanat', 'answer': 'Balance', 'options': ['Squirrel', 'Balance', 'Ballon', 'Bath']} ,

{'numb': 306, 'question': 'Bank hisob raqami', 'answer': 'Bank account', 'options': ['Excuse', 'Bank account', 'Code', 'Predict']} ,

{'numb': 307, 'question': 'Foyda', 'answer': 'Benefit', 'options': ['Husband', 'Chin', 'Disappointed', 'Benefit']} ,

{'numb': 308, 'question': 'Hisob', 'answer': 'Bill', 'options': ['Bill', 'Possess', 'Newspaper', 'Development']} ,

{'numb': 309, 'question': 'Qarz oldi', 'answer': 'Borrowed', 'options': ['Next', 'Outdoors', 'Shopping centre', 'Borrowed']} ,

{'numb': 310, 'question': 'Yangi', 'answer': 'Brand new', 'options': ['Subtropical', 'Brand new', 'Driver', 'Car mechanic']} ,

{'numb': 311, 'question': 'Yorqin', 'answer': 'Bright', 'options': ['Spinach', 'Serve', 'Curry', 'Bright']} ,

{'numb': 312, 'question': 'Xaridor', 'answer': 'Buyer', 'options': ['Hairdresserãšâ¼s', 'Home', 'Lemon', 'Buyer']} ,

{'numb': 313, 'question': 'Ozgartirish', 'answer': 'Change', 'options': ['Red', 'Change', 'Fishing', 'Receive']} ,

{'numb': 314, 'question': 'Tanga', 'answer': 'Coin', 'options': ['Coin', 'Watch tv', 'Architect', 'Organize']} ,

{'numb': 315, 'question': 'Yigish', 'answer': 'Collection', 'options': ['Airport', 'Bill', 'Last name', 'Collection']} ,

{'numb': 316, 'question': 'Qulaylik', 'answer': 'Comfort', 'options': ['Comfort', 'Arm', 'Dirty', 'Still']} ,

{'numb': 317, 'question': 'Qulay', 'answer': 'Comfortable', 'options': ['Foreign language', 'Enjoy', 'Homework', 'Comfortable']} ,

{'numb': 318, 'question': 'Hisoblash', 'answer': 'Compute', 'options': ['Contact', 'Learn', 'Cold', 'Compute']} ,

{'numb': 319, 'question': 'Holat', 'answer': 'Condition', 'options': ['Cut', 'Characteristics', 'Condition', 'Confused']} ,

{'numb': 320, 'question': 'Kredit kartasi', 'answer': 'Credit card', 'options': ['Wedding', 'Literature', 'Credit card', 'Busy']} ,

{'numb': 321, 'question': 'Jinoyat', 'answer': 'Crime', 'options': ['Post', 'Crime', 'Bus driver', 'Shorts']} ,

{'numb': 322, 'question': 'Qorongi', 'answer': 'Dark', 'options': ['Benefit', 'Progress', 'Leader', 'Dark']} ,

{'numb': 323, 'question': 'Qarz', 'answer': 'Debt', 'options': ['Useful', 'Duvet', 'Partner', 'Debt']} ,

{'numb': 324, 'question': 'Qaror', 'answer': 'Decide', 'options': ['Decide', 'Get around', 'Purse', 'Heavy']} ,

{'numb': 325, 'question': 'Rivojlanayotgan dunyo', 'answer': 'Developing world', 'options': ['Germs', 'Get divorced', 'Developing world', 'Genetic']} ,

{'numb': 326, 'question': 'Raqam', 'answer': 'Digit', 'options': ['Armchair', 'Digit', 'Flat', 'Romantic']} ,

{'numb': 327, 'question': 'Raqamli', 'answer': 'Digital', 'options': ['Digital', 'Rope', 'Garlic', 'Shorts']} ,

{'numb': 328, 'question': 'Umidsizlik', 'answer': 'Disappointment', 'options': ['Trainee', 'Thursday', 'Disappointment', 'Tired']} ,

{'numb': 329, 'question': 'Iqtisodiyot', 'answer': 'Economy', 'options': ['Behaviour', 'Kiss', 'Economy', 'Industry']} ,

{'numb': 330, 'question': 'Rohatlaning', 'answer': 'Enjoy', 'options': ['Comfort', 'Enjoy', 'Sock', 'January']} ,

{'numb': 331, 'question': 'Zavqli', 'answer': 'Enjoyable', 'options': ['Enjoyable', 'Birth date', 'Parachute', 'Receive']} ,

{'numb': 332, 'question': 'Jihozlash', 'answer': 'Equip', 'options': ['Rabbit', 'Equip', 'Twentieth', 'Swimmer']} ,

{'numb': 333, 'question': 'Muhim', 'answer': 'Essential', 'options': ['Tiny', 'Seventh', 'Word', 'Essential']} ,

{'numb': 334, 'question': 'Moda', 'answer': 'Fashionable', 'options': ['Fashionable', 'Bus pass', 'Giraffe', 'Tale']} ,

{'numb': 335, 'question': 'Haq', 'answer': 'Fee', 'options': ['Eye contact', 'Fee', 'Lamb', 'Success']} ,

{'numb': 336, 'question': 'Ogir', 'answer': 'Heavy', 'options': ['Heavy', 'Consumer', 'Text', 'Colleague']} ,

{'numb': 337, 'question': 'Katta', 'answer': 'Large', 'options': ['Careful', 'Large', 'Mirror', 'Refreshments']} ,

{'numb': 338, 'question': 'Teri', 'answer': 'Leather', 'options': ['Leather', 'Partner', 'Code', 'Tie']} ,

{'numb': 339, 'question': 'Qarz bergan', 'answer': 'Lent', 'options': ['Lent', 'Shout', 'Float', 'Dark']} ,

{'numb': 340, 'question': 'Metall', 'answer': 'Metal', 'options': ['Walker', 'On theinternet', 'Carton', 'Metal']} ,

{'numb': 341, 'question': 'Minimalist', 'answer': 'Minimalist', 'options': ['Return', 'Angry', 'Minimalist', 'On']} ,

{'numb': 342, 'question': 'Chivin', 'answer': 'Mosquito', 'options': ['Butter', 'Kilogramm', 'Russia', 'Mosquito']} ,

{'numb': 343, 'question': 'Eslatma', 'answer': 'Note', 'options': ['Pass your exams', 'Foolish', 'Rabbit', 'Note']} ,

{'numb': 344, 'question': 'Qarz', 'answer': 'Owe', 'options': ['Owe', 'Air conditioned', 'Pair', 'Be']} ,

{'numb': 345, 'question': 'Rangpar', 'answer': 'Pale', 'options': ['Pale', 'Quite', 'Maybe', 'Journalist']} ,

{'numb': 346, 'question': 'Tolov', 'answer': 'Payback', 'options': ['Useby', 'Nephew', 'Payback', 'Wake']} ,

{'numb': 347, 'question': 'Shaxsiy', 'answer': 'Personal', 'options': ['Bedroom', 'Play', 'Personal', 'Uncle']} ,

{'numb': 348, 'question': 'Plastik', 'answer': 'Plastic', 'options': ['Plastic', 'Dirty', 'Predict', 'In front of']} ,

{'numb': 349, 'question': 'Egalik qilish', 'answer': 'Possess', 'options': ['Delivery', 'Possess', 'Lonely', 'Main course']} ,

{'numb': 350, 'question': 'Egalik qilish', 'answer': 'Possession', 'options': ['Possession', 'On time', 'Arrive', 'Astronaut']} ,

{'numb': 351, 'question': 'Hamyon', 'answer': 'Purse', 'options': ['Purse', 'Bake', 'Check in', 'Introduce']} ,

{'numb': 352, 'question': 'Qaytarib berish', 'answer': 'Refund', 'options': ['Sandy', 'Refund', 'Fermer', 'Stall']} ,

{'numb': 353, 'question': 'Ijara', 'answer': 'Rent', 'options': ['Workplace', 'Umbrella', 'Guest', 'Rent']} ,

{'numb': 354, 'question': 'Qaytaruvchi', 'answer': 'Repellent', 'options': ['Repellent', 'Surname', 'Karate', 'Homeless']} ,

{'numb': 355, 'question': 'Inqilob', 'answer': 'Revolution', 'options': ['Pale', 'Revolution', 'Napkin', 'Shout']} ,

{'numb': 356, 'question': 'Saqla', 'answer': 'Save up', 'options': ['Score', 'Outside', 'Russian', 'Save up']} ,

{'numb': 357, 'question': 'Skuter', 'answer': 'Scooter', 'options': ['Scooter', 'Grass', 'Greener', 'Surname']} ,

{'numb': 358, 'question': 'Yaltiroq', 'answer': 'Shiny', 'options': ['Bare feet', 'Ride', 'Shiny', 'Arm']} ,

{'numb': 359, 'question': 'Maxsus', 'answer': 'Special', 'options': ['Seal', 'Special', 'Icy', 'Location']} ,

{'numb': 360, 'question': 'Statistika', 'answer': 'Statistic', 'options': ['Mother', 'Subtropical', 'Tree', 'Statistic']} ,

{'numb': 361, 'question': 'Urgu', 'answer': 'Stress', 'options': ['Packet', 'In the week', 'Dark', 'Stress']} ,

{'numb': 362, 'question': 'Stressli', 'answer': 'Stressful', 'options': ['Colorful', 'Discuss', 'Stressful', 'Warm']} ,

{'numb': 363, 'question': 'Mos', 'answer': 'Suitable', 'options': ['Suitable', 'Collect', 'Roast', 'Ship']} ,

{'numb': 364, 'question': 'Yupqa', 'answer': 'Thin', 'options': ['Fridge', 'Rainforest', 'Thin', 'Crime']} ,

{'numb': 365, 'question': 'Vaqt kapsulasi', 'answer': 'Timecapsule', 'options': ['Village', 'Women', 'Timecapsule', 'Personal']} ,

{'numb': 366, 'question': 'Transfer', 'answer': 'Transfer', 'options': ['Transfer', 'Great', 'Juice', 'Yet']} ,

{'numb': 367, 'question': 'Foydali', 'answer': 'Useful', 'options': ['Oath', 'Useful', 'Monday', 'Often']} ,

{'numb': 368, 'question': 'Qimmatli', 'answer': 'Valuable', 'options': ['Plan', 'Put', 'Valuable', 'Honey']} ,

{'numb': 369, 'question': 'Hamyon', 'answer': 'Wallet', 'options': ['Air conditioned', 'Wallet', 'Cafe', 'Science']} ,

{'numb': 370, 'question': 'Muvaffaqiyat', 'answer': 'Achievement', 'options': ['Physical', 'Achievement', 'Worried', 'Moon']} ,

{'numb': 371, 'question': 'Jahl bilan', 'answer': 'Angrily', 'options': ['Lips', 'Angrily', 'Teach', 'Chair']} ,

{'numb': 372, 'question': 'Badjahl', 'answer': 'Angry', 'options': ['Code', 'Angry', 'Spain', 'Article']} ,

{'numb': 373, 'question': 'Tashvishli', 'answer': 'Anxious', 'options': ['Wash basin', 'Degree', 'Left', 'Anxious']} ,

{'numb': 374, 'question': 'Qochish', 'answer': 'Avoid', 'options': ['Line', 'Public transport', 'Picture', 'Avoid']} ,

{'numb': 375, 'question': 'Orqaga', 'answer': 'Backwards', 'options': ['Eyesight', 'Watch', 'The day before yesterday', 'Backwards']} ,

{'numb': 376, 'question': 'Shar', 'answer': 'Balloon', 'options': ['Distance', 'Achieve', 'Frightened', 'Balloon']} ,

{'numb': 377, 'question': 'Xulq atvor', 'answer': 'Behaviour', 'options': ['Mp3 player', 'Confusing', 'Behaviour', 'Eat']} ,

{'numb': 378, 'question': 'Bezovta qilmoq', 'answer': 'Bother', 'options': ['September', 'Bother', 'Carton', 'Typical']} ,

{'numb': 379, 'question': 'Xotirjamlik bilan', 'answer': 'Calmly', 'options': ['Up', 'Bakery', 'Distance', 'Calmly']} ,

{'numb': 380, 'question': 'Kapsula', 'answer': 'Capsule', 'options': ['Capsule', 'My', 'Kettle', 'Letter']} ,

{'numb': 381, 'question': 'Kotarilish', 'answer': 'Climb', 'options': ['Ceremony', 'Climb', 'Center', 'Painkiller']} ,

{'numb': 382, 'question': 'Chalkash', 'answer': 'Confused', 'options': ['Ear', 'Confused', 'Italian', 'Cycle lane']} ,

{'numb': 383, 'question': 'Oshpaz', 'answer': 'Cook', 'options': ['Capsule', 'Apple juice', 'Windowsill', 'Cook']} ,

{'numb': 384, 'question': 'Shongin', 'answer': 'Dive', 'options': ['Dive', 'Board', 'Middle aged', 'Mixed']} ,

{'numb': 385, 'question': 'Tushirish', 'answer': 'Drop', 'options': ['Drop', 'Waste', 'Fast lane', 'When']} ,

{'numb': 386, 'question': 'Osongina', 'answer': 'Easily', 'options': ['Rope', 'Easily', 'Toast', 'Learning skills']} ,

{'numb': 387, 'question': 'Yeyuvchi', 'answer': 'Eater', 'options': ['Day', 'Jam', 'Eater', 'Sister']} ,

{'numb': 388, 'question': 'Xijolat tortdi', 'answer': 'Embarrassed', 'options': ['Photograph', 'Embarrassed', 'Laptop', 'Mild']} ,

{'numb': 389, 'question': 'Ajoyib', 'answer': 'Excited', 'options': ['Amazed', 'Excited', 'Enjoyable', 'Dining room']} ,

{'numb': 390, 'question': 'Charchagan', 'answer': 'Exhausted', 'options': ['Kitchen', 'Fear', 'Exhausted', 'Important']} ,

{'numb': 391, 'question': 'Kozbilan aloqa qilish', 'answer': 'Eye contact', 'options': ['Eye contact', 'Roast', 'Eye contact', 'Roast']} ,

{'numb': 392, 'question': 'Tushish', 'answer': 'Fall', 'options': ['Sick', 'Half past', 'Fall', 'New zealand']} ,

{'numb': 393, 'question': 'Ravon', 'answer': 'Fluently', 'options': ['Grandfather', 'Comedian', 'Romania', 'Fluently']} ,

{'numb': 394, 'question': 'Oldinga', 'answer': 'Forwards', 'options': ['Mobile phone', 'Relationship', 'Forwards', 'Canteen']} ,

{'numb': 395, 'question': 'Qorqib ketgan', 'answer': 'Frightened', 'options': ['For me', 'Frightened', 'Cycling', 'Advantages']} ,

{'numb': 396, 'question': 'Aybdor', 'answer': 'Guilty', 'options': ['Organized', 'Brush', 'Like', 'Guilty']} ,

{'numb': 397, 'question': 'Naushniklar', 'answer': 'Headphones', 'options': ['Have a bath', 'Headphones', 'Place of birth', 'Embarrassing']} ,

{'numb': 398, 'question': 'Yaxshi kayfiyatda', 'answer': 'In a good mood', 'options': ['Just', 'In a good mood', 'Change', 'Postcard']} ,

{'numb': 399, 'question': 'Interkom', 'answer': 'Intercom', 'options': ['Intercom', 'Solid', 'Tale', 'Underground']} ,

{'numb': 400, 'question': 'Ichiga', 'answer': 'Into', 'options': ['Into', 'Promotion', 'Make arrangements', 'Diesel']} ,

{'numb': 401, 'question': 'Sakramoq', 'answer': 'Jump', 'options': ['Jump', 'Owe', 'Waiter', 'Forest']} ,

{'numb': 402, 'question': 'Lift', 'answer': 'Lift', 'options': ['Exercise', 'Lift', 'Agree', 'Advice']} ,

{'numb': 403, 'question': 'Yer', 'answer': 'Land', 'options': ['Land', 'Bus', 'Exercise', 'Suggest']} ,

{'numb': 404, 'question': 'Baland ovozda', 'answer': 'Loudly', 'options': ['Break', 'Fence', 'Loudly', 'Cup']} ,

{'numb': 405, 'question': 'Asabiy', 'answer': 'Nervous', 'options': ['Succeed in', 'Cost', 'Conversation', 'Nervous']} ,

{'numb': 406, 'question': 'Yaxshigina', 'answer': 'Nicely', 'options': ['Painkiller', 'Nicely', 'Meal', 'Time']} ,

{'numb': 407, 'question': 'Haqida', 'answer': 'About', 'options': ['Fridge', 'Herb', 'About', 'Peace']} ,

{'numb': 408, 'question': 'Yetib kelish', 'answer': 'Arrive', 'options': ['Perhaps', 'Arrive', 'Lucky', 'Badly']} ,

{'numb': 409, 'question': 'Hujum', 'answer': 'Attack', 'options': ['South africa', 'Unsociable', 'Switch', 'Attack']} ,

{'numb': 410, 'question': 'Bolish', 'answer': 'Become', 'options': ['Fifth', 'Tell', 'Become', 'Throw']} ,

{'numb': 411, 'question': 'Blog', 'answer': 'Blog', 'options': ['Vietnam', 'Burger', 'Change', 'Blog']} ,

{'numb': 412, 'question': 'Bokschi', 'answer': 'Boxer', 'options': ['Motorbike', 'Snack', 'Maiden name', 'Boxer']} ,

{'numb': 413, 'question': 'Sotib olish', 'answer': 'Buy', 'options': ['Second', 'Change jobs', 'Buy', 'Flavour']} ,

{'numb': 414, 'question': 'Qiyinchilik', 'answer': 'Challenge', 'options': ['Challenge', 'Tweet', 'Reviewer', 'Peach']} ,

{'numb': 415, 'question': 'Tasodifiy martaba', 'answer': 'Chance career', 'options': ['Tourist information centre', 'Starter', 'Chance career', 'Card games']} ,

{'numb': 416, 'question': 'Tanlang', 'answer': 'Choose', 'options': ['Choose', 'Disappointed', 'Suit', 'Eater']} ,

{'numb': 417, 'question': 'Konsert zali', 'answer': 'Concert hall', 'options': ['Behind', 'Granddaughter', 'Nice', 'Concert hall']} ,

{'numb': 418, 'question': 'Dirijyor', 'answer': 'Conducter', 'options': ['Air conditioning', 'Finish work', 'Judo', 'Conducter']} ,

{'numb': 419, 'question': 'Ish kormoq shugullanmoq', 'answer': 'Deal with', 'options': ['Desicion', 'Pet', 'Mistake', 'Deal with']} ,

{'numb': 420, 'question': 'Onlayn banking bilan shugullaning', 'answer': 'Do online banking', 'options': ['Do online banking', 'Family name', 'Expensive', 'Bottle']} ,

{'numb': 421, 'question': 'Yuklab oling', 'answer': 'Download', 'options': ['Download', 'Worrying', 'Box', 'Sister']} ,

{'numb': 422, 'question': 'Unashtirilgan', 'answer': 'Engaged', 'options': ['Engaged', 'Wrist', 'Take care of', 'Seventh']} ,

{'numb': 423, 'question': 'Turmush qurmoq', 'answer': 'Get merried', 'options': ['Public transport', 'Tomato', 'Get merried', 'Apply']} ,

{'numb': 424, 'question': 'Onlayn oting', 'answer': 'Go online', 'options': ['Scientific', 'Product', 'Go fishing', 'Go online']} ,

{'numb': 425, 'question': 'Ga boring', 'answer': 'Go to', 'options': ['Tie', 'Go to', 'March', 'Money']} ,

{'numb': 426, 'question': 'Farzandli boling', 'answer': 'Have a baby', 'options': ['Have a baby', 'Sickness', 'Gym', 'Environment']} ,

{'numb': 427, 'question': 'Yigirmanchi yillar oxirida', 'answer': 'In late twenties', 'options': ['Masters degree', 'In late twenties', 'Machine', 'Bark']} ,

{'numb': 428, 'question': 'Oltmishinchi yillarda', 'answer': 'In sixties', 'options': ['Have breakfast', 'Worker', 'In sixties', 'Animal']} ,

{'numb': 429, 'question': 'Suzishni organing', 'answer': 'Learn to swim', 'options': ['Last', 'Learn to swim', 'Hot', 'Practical skills']} ,

{'numb': 430, 'question': 'Uydan ket', 'answer': 'Leave home', 'options': ['Airport', 'Leave home', 'Fit', 'Road']} ,

{'numb': 431, 'question': 'Bilan yashash', 'answer': 'Live with', 'options': ['Live with', 'Skin', 'Boring', 'Thanks']} ,

{'numb': 432, 'question': 'Tizimga kirish', 'answer': 'Log on', 'options': ['Log on', 'Future', 'Twins', 'Sauce']} ,

{'numb': 433, 'question': 'Orta', 'answer': 'Mid', 'options': ['Mid', 'Make a list', 'Chest', 'Center']} ,

{'numb': 434, 'question': 'Orta yoshli', 'answer': 'Middle aged', 'options': ['Bedroom', 'Literature', 'Middle aged', 'Go to the cinema']} ,

{'numb': 435, 'question': 'Moment', 'answer': 'Moment', 'options': ['Moment', 'Receipt', 'Bucket', 'Fifth']} ,

{'numb': 436, 'question': 'Uy yoki kvartirani kochirish', 'answer': 'Move house or flat', 'options': ['Agree', 'Move house or flat', 'Centre', 'Free']} ,

{'numb': 437, 'question': 'Oladi', 'answer': 'Obtains', 'options': ['Calendar', 'Signal', 'Obtains', 'Fry']} ,

{'numb': 438, 'question': 'Imtihonlaringizni topshiring', 'answer': 'Pass your exams', 'options': ['Pass your exams', 'Carrot', 'Public transport', 'Takeaway food']} ,

{'numb': 439, 'question': 'Bajarish', 'answer': 'Perform', 'options': ['Sign', 'Engineer', 'Good morning', 'Perform']} ,

{'numb': 440, 'question': 'Pianinochi', 'answer': 'Pianist', 'options': ['Through', 'Duvet', 'Pianist', 'Foreign']} ,

{'numb': 441, 'question': 'Hozir', 'answer': 'Present', 'options': ['Vegetables', 'Achievement', 'Present', 'Prepare']} ,

{'numb': 442, 'question': 'Yangiliklarni oqing', 'answer': 'Read to the news', 'options': ['Read to the news', 'Easy', 'Much', 'Charge']} ,

{'numb': 443, 'question': 'Dahshatli tush', 'answer': 'Nightmare', 'options': ['Nightmare', 'Tomato', 'Traffic lights', 'Park']} ,

{'numb': 444, 'question': 'Tashqarida', 'answer': 'Out of', 'options': ['Bus driver', 'Lucky', 'Height', 'Out of']} ,

{'numb': 445, 'question': 'Ustida', 'answer': 'Over', 'options': ['Difficult', 'Chin', 'Over', 'Among']} ,

{'numb': 446, 'question': 'Parashyut', 'answer': 'Parachute', 'options': ['Air', 'Parachute', 'Check in', 'Later']} ,

{'numb': 447, 'question': 'Mamnun', 'answer': 'Pleased', 'options': ['Fashion', 'Guy', 'Small', 'Pleased']} ,

{'numb': 448, 'question': 'Muloyimlik bilan', 'answer': 'Politely', 'options': ['Delicious', 'Politely', 'Trainers', 'Realize']} ,

{'numb': 449, 'question': 'Tortib olmoq', 'answer': 'Pull out', 'options': ['That', 'Yet', 'Pull out', 'Chat']} ,

{'numb': 450, 'question': 'Tez', 'answer': 'Quickly', 'options': ['Form', 'Have dinner', 'Quickly', 'Instructions']} ,

{'numb': 451, 'question': 'Oquvchi', 'answer': 'Reader', 'options': ['Foreign language', 'Please', 'Wife', 'Reader']} ,

{'numb': 452, 'question': 'Qutqaruv guruhi', 'answer': 'Rescue team', 'options': ['Pretty', 'Rent', 'Rescue team', 'Fashion designer']} ,

{'numb': 453, 'question': 'Dumaloq va dumaloq', 'answer': 'Round and round', 'options': ['Round and round', 'Egg', 'Daughter', 'Underground']} ,

{'numb': 454, 'question': 'Yuguruvchi', 'answer': 'Runner', 'options': ['Runner', 'Men', 'Texture', 'Nephew']} ,

{'numb': 455, 'question': 'Parashyutdan sakrash', 'answer': 'Skydiving', 'options': ['Center', 'Skydiving', 'Towel', 'Ride']} ,

{'numb': 456, 'question': 'Aqlli', 'answer': 'Smartly', 'options': ['Picture', 'Song', 'Avoid', 'Smartly']} ,

{'numb': 457, 'question': 'Snoubordda uchish', 'answer': 'Snowboarding', 'options': ['Call', 'Big', 'Sleeping bag', 'Snowboarding']} ,

{'numb': 458, 'question': 'Begona', 'answer': 'Stranger', 'options': ['Fork', 'Stranger', 'Task', 'Secret']} ,

{'numb': 459, 'question': 'Somon', 'answer': 'Straw', 'options': ['Straw', 'Stall', 'Science', 'Reliable']} ,

{'numb': 460, 'question': 'Takidladi', 'answer': 'Stressed', 'options': ['Shirt', 'Notice', 'Wife', 'Stressed']} ,

{'numb': 461, 'question': 'Olish', 'answer': 'Takeof', 'options': ['Takeof', 'Purchase', 'Angrily', 'Cardigan']} ,

{'numb': 462, 'question': 'Orqali', 'answer': 'Through', 'options': ['Cube', 'Niece', 'Publisher', 'Through']} ,

{'numb': 463, 'question': 'Tortmoq', 'answer': 'Towards', 'options': ['Bother', 'Different', 'Towards', 'Discount']} ,

{'numb': 464, 'question': 'Svetofor', 'answer': 'Traffic lights', 'options': ['Train', 'Trend', 'Traffic lights', 'Bedroom']} ,

{'numb': 465, 'question': 'Sayohatchi', 'answer': 'Traveller', 'options': ['Small', 'Health', 'Traveller', 'Think']} ,

{'numb': 466, 'question': 'Yozuvteruvchi', 'answer': 'Typist', 'options': ['Work', 'Pie', 'Typist', 'Yet']} ,

{'numb': 467, 'question': 'Video kamera', 'answer': 'Videocamera', 'options': ['Germs', 'Videocamera', 'Big', 'See']} ,

{'numb': 468, 'question': 'Piyoda', 'answer': 'Walker', 'options': ['Become', 'Camping', 'Walker', 'Get ill']} ,

{'numb': 469, 'question': 'Jirkanch', 'answer': 'Nasty', 'options': ['Butcherãšâ¼s', 'Nasty', 'Philosophy', 'Passenger']} ,

{'numb': 470, 'question': 'Ochiq havoda', 'answer': 'Outdoors', 'options': ['Outdoors', 'Cheese', 'Supermarket', 'Rent']} ,

{'numb': 471, 'question': 'Davr', 'answer': 'Period', 'options': ['Goal', 'Jewellery', 'Period', 'Chef']} ,

{'numb': 472, 'question': 'Fotosurat', 'answer': 'Photograph', 'options': ['Their', 'Photograph', 'Diabetes', 'Suggest']} ,

{'numb': 473, 'question': 'Zavq', 'answer': 'Pleasure', 'options': ['Pleasure', 'Quiet', 'Impolite', 'Free time']} ,

{'numb': 474, 'question': 'Yoqimli', 'answer': 'Pleasant', 'options': ['Pleasant', 'All', 'Festival', 'Yet']} ,

{'numb': 475, 'question': 'Post', 'answer': 'Post', 'options': ['Deal with', 'Address', 'Dead', 'Post']} ,

{'numb': 476, 'question': 'Vada', 'answer': 'Promise', 'options': ['Work long hours', 'Girl', 'Promise', 'Bottle']} ,

{'numb': 477, 'question': 'Psixolog', 'answer': 'Psychologist', 'options': ['Bicycle', 'Simple', 'Psychologist', 'Avoid']} ,

{'numb': 478, 'question': 'Rekord', 'answer': 'Record', 'options': ['Record', 'Cook', 'Uncle', 'Replace']} ,

{'numb': 479, 'question': 'Munosabat', 'answer': 'Relationship', 'options': ['Seventh', 'Relationship', 'Carefully', 'Recognize']} ,

{'numb': 480, 'question': 'Qarindosh', 'answer': 'Relative', 'options': ['Relative', 'Dinner', 'Rat', 'Free']} ,

{'numb': 481, 'question': 'Sharhlovchi', 'answer': 'Reviewer', 'options': ['Decision', 'Sleep', 'Reviewer', 'Community']} ,

{'numb': 482, 'question': 'Yugurish', 'answer': 'Running', 'options': ['Sock', 'Place of birth', 'Angrily', 'Running']} ,

{'numb': 483, 'question': 'Xarid qilish', 'answer': 'Shopping', 'options': ['Shopping', 'Test', 'Shower', 'Assignment']} ,

{'numb': 484, 'question': 'Qor yogishi', 'answer': 'Snowfall', 'options': ['Snowfall', 'High speed', 'Cousin', 'Photograph']} ,

{'numb': 485, 'question': 'Vaqt otkazmoq', 'answer': 'Spend time', 'options': ['My', 'Spend time', 'Publisher', 'Case']} ,

{'numb': 486, 'question': 'Ichida qoling', 'answer': 'Stay in', 'options': ['Bolivia', 'Yoghurt', 'Research', 'Stay in']} ,

{'numb': 487, 'question': 'Suzish', 'answer': 'Swimming', 'options': ['Story', 'Taxi driver', 'Angrily', 'Swimming']} ,

{'numb': 488, 'question': 'Matn', 'answer': 'Text', 'options': ['Text', 'Online', 'Benefit', 'Probably']} ,

{'numb': 489, 'question': 'Vaqt', 'answer': 'Time', 'options': ['Time', 'Penguin', 'Honey', 'Fluent']} ,

{'numb': 490, 'question': 'Royxatini qilish', 'answer': 'To do list', 'options': ['To do list', 'Night', 'Perhaps', 'Impatient']} ,

{'numb': 491, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Trip', 'options': ['Watch sport', 'Vacant', 'Trip', 'Cousin']} ,

{'numb': 492, 'question': 'Noqulay', 'answer': 'Uncomfortable', 'options': ['Why', 'Lonely', 'Uncomfortable', 'Season']} ,

{'numb': 493, 'question': 'Yurish', 'answer': 'Walk', 'options': ['Bakery', 'Take care of', 'Walk', 'Rent']} ,

{'numb': 494, 'question': 'Ish', 'answer': 'Work', 'options': ['Work', 'Go to', 'Successful', 'Library']} ,

{'numb': 495, 'question': 'Arxitektor', 'answer': 'Architect', 'options': ['Russia', 'Stand', 'Architect', 'Code']} ,

{'numb': 496, 'question': 'Blok', 'answer': 'Block', 'options': ['Those', 'Block', 'If', 'Still']} ,

{'numb': 497, 'question': 'Kafe', 'answer': 'Cafe', 'options': ['Next', 'Sparklingwater', 'July', 'Cafe']} ,

{'numb': 498, 'question': 'Sham', 'answer': 'Candle', 'options': ['Nurse', 'Photocopy', 'Candle', 'Forwards']} ,

{'numb': 499, 'question': 'Sandiq', 'answer': 'Chest of drawers', 'options': ['Ask', 'Chest of drawers', 'Worry', 'Graduation']} ,

{'numb': 500, 'question': 'Mato', 'answer': 'Cloth', 'options': ['Girl', 'Indian', 'Wednesday', 'Cloth']} ,

{'numb': 501, 'question': 'Yigish', 'answer': 'Collect', 'options': ['Film', 'Impression', 'Collect', 'Designer']} ,

{'numb': 502, 'question': 'Gavjum', 'answer': 'Crowded', 'options': ['Crowded', 'Tweet', 'Move', 'Compass']} ,

{'numb': 503, 'question': 'Yoq qilish', 'answer': 'Destroy', 'options': ['Start', 'Destroy', 'Jumper', 'Reserve']} ,

{'numb': 504, 'question': 'Zerikarli', 'answer': 'Dull', 'options': ['Dull', 'Ironing', 'Valuable', 'Survive']} ,

{'numb': 505, 'question': 'Changyutgich va chotka', 'answer': 'Dustpan and brush', 'options': ['Understand', 'Adopt', 'Artist', 'Dustpan and brush']} ,

{'numb': 506, 'question': 'Yorgan', 'answer': 'Duvet', 'options': ['Angry', 'Duvet', 'Body clock', 'Housemate']} ,

{'numb': 507, 'question': 'Tez yolak', 'answer': 'Fast lane', 'options': ['Fast lane', 'Wonderful', 'Dear', 'Exactly']} ,

{'numb': 508, 'question': 'Yaxshi', 'answer': 'Fine', 'options': ['Already', 'Fluently', 'Takeof', 'Fine']} ,

{'numb': 509, 'question': 'Gulzor', 'answer': 'Flower stall', 'options': ['Flower stall', 'Change', 'Those', 'Bone']} ,

{'numb': 510, 'question': 'Uy almashish', 'answer': 'House swap', 'options': ['Oil', 'House swap', 'Promotion', 'A piece of']} ,

{'numb': 511, 'question': 'Uy rozgor buyumlari', 'answer': 'Household possessioins', 'options': ['Household possessioins', 'Furniture', 'Diet', 'Buy']} ,

{'numb': 512, 'question': 'Sanoat', 'answer': 'Industry', 'options': ['Industry', 'Aunt', 'Use', 'Our']} ,

{'numb': 513, 'question': 'Uyda otirish', 'answer': 'House sit', 'options': ['Embarrassing', 'Jungle', 'Platform', 'House sit']} ,

{'numb': 514, 'question': 'Yoqimli', 'answer': 'Lovely', 'options': ['Mini bar', 'Lovely', 'Twelfth', 'Consistof']} ,

{'numb': 515, 'question': 'Manzil', 'answer': 'Location', 'options': ['Many', 'Opportunity', 'Piece', 'Location']} ,

{'numb': 516, 'question': 'Bozor joyi', 'answer': 'Market place', 'options': ['Market place', 'Record', 'Business', 'Data']} ,

{'numb': 517, 'question': 'Labirint', 'answer': 'Maze', 'options': ['Walker', 'Flatmate', 'Maze', 'Statue']} ,

{'numb': 518, 'question': 'Mikrotolqinli pech', 'answer': 'Microwave oven', 'options': ['Athletics', 'Microwave oven', 'Feel', 'Least']} ,

{'numb': 519, 'question': 'Oyna', 'answer': 'Mirror', 'options': ['Fashionable', 'Down', 'Mirror', 'Hire']} ,

{'numb': 520, 'question': 'Tor', 'answer': 'Narrow', 'options': ['Fun', 'Wolf', 'Education', 'Narrow']} ,

{'numb': 521, 'question': 'Navigatsiya', 'answer': 'Navigation', 'options': ['North', 'Problem', 'Navigation', 'Brilliant']} ,

{'numb': 522, 'question': 'Biznesda', 'answer': 'On business', 'options': ['Greet', 'Answer', 'Oclock', 'On business']} ,

{'numb': 523, 'question': 'Bayramda', 'answer': 'On holiday', 'options': ['Prepare', 'On holiday', 'Get around', 'Rat']} ,

{'numb': 524, 'question': 'Jamoat transportida', 'answer': 'On publictransport', 'options': ['Above', 'On publictransport', 'Ability', 'Worrying']} ,

{'numb': 525, 'question': 'Internetda', 'answer': 'On theinternet', 'options': ['Lie', 'Speak', 'On theinternet', 'Relaxed']} ,

{'numb': 526, 'question': 'Yolda', 'answer': 'On theway', 'options': ['On theway', 'Relationship', 'Embarrassed', 'Paper']} ,

{'numb': 527, 'question': 'Vaqtida', 'answer': 'On time', 'options': ['On time', 'Always', 'Sculpture', 'Neighbor']} ,

{'numb': 528, 'question': 'Televizorda', 'answer': 'On tv', 'options': ['Takeof', 'Pizza', 'Learn', 'On tv']} ,

{'numb': 529, 'question': 'Tova', 'answer': 'Pan', 'options': ['Rough', 'Concert hall', 'Park', 'Pan']} ,

{'numb': 530, 'question': 'Toxtash joyi', 'answer': 'Parking space', 'options': ['Emirate', 'Balance', 'Private school', 'Parking space']} ,

{'numb': 531, 'question': 'Yulka rassomi', 'answer': 'Pavement artist', 'options': ['Thank', 'Boil', 'Ask', 'Pavement artist']} ,

{'numb': 532, 'question': 'Piyodalar hududi', 'answer': 'Pedestrian area', 'options': ['Achieve', 'Switzerland', 'Football', 'Pedestrian area']} ,

{'numb': 533, 'question': 'Oyin maydoni', 'answer': 'Play area', 'options': ['Strength', 'Est', 'Above', 'Play area']} ,

{'numb': 534, 'question': 'Loyiha', 'answer': 'Project', 'options': ['Read to the news', 'Fitness', 'Project', 'Social media']} ,

{'numb': 535, 'question': 'Nashriyotchi', 'answer': 'Publisher', 'options': ['Publisher', 'Olive', 'Size', 'Sun']} ,

{'numb': 536, 'question': 'Latta', 'answer': 'Rag', 'options': ['Rag', 'Olives', 'Reply', 'Noodles']} ,

{'numb': 537, 'question': 'Xavfsiz', 'answer': 'Safe', 'options': ['Rope', 'Safe', 'Studio flat', 'Coffee']} ,

{'numb': 538, 'question': 'Suniy yoldosh antennasi', 'answer': 'Satellite dish', 'options': ['Studio flat', 'Satellite dish', 'Hero', 'Fluent']} ,

{'numb': 539, 'question': 'Varaq', 'answer': 'Sheet', 'options': ['Log on', 'Sheet', 'Alcoholic drinks', 'Late']} ,

{'numb': 540, 'question': 'Dokon korgazmasi', 'answer': 'Shop display', 'options': ['Algeria', 'Shop display', 'Architecture', 'Kindof']} ,

{'numb': 541, 'question': 'Xaridor', 'answer': 'Shopper', 'options': ['Euro', 'Mitten', 'Shopper', 'Behind']} ,

{'numb': 542, 'question': 'Yechim', 'answer': 'Solution', 'options': ['Challenge', 'Environment', 'Find', 'Solution']} ,

{'numb': 543, 'question': 'Suvenir sotuvchisi', 'answer': 'Souvenir seller', 'options': ['Souvenir seller', 'Sculpture', 'Possession', 'Conversation']} ,

{'numb': 544, 'question': 'Toxtash joyi', 'answer': 'Stall', 'options': ['Behaviour', 'Theatre', 'Stall', 'Dream']} ,

{'numb': 545, 'question': 'Haykal', 'answer': 'Statue', 'options': ['Cafe', 'Statue', 'Shop online', 'Advertising']} ,

{'numb': 546, 'question': 'Galati', 'answer': 'Strange', 'options': ['Frog', 'Russian', 'Strange', 'Receive']} ,

{'numb': 547, 'question': 'Kocha tozalovchi', 'answer': 'Street cleaner', 'options': ['Street cleaner', 'On time', 'Fun', 'Like']} ,

{'numb': 548, 'question': 'Kocha ijrochisi', 'answer': 'Street performer', 'options': ['Street performer', 'Fog', 'Holiday', 'Sorry']} ,

{'numb': 549, 'question': 'Talabalar turar joyi', 'answer': 'Student accommodation', 'options': ['Student accommodation', 'Living room', 'Score', 'Relationship']} ,

{'numb': 550, 'question': 'Teging', 'answer': 'Tap', 'options': ['Tap', 'Tobacco', 'Habit', 'At the weekend']} ,

{'numb': 551, 'question': 'Sochiq', 'answer': 'Towel', 'options': ['Accommodation', 'Crucial', 'Towel', 'Diploma']} ,

{'numb': 552, 'question': 'Minora bloki', 'answer': 'Tower block', 'options': ['Ferry', 'Packet', 'Mini bar', 'Tower block']} ,

{'numb': 553, 'question': 'Yukmashinasi', 'answer': 'Truck', 'options': ['Join', 'Truck', 'Hostel', 'Awful']} ,

{'numb': 554, 'question': 'Shkaf', 'answer': 'Wardrobe', 'options': ['Wardrobe', 'Repellent', 'Download', 'Hospital']} ,

{'numb': 555, 'question': 'Yuvinish havzasi', 'answer': 'Wash basin', 'options': ['Depressed', 'Award', 'Wash basin', 'Practical skills']} ,

{'numb': 556, 'question': 'Aerobika', 'answer': 'Aerobics', 'options': ['Aerobics', 'Survey', 'Hold', 'Left']} ,

{'numb': 557, 'question': 'Band', 'answer': 'Busy', 'options': ['Busy', 'Narrow', 'Solution', 'Journalist']} ,

{'numb': 558, 'question': 'Lager', 'answer': 'Camping', 'options': ['Development', 'Nothing', 'Camping', 'Ingredient']} ,

{'numb': 559, 'question': 'Karta', 'answer': 'Cards', 'options': ['Black', 'Cards', 'Painting', 'Discuss']} ,

{'numb': 560, 'question': 'Suhbat', 'answer': 'Chat', 'options': ['Chat', 'Unusual', 'Meeting', 'Capsule']} ,

{'numb': 561, 'question': 'Shaxmat', 'answer': 'Chess', 'options': ['Hi', 'Group', 'Chess', 'Saucepan']} ,

{'numb': 562, 'question': 'Bulutli', 'answer': 'Cloudy', 'options': ['Supermarket', 'Mine', 'Cloudy', 'Understand']} ,

{'numb': 563, 'question': 'Kofe', 'answer': 'Coffee', 'options': ['Coffee', 'Obtains', 'Couple', 'Hold']} ,

{'numb': 564, 'question': 'Sovuq', 'answer': 'Cold', 'options': ['Oasis', 'Divorced', 'Cold', 'Roast']} ,

{'numb': 565, 'question': 'Kompyuter oyini', 'answer': 'Computer game', 'options': ['Computer game', 'Garage', 'In a good mood', 'Transport']} ,

{'numb': 566, 'question': 'Nam', 'answer': 'Damp', 'options': ['Narrow', 'In my free time', 'Computer game', 'Damp']} ,

{'numb': 567, 'question': 'Orzu', 'answer': 'Dream', 'options': ['Pleasant', 'Thursday', 'Dream', 'Practical skills']} ,

{'numb': 568, 'question': 'Erta', 'answer': 'Early', 'options': ['Fever', 'Children', 'Early', 'Visitor']} ,

{'numb': 569, 'question': 'Teng', 'answer': 'Equal', 'options': ['Equal', 'Unnecessary', 'Relationship', 'Volunteer']} ,

{'numb': 570, 'question': 'Mashq qilish', 'answer': 'Exercise', 'options': ['Cut', 'Exercise', 'Relaxing', 'Nationality']} ,

{'numb': 571, 'question': 'Oila', 'answer': 'Family', 'options': ['Hear', 'Child', 'Family', 'Frog']} ,

{'numb': 572, 'question': 'Film', 'answer': 'Film', 'options': ['Balcony', 'Film', 'Tea', 'Fun']} ,

{'numb': 573, 'question': 'Qiziqarli', 'answer': 'Fun', 'options': ['A cup of', 'Then', 'Suchã‚', 'Fun']} ,

{'numb': 574, 'question': 'Golf', 'answer': 'Golf', 'options': ['Parents', 'Obviously', 'Dessert', 'Golf']} ,

{'numb': 575, 'question': 'Sportzal', 'answer': 'Gym', 'options': ['Text', 'Wrist', 'Gym', 'Singer']} ,

{'numb': 576, 'question': 'Uy ishi', 'answer': 'Homework', 'options': ['Sugar', 'Tourist', 'Rent', 'Homework']} ,

{'numb': 577, 'question': 'Issiq', 'answer': 'Hot', 'options': ['Hot', 'Delay', 'Travel', 'Noodles']} ,

{'numb': 578, 'question': 'Uy ishlari', 'answer': 'Housework', 'options': ['Housework', 'Why', 'Leaf', 'Forest']} ,

{'numb': 579, 'question': 'Nam', 'answer': 'Humid', 'options': ['Humid', 'Dangerous', 'Head', 'Length']} ,

{'numb': 580, 'question': 'Bino ichida', 'answer': 'Indoors', 'options': ['Indoors', 'Stomach', 'Benefit', 'Good']} ,

{'numb': 581, 'question': 'Karate', 'answer': 'Karate', 'options': ['Skydiving', 'Lovely', 'Karate', 'Terrible']} ,

{'numb': 582, 'question': 'Kechgacha yotish', 'answer': 'Lie in', 'options': ['Long', 'Typist', 'Her', 'Lie in']} ,

{'numb': 583, 'question': 'Yoruglik', 'answer': 'Light', 'options': ['Light', 'Medical', 'Wife', 'Low']} ,

{'numb': 584, 'question': 'Chaqmoq', 'answer': 'Lightning', 'options': ['Honest', 'Lightning', 'Step', 'There']} ,

{'numb': 585, 'question': 'Qarang', 'answer': 'Look', 'options': ['They', 'Still', 'Look', 'Warm']} ,

{'numb': 586, 'question': 'Royxat tuzing', 'answer': 'Make a list', 'options': ['Make a list', 'Lab', 'Recommend', 'Singer']} ,

{'numb': 587, 'question': 'Rejalar tuzing', 'answer': 'Make plans', 'options': ['Make plans', 'Sock', 'Handshake', 'Husband']} ,

{'numb': 588, 'question': 'Ovqat', 'answer': 'Meal', 'options': ['Meal', 'Home', 'Bored', 'Reliable']} ,

{'numb': 589, 'question': 'Ular', 'answer': 'They', 'options': ['They', 'Cafe', 'Possess', 'Century']} ,

{'numb': 590, 'question': 'Nima', 'answer': 'What', 'options': ['Strict', 'Large', 'Lemon', 'What']} ,

{'numb': 591, 'question': 'Kim', 'answer': 'Who', 'options': ['Who', 'Swimming', 'Ocean', 'Special']} ,

{'numb': 592, 'question': 'Qayerga qayerda', 'answer': 'Where', 'options': ['Souvenir seller', 'Arrive', 'Where', 'Do']} ,

{'numb': 593, 'question': 'Qanday', 'answer': 'How', 'options': ['Unhealthy', 'Lovely', 'Course', 'How']} ,

{'numb': 594, 'question': 'Nega', 'answer': 'Why', 'options': ['Women', 'Purchase', 'Designer', 'Why']} ,

{'numb': 595, 'question': 'Qachon', 'answer': 'When', 'options': ['Expert', 'Public', 'When', 'Relax']} ,

{'numb': 596, 'question': 'Mening', 'answer': 'My', 'options': ['Pet', 'My', 'Tropical', 'Kenya']} ,

{'numb': 597, 'question': 'Sening', 'answer': 'Your', 'options': ['Famous', 'Fire', 'Copybook', 'Your']} ,

{'numb': 598, 'question': 'Uning', 'answer': 'His', 'options': ['His', 'In my free time', 'Blanket', 'Team']} ,

{'numb': 599, 'question': 'Uning', 'answer': 'Her', 'options': ['Against', 'Menu', 'Her', 'Honest']} ,

{'numb': 600, 'question': 'Uning', 'answer': 'Its', 'options': ['Try', 'Its', 'Stressful', 'That']} ,

{'numb': 601, 'question': 'Bizning', 'answer': 'Our', 'options': ['Our', 'Fashion', 'Rat', 'False']} ,

{'numb': 602, 'question': 'Ularning', 'answer': 'Their', 'options': ['Their', 'Oil', 'Important', 'Book in advance']} ,

{'numb': 603, 'question': 'Mushuk', 'answer': 'Cat', 'options': ['Cat', 'Shop online', 'Funny', 'Thirsty']} ,

{'numb': 604, 'question': 'Kuchuk', 'answer': 'Dog', 'options': ['Dog', 'Volunteer', 'Electric piano', 'Lie in']} ,

{'numb': 605, 'question': 'Qush', 'answer': 'Bird', 'options': ['Italian', 'Hammer', 'Bird', 'Sister']} ,

{'numb': 606, 'question': 'Olmaxon', 'answer': 'Squirrel', 'options': ['Squirrel', 'Lent', 'Paint', 'Last name']} ,

{'numb': 607, 'question': 'Bori', 'answer': 'Wolf', 'options': ['Expensive', 'Individual', 'Wolf', 'Place']} ,

{'numb': 608, 'question': 'Goz', 'answer': 'Goose', 'options': ['Help', 'Breakfast', 'Modern art', 'Goose']} ,

{'numb': 609, 'question': 'Jirafa', 'answer': 'Giraffe', 'options': ['Traffic jam', 'Giraffe', 'Hair', 'Spacesuit']} ,

{'numb': 610, 'question': 'Quyon', 'answer': 'Rabbit', 'options': ['Rabbit', 'Wash basin', 'Holiday', 'Ball']} ,

{'numb': 611, 'question': 'Sigir', 'answer': 'Cow', 'options': ['Cow', 'Toilet', 'Gorilla', 'Swap']} ,

{'numb': 612, 'question': 'Kalamush', 'answer': 'Rat', 'options': ['Bump', 'Rat', 'Touch', 'Zoology']} ,

{'numb': 613, 'question': 'Tulki', 'answer': 'Fox', 'options': ['Lebanon', 'Tomato', 'Ride', 'Fox']} ,

{'numb': 614, 'question': 'Ot', 'answer': 'Horse', 'options': ['Around', 'Sandwich', 'Horse', 'Moment']} ,

{'numb': 615, 'question': 'Qurbaqa', 'answer': 'Frog', 'options': ['First', 'Frog', 'Soul', 'Football']} ,

{'numb': 616, 'question': 'Ayiq', 'answer': 'Bear', 'options': ['Ticket', 'Adult', 'Bear', 'Practice']} ,

{'numb': 617, 'question': 'Sichqon', 'answer': 'Mouse', 'options': ['Tram', 'Mouse', 'Work freelance', 'Taxi driver']} ,

{'numb': 618, 'question': 'Maymun', 'answer': 'Monkey', 'options': ['Monkey', 'On theinternet', 'Dead', 'In the week']} ,

{'numb': 619, 'question': 'Chochqa', 'answer': 'Pig', 'options': ['Factory', 'Pig', 'Prise', 'Read']} ,

{'numb': 620, 'question': 'Fil', 'answer': 'Elephant', 'options': ['Elephant', 'Alphabet', 'Can', 'Behavior']} ,

{'numb': 621, 'question': 'Ordak', 'answer': 'Duck', 'options': ['Father', 'Very', 'Duck', 'Leather']} ,

{'numb': 622, 'question': 'Non', 'answer': 'Bread', 'options': ['Often', 'Peace', 'Bread', 'Parking space']} ,

{'numb': 623, 'question': 'Saryog', 'answer': 'Butter', 'options': ['Train', 'Tie', 'Bent', 'Butter']} ,

{'numb': 624, 'question': 'Yog', 'answer': 'Oil', 'options': ['Emotion', 'Take up', 'Oil', 'Spell']} ,

{'numb': 625, 'question': 'Pishloq', 'answer': 'Cheese', 'options': ['Cheese', 'Match', 'Giraffe', 'Important']} ,

{'numb': 626, 'question': 'Kolbasa', 'answer': 'Sausage', 'options': ['Dish', 'Shout', 'Credit card', 'Sausage']} ,

{'numb': 627, 'question': 'Vetchina(chochqa goshti)', 'answer': 'Ham', 'options': ['Take care of', 'Put', 'Ham', 'Hug']} ,

{'numb': 628, 'question': 'Gosht', 'answer': 'Meat', 'options': ['List', 'Meat', 'Probably', 'Antique']} ,

{'numb': 629, 'question': 'Mol goshti', 'answer': 'Beef', 'options': ['Snow', 'Beef', 'Fix', 'Ruins']} ,

{'numb': 630, 'question': 'Qoy goshti', 'answer': 'Lamb', 'options': ['Colleague', 'Object', 'Lamb', 'Economy']} ,

{'numb': 631, 'question': 'Joja', 'answer': 'Chicken', 'options': ['Course', 'Chicken', 'Have dinner', 'Ferry']} ,

{'numb': 632, 'question': 'Kotlet', 'answer': 'Cutlet', 'options': ['Olive', 'Cutlet', 'Poor', 'Degree']} ,

{'numb': 633, 'question': 'Baliq', 'answer': 'Fish', 'options': ['Clurp', 'Strong', 'Fish', 'Pound']} ,

{'numb': 634, 'question': 'Tuxum', 'answer': 'Egg', 'options': ['Culture', 'Fashionable', 'Egg', 'Next']} ,

{'numb': 635, 'question': 'Salad', 'answer': 'Salad', 'options': ['Look after', 'Door', 'Bad manners', 'Salad']} ,

{'numb': 636, 'question': 'Qoziqorin', 'answer': 'Mushroom', 'options': ['Note', 'Compare', 'Trip', 'Mushroom']} ,

{'numb': 637, 'question': 'Don', 'answer': 'Corn', 'options': ['Corn', 'Bother', 'Modern art', 'Disease']} ,

{'numb': 638, 'question': 'Botqa', 'answer': 'Porridge', 'options': ['Porridge', 'Psychologist', 'Reader', 'Juice']} ,

{'numb': 639, 'question': 'Shorva', 'answer': 'Soup', 'options': ['Happen', 'Moment', 'Soup', 'Furniture']} ,

{'numb': 640, 'question': 'Sendvich', 'answer': 'Sandwich', 'options': ['Who', 'Cardigan', 'Sandwich', 'Autumn']} ,

{'numb': 641, 'question': 'Guruch', 'answer': 'Rice', 'options': ['Art', 'Rice', 'Flavour', 'Finish school']} ,

{'numb': 642, 'question': 'Lapsha', 'answer': 'Noodles', 'options': ['Noodles', 'Study', 'Bottle', 'Niece']} ,

{'numb': 643, 'question': 'Un', 'answer': 'Flour', 'options': ['Stomach', 'Success', 'Health', 'Flour']} ,

{'numb': 644, 'question': 'Dorivor', 'answer': 'Spice', 'options': ['Outside', 'Bitter', 'Traveller', 'Spice']} ,

{'numb': 645, 'question': 'Qalampir', 'answer': 'Pepper', 'options': ['Fall', 'Worth', 'Publisher', 'Pepper']} ,

{'numb': 646, 'question': 'Tuz', 'answer': 'Salt', 'options': ['Work', 'Vase', 'Community', 'Salt']} ,

{'numb': 647, 'question': 'Piyoz', 'answer': 'Onion', 'options': ['There', 'Onion', 'Bobsleigh', 'Organization']} ,

{'numb': 648, 'question': 'Sarimsoq', 'answer': 'Garlic', 'options': ['Excellent', 'Garlic', 'Customs', 'Card games']} ,

{'numb': 649, 'question': 'Sous', 'answer': 'Sauce', 'options': ['Pakistani', 'Sauce', 'On theway', 'Document']} ,

{'numb': 650, 'question': 'Sabzavotlar', 'answer': 'Vegetables', 'options': ['White', 'Cake', 'Vegetables', 'Chef']} ,

{'numb': 651, 'question': 'Kartoshka', 'answer': 'Potatoes', 'options': ['Potatoes', 'Mirror', 'Penguin', 'Public']} ,

{'numb': 652, 'question': 'Sabzi', 'answer': 'Carrot', 'options': ['Politely', 'Carrot', 'Regular', 'Turkey']} ,

{'numb': 653, 'question': 'Lavlagi', 'answer': 'Beet', 'options': ['Cook', 'Post office', 'Beet', 'Fog']} ,

{'numb': 654, 'question': 'Pamidor', 'answer': 'Tomato', 'options': ['Birthday', 'Suitable', 'Tomato', 'Soft']} ,

{'numb': 655, 'question': 'Bodring', 'answer': 'Cucumber', 'options': ['Nothing', 'Cucumber', 'Relaxing', 'Soul']} ,

{'numb': 656, 'question': 'Karam', 'answer': 'Cabbage', 'options': ['Father', 'Nasty', 'Jam', 'Cabbage']} ,

{'numb': 657, 'question': 'Baqlajon', 'answer': 'Eggplant', 'options': ['Eggplant', 'Together', 'Friend', 'South korea']} ,

{'numb': 658, 'question': 'Yongoq', 'answer': 'Nut', 'options': ['Nut', 'Bitter', 'Since', 'Place']} ,

{'numb': 659, 'question': 'Meva', 'answer': 'Fruit', 'options': ['Umbrella', 'Lightning', 'Fruit', 'Complete']} ,

{'numb': 660, 'question': 'Olma', 'answer': 'Apple', 'options': ['Stepfather', 'Clothes', 'Apple', 'Lebanon']} ,

{'numb': 661, 'question': 'Nok', 'answer': 'Pear', 'options': ['Woman', 'Hardship', 'Pear', 'Alone']} ,

{'numb': 662, 'question': 'Banan', 'answer': 'Banana', 'options': ['Bath', 'Banana', 'Clever', 'Statement']} ,

{'numb': 663, 'question': 'Mayda mevalar', 'answer': 'Berry', 'options': ['Beach', 'Impression', 'Wood', 'Berry']} ,

{'numb': 664, 'question': 'Qulupnay', 'answer': 'Strawberry', 'options': ['Get merried', 'Strawberry', 'Get up', 'Text']} ,

{'numb': 665, 'question': 'Malina', 'answer': 'Raspberry', 'options': ['Our', 'Raspberry', 'Subtropical', 'Circle']} ,

{'numb': 666, 'question': 'Olcha', 'answer': 'Cherry', 'options': ['Currency', 'Couple', 'Cherry', 'Maiden name']} ,

{'numb': 667, 'question': 'Olxori', 'answer': 'Plum', 'options': ['Chest', 'Boss', 'Plum', 'Consistof']} ,

{'numb': 668, 'question': 'Uzum', 'answer': 'Grape', 'options': ['Consequence', 'Grape', 'Nod', 'Announcement']} ,

{'numb': 669, 'question': 'Orik', 'answer': 'Apricot', 'options': ['Apricot', 'Calendar', 'Evening', 'Close']} ,

{'numb': 670, 'question': 'Shaftoli', 'answer': 'Peach', 'options': ['Peach', 'Happen', 'Keep', 'Embarrassed']} ,

{'numb': 671, 'question': 'Qovun', 'answer': 'Melon', 'options': ['Melon', 'Brilliant', 'Wash basin', 'Son']} ,

{'numb': 672, 'question': 'Tarvuz', 'answer': 'Watermelon', 'options': ['Calm', 'Watermelon', 'Ban', 'Launderette']} ,

{'numb': 673, 'question': 'Oshqovoq', 'answer': 'Pumpkin', 'options': ['Pumpkin', 'Flat', 'Ruler', 'Match']} ,

{'numb': 674, 'question': 'Apelsin', 'answer': 'Orange', 'options': ['Wash basin', 'Nephew', 'Orange', 'Dirty']} ,

{'numb': 675, 'question': 'Mandarin', 'answer': 'Mandarin', 'options': ['Railway', 'Friendly', 'Mandarin', 'Place of birth']} ,

{'numb': 676, 'question': 'Limon', 'answer': 'Lemon', 'options': ['Lemon', 'Delivery', 'Wine', 'Swimming']} ,

{'numb': 677, 'question': 'Ananas', 'answer': 'Pineapple', 'options': ['Fear', 'Pineapple', 'Business management', 'Sleeve']} ,

{'numb': 678, 'question': 'Shakar', 'answer': 'Sugar', 'options': ['Aunt', 'Sugar', 'Shame', 'Example']} ,

{'numb': 679, 'question': 'Asal', 'answer': 'Honey', 'options': ['Boil', 'Honey', 'Night', 'Dessert']} ,

{'numb': 680, 'question': 'Tort', 'answer': 'Cake', 'options': ['Each other', 'Mushroom', 'Public', 'Cake']} ,

{'numb': 681, 'question': 'Bulochka', 'answer': 'Bun', 'options': ['Myth', 'Lamb', 'Bun', 'Look']} ,

{'numb': 682, 'question': 'Pechenye', 'answer': 'Cookie', 'options': ['Boss', 'Wind', 'Carrot', 'Cookie']} ,

{'numb': 683, 'question': 'Pirog', 'answer': 'Pie', 'options': ['Pie', 'Food processor', 'Something', 'Tonight']} ,

{'numb': 684, 'question': 'Shirinlik', 'answer': 'Sweet', 'options': ['Think', 'Prompt', 'Sweet', 'Only']} ,

{'numb': 685, 'question': 'Muzqaymoq', 'answer': 'Ice cream', 'options': ['Elbow', 'Hungry', 'Ice cream', 'Designer']} ,

{'numb': 686, 'question': 'Shokolad', 'answer': 'Chocolate', 'options': ['Glue', 'Break', 'Chocolate', 'Today']} ,

{'numb': 687, 'question': 'Suv', 'answer': 'Water', 'options': ['The usa', 'Post', 'Only', 'Water']} ,

{'numb': 688, 'question': 'Gazli suv', 'answer': 'Soda', 'options': ['Soda', 'Cube', 'Socks', 'Art gallery']} ,

{'numb': 689, 'question': 'Sharbat', 'answer': 'Juice', 'options': ['Bank account', 'Burger', 'Tower block', 'Juice']} ,

{'numb': 690, 'question': 'Vino', 'answer': 'Wine', 'options': ['Feature', 'Public', 'Wine', 'Pay']} ,

{'numb': 691, 'question': 'Choy', 'answer': 'Tea', 'options': ['Forehead', 'Nice', 'Home', 'Tea']} ,

{'numb': 692, 'question': 'Kofe', 'answer': 'Coffee', 'options': ['Coffee', 'Through', 'Tower block', 'Golf']} ,

{'numb': 693, 'question': 'Sut', 'answer': 'Milk', 'options': ['Bag', 'Museum', 'Milk', 'Also']} ,

{'numb': 694, 'question': 'Krem', 'answer': 'Cream.', 'options': ['Cream.', 'Food processor', 'Receive', 'Research']} ,

{'numb': 695, 'question': 'Yogurt', 'answer': 'Yogurt', 'options': ['In front of', 'In a good mood', 'Because', 'Yogurt']} ,

{'numb': 696, 'question': 'Tvorog', 'answer': 'Curd', 'options': ['Get around', 'Curd', 'Wire', 'Fishing']} ,

{'numb': 697, 'question': 'Salom', 'answer': 'Hi', 'options': ['Play', 'Clothes', 'Baseball', 'Hi']} ,

{'numb': 698, 'question': 'Salom', 'answer': 'Hello', 'options': ['Mug', 'Pleasure', 'Lockout', 'Hello']} ,

{'numb': 699, 'question': 'Uzur', 'answer': 'Sorry', 'options': ['Sorry', 'Mark', 'Spice', 'Height']} ,

{'numb': 700, 'question': 'Iltimos', 'answer': 'Please', 'options': ['In advance', 'Boy', 'Denmark', 'Please']} ,

{'numb': 701, 'question': 'Erkak', 'answer': 'Man', 'options': ['July', 'Man', 'Borrowed', 'Weight litfing']} ,

{'numb': 702, 'question': 'Ayol', 'answer': 'Woman', 'options': ['Niece', 'Film', 'Bathroom', 'Woman']} ,

{'numb': 703, 'question': 'Bola', 'answer': 'Child', 'options': ['Snowfall', 'Letter', 'Child', 'Messy']} ,

{'numb': 704, 'question': 'Bola', 'answer': 'Boy', 'options': ['Boy', 'Dress', 'Fishing', 'Sunny']} ,

{'numb': 705, 'question': 'Qiz bola', 'answer': 'Girl', 'options': ['Furniture', 'Girl', 'Luggage', 'Sleeve']} ,

{'numb': 706, 'question': 'Kishi', 'answer': 'Guy', 'options': ['Dolphin', 'Title', 'Team', 'Guy']} ,

{'numb': 707, 'question': 'Dost', 'answer': 'Friend', 'options': ['Text', 'Discount', 'House', 'Friend']} ,

{'numb': 708, 'question': 'Tanish', 'answer': 'Acquaintance', 'options': ['Lemonade', 'Hall', 'Acquaintance', 'Help']} ,

{'numb': 709, 'question': 'Qoshni', 'answer': 'Neighbor', 'options': ['Neighbor', 'Toy', 'Bear', 'Day']} ,

{'numb': 710, 'question': 'Taxmin', 'answer': 'Guest', 'options': ['Tell jokes', 'Succeed in', 'Wine', 'Guest']} ,

{'numb': 711, 'question': 'Boshliq', 'answer': 'Chief', 'options': ['Chief', 'Accident', 'Japan', 'Station']} ,

{'numb': 712, 'question': 'Xojayin', 'answer': 'Boss', 'options': ['Fluently', 'Niece', 'Boss', 'Of course']} ,

{'numb': 713, 'question': 'Raqobatchi', 'answer': 'Competitor', 'options': ['Competitor', 'Greener', 'Spice', 'Exit']} ,

{'numb': 714, 'question': 'Mijoz', 'answer': 'Client', 'options': ['Should', 'Reason', 'What', 'Client']} ,

{'numb': 715, 'question': 'Hamkasb', 'answer': 'Colleague', 'options': ['Watch a film', 'Colleague', 'Flatmate', 'Dishonest']} ,

{'numb': 716, 'question': 'Oila', 'answer': 'Family', 'options': ['Second', 'Degree', 'Family', 'Its']} ,

{'numb': 717, 'question': 'Odamlar', 'answer': 'People', 'options': ['Moon', 'Fine', 'People', 'Apartment']} ,

{'numb': 718, 'question': 'Ota ona', 'answer': 'Parents', 'options': ['Trousers', 'Parents', 'Bottle', 'Junkfood']} ,

{'numb': 719, 'question': 'Ota', 'answer': 'Father', 'options': ['Buyer', 'Father', 'A piece of', 'Granddaughter']} ,

{'numb': 720, 'question': 'Ona', 'answer': 'Mother', 'options': ['Tobacco', 'A lot', 'Mother', 'Keyboard']} ,

{'numb': 721, 'question': 'Er', 'answer': 'Husband', 'options': ['Seldom', 'Public', 'Platform', 'Husband']} ,

{'numb': 722, 'question': 'Xotin', 'answer': 'Wife', 'options': ['Bake', 'Wife', 'Canteen', 'Grek']} ,

{'numb': 723, 'question': 'Ogil bola', 'answer': 'Son', 'options': ['Ready', 'Son', 'Usually', 'Group']} ,

{'numb': 724, 'question': 'Qiz', 'answer': 'Daughter', 'options': ['Bone', 'Daughter', 'Publisher', 'Journalist']} ,

{'numb': 725, 'question': 'Aka', 'answer': 'Brother', 'options': ['Pay', 'Advantage', 'Brother', 'Science']} ,

{'numb': 726, 'question': 'Opa', 'answer': 'Sister', 'options': ['Fail', 'Sister', 'Pilot', 'Gym']} ,

{'numb': 727, 'question': 'Bobo', 'answer': 'Grandfather', 'options': ['Exciting', 'Elbow', 'Grandfather', 'Ice cream']} ,

{'numb': 728, 'question': 'Buvi', 'answer': 'Grandmother', 'options': ['Father in law', 'Business', 'Grandmother', 'Sandwich']} ,

{'numb': 729, 'question': 'Qaynota', 'answer': 'Father in law', 'options': ['Father in law', 'Jealous', 'Forwards', 'Location']} ,

{'numb': 730, 'question': 'Amaki', 'answer': 'Uncle', 'options': ['Uncle', 'Do online banking', 'This evening', 'A cup of']} ,

{'numb': 731, 'question': 'Xola', 'answer': 'Aunt', 'options': ['Buy a house', 'Aunt', 'Packet', 'Make a list']} ,

{'numb': 732, 'question': 'Amakivachcha', 'answer': 'Cousin', 'options': ['Cousin', 'Laptop', 'May', 'Lips']} ,

{'numb': 733, 'question': 'Ogil bola jiyan', 'answer': 'Nephew', 'options': ['Go out with friends', 'Neighbor', 'Nephew', 'Luggage']} ,

{'numb': 734, 'question': 'Qiz bola jiyan', 'answer': 'Niece', 'options': ['Park', 'Reading glasses', 'Walk', 'Niece']} ,

{'numb': 735, 'question': 'Ish', 'answer': 'Job', 'options': ['Centre', 'Job', 'Retired', 'Press']} ,

{'numb': 736, 'question': 'Tadbirkor', 'answer': 'Businessman', 'options': ['Memory', 'Should', 'Look at', 'Businessman']} ,

{'numb': 737, 'question': 'Haydovchi', 'answer': 'Driver', 'options': ['Driver', 'Cinema', 'Check in', 'Fix']} ,

{'numb': 738, 'question': 'Ishchi', 'answer': 'Worker', 'options': ['Hero', 'Thumb', 'Together', 'Worker']} ,

{'numb': 739, 'question': 'Injener', 'answer': 'Engineer', 'options': ['Ballon', 'Engineer', 'Paper', 'Begin']} ,

{'numb': 740, 'question': 'Doktor', 'answer': 'Doctor', 'options': ['Minut', 'Doctor', 'Cold', 'Library']} ,

{'numb': 741, 'question': 'Advokat', 'answer': 'Lawyer', 'options': ['Glue', 'Lawyer', 'Trip', 'Canteen']} ,

{'numb': 742, 'question': 'Jurnalist', 'answer': 'Journalist', 'options': ['Apple', 'Leave', 'Garlic', 'Journalist']} ,

{'numb': 743, 'question': 'Hamshira', 'answer': 'Nurse', 'options': ['Busy', 'Diesel', 'Fresh air', 'Nurse']} ,

{'numb': 744, 'question': 'Sotuvchi', 'answer': 'Shop assistant', 'options': ['Effort', 'Frying', 'Shop assistant', 'Flatmate']} ,

{'numb': 745, 'question': 'Buxgalter', 'answer': 'Accountant', 'options': ['Cruel', 'Best', 'Several', 'Accountant']} ,

{'numb': 746, 'question': 'Rassom', 'answer': 'Artist', 'options': ['Ceremony', 'Cookie', 'Burger', 'Artist']} ,

{'numb': 747, 'question': 'Musiqachi', 'answer': 'Musician', 'options': ['Mistake', 'Carpenter', 'Musician', 'Fermer']} ,

{'numb': 748, 'question': 'Aktyor', 'answer': 'Actor', 'options': ['Quite', 'Coffee', 'Friend', 'Actor']} ,

{'numb': 749, 'question': 'Student', 'answer': 'Student', 'options': ['Student', 'Funny', 'Nicely', 'Cycling']} ,

{'numb': 750, 'question': 'Oquvchi', 'answer': 'Pupil', 'options': ['Temperature', 'Pupil', 'Soup', 'In front of']} ,

{'numb': 751, 'question': 'Shahar', 'answer': 'City', 'options': ['Palace', 'Great britain', 'City', 'Icy']} ,

{'numb': 752, 'question': 'Uy', 'answer': 'House', 'options': ['House', 'Can', 'Bus pass', 'Comfort']} ,

{'numb': 753, 'question': 'Uy', 'answer': 'Home', 'options': ['Home', 'Collect', 'Knee', 'Languages']} ,

{'numb': 754, 'question': 'Bino', 'answer': 'Building', 'options': ['Get around', 'Different', 'Fork', 'Building']} ,

{'numb': 755, 'question': 'Joy', 'answer': 'Place', 'options': ['Place', 'Purple', 'Author', 'Business']} ,

{'numb': 756, 'question': 'Kirish', 'answer': 'Entrance', 'options': ['Free time', 'Remote', 'Entrance', 'Guest']} ,

{'numb': 757, 'question': 'Chiqish', 'answer': 'Exit', 'options': ['Learn to swim', 'Something', 'Fish', 'Exit']} ,

{'numb': 758, 'question': 'Markaz', 'answer': 'Center', 'options': ['Fruit', 'Carton', 'Center', 'Bakerãšâ¼s']} ,

{'numb': 759, 'question': 'Hovli', 'answer': 'Yard', 'options': ['Ride', 'Child', 'Yard', 'Correctly']} ,

{'numb': 760, 'question': 'Tom', 'answer': 'Roof', 'options': ['Husband', 'Roof', 'Founder', 'Or']} ,

{'numb': 761, 'question': 'Panjara', 'answer': 'Fence', 'options': ['Monday', 'Fence', 'Place of work', 'New zealand']} ,

{'numb': 762, 'question': 'Yer', 'answer': 'Land', 'options': ['Land', 'Goal', 'Nothing', 'Successful']} ,

{'numb': 763, 'question': 'Qishloq', 'answer': 'Village', 'options': ['Village', 'Grade', 'Possess', 'Floor']} ,

{'numb': 764, 'question': 'Maktab', 'answer': 'School', 'options': ['Excited', 'School', 'On publictransport', 'Write']} ,

{'numb': 765, 'question': 'Universitet', 'answer': 'University', 'options': ['Guy', 'Dangerous', 'University', 'Takeof']} ,

{'numb': 766, 'question': 'Teatr', 'answer': 'Theater', 'options': ['Bank account', 'Ruins', 'Jungle', 'Theater']} ,

{'numb': 767, 'question': 'Cherkov', 'answer': 'Church', 'options': ['Yogurt', 'China', 'Church', 'Mountain']} ,

{'numb': 768, 'question': 'Restoran', 'answer': 'Restaurant', 'options': ['Bark', 'Look', 'Take', 'Restaurant']} ,

{'numb': 769, 'question': 'Qahvaxona', 'answer': 'Cafe', 'options': ['Lawyer', 'Fine', 'Agree', 'Cafe']} ,

{'numb': 770, 'question': 'Mehmonxona', 'answer': 'Hotel', 'options': ['Arm', 'Worried', 'Hotel', 'Account']} ,

{'numb': 771, 'question': 'Bank', 'answer': 'Bank', 'options': ['A day off', 'Bank', 'Where', 'Stairs']} ,

{'numb': 772, 'question': 'Kino', 'answer': 'Cinema', 'options': ['Minut', 'Goal', 'Obviously', 'Cinema']} ,

{'numb': 773, 'question': 'Kasalxona', 'answer': 'Hospital', 'options': ['Hospital', 'All', 'Nobody', 'Fresh air']} ,

{'numb': 774, 'question': 'Pochta', 'answer': 'Post', 'options': ['Eleventh', 'Difficult', 'Post', 'Spring']} ,

{'numb': 775, 'question': 'Vokzal', 'answer': 'Station', 'options': ['Form', 'Station', 'Philosophy', 'Health']} ,

{'numb': 776, 'question': 'Ayeroport', 'answer': 'Airport', 'options': ['Airport', 'Moment', 'Tomato', 'Sofa']} ,

{'numb': 777, 'question': 'Dokon', 'answer': 'Shop', 'options': ['Ride', 'Shop', 'Snowfall', 'Headache']} ,

{'numb': 778, 'question': 'Dorixona', 'answer': 'Pharmacy', 'options': ['Something', 'Story', 'Pharmacy', 'Patient']} ,

{'numb': 779, 'question': 'Bozor', 'answer': 'Market', 'options': ['Opposite', 'Best', 'Blow', 'Market']} ,

{'numb': 780, 'question': 'Ofis', 'answer': 'Office', 'options': ['Lend', 'Surprising', 'Office', 'Stepmother/father']} ,

{'numb': 781, 'question': 'Kompaniya', 'answer': 'Company', 'options': ['Company', 'Oath', 'Season', 'Pianist']} ,

{'numb': 782, 'question': 'Fabrika', 'answer': 'Factory', 'options': ['Grey', 'Tablet', 'Pan', 'Factory']} ,

{'numb': 783, 'question': 'Xiyobon', 'answer': 'Square', 'options': ['Sour', 'Hospital', 'Timecapsule', 'Square']} ,

{'numb': 784, 'question': 'Kocha', 'answer': 'Street', 'options': ['Cash', 'Wear', 'Bump', 'Street']} ,

{'numb': 785, 'question': 'Toxtatmoq', 'answer': 'Stop', 'options': ['Stop', 'Contact', 'Italian', 'March']} ,

{'numb': 786, 'question': 'Tratuar', 'answer': 'Sidewalk', 'options': ['Stockings', 'Sidewalk', 'Chair', 'Prise']} ,

{'numb': 787, 'question': 'Bog', 'answer': 'Garden', 'options': ['Traffic', 'Competitor', 'Garden', 'Make things']} ,

{'numb': 788, 'question': 'Park', 'answer': 'Park', 'options': ['Tale', 'Park', 'Since', 'Film']} ,

{'numb': 789, 'question': 'Koprik', 'answer': 'Bridge', 'options': ['Page', 'Bridge', 'Public', 'Winter']} ,

{'numb': 790, 'question': 'Daryo', 'answer': 'River', 'options': ['Use', 'River', 'Respond', 'Men']} ,

{'numb': 791, 'question': 'Ormon', 'answer': 'Forest', 'options': ['Book in advance', 'Forest', 'Jewellery', 'There']} ,

{'numb': 792, 'question': 'Dala', 'answer': 'Field', 'options': ['Field', 'Refreshments', 'Healthy', 'Thick']} ,

{'numb': 793, 'question': 'Tog', 'answer': 'Mountain', 'options': ['Mountain', 'Die', 'Great britain', 'Record']} ,

{'numb': 794, 'question': 'Kol', 'answer': 'Lake', 'options': ['Since', 'Lake', 'Elbow', 'Trainers']} ,

{'numb': 795, 'question': 'Dengiz', 'answer': 'Sea', 'options': ['Match', 'Just', 'Ending', 'Sea']} ,

{'numb': 796, 'question': 'Okean', 'answer': 'Ocean', 'options': ['Ocean', 'Traffic', 'Surface', 'Thirtieth']} ,

{'numb': 797, 'question': 'Sohil', 'answer': 'Coast', 'options': ['Bare feet', 'Eyebrow', 'Send', 'Coast']} ,

{'numb': 798, 'question': 'Sohil', 'answer': 'Beach', 'options': ['Beach', 'Cherry', 'Go out with friends', 'Fill']} ,

{'numb': 799, 'question': 'Qum', 'answer': 'Sand', 'options': ['Fence', 'In the week', 'Sand', 'Signal']} ,

{'numb': 800, 'question': 'Chegara', 'answer': 'Border', 'options': ['Bank', 'Finish school', 'System', 'Border']} ,

{'numb': 801, 'question': 'Tamojnya', 'answer': 'Customs', 'options': ['Account', 'Good', 'Platform', 'Customs']} ,

{'numb': 802, 'question': 'Axlat', 'answer': 'Garbage', 'options': ['Underwear', 'Garbage', 'Forehead', 'Blossom']} ,

{'numb': 803, 'question': 'Qoldiq', 'answer': 'Waste', 'options': ['Stand', 'Mean', 'Forehead', 'Waste']} ,

{'numb': 804, 'question': 'Tosh', 'answer': 'Stone', 'options': ['Hot', 'Special', 'Stone', 'Rough']} ,

{'numb': 805, 'question': 'Rozi bolmoq', 'answer': 'Agree', 'options': ['Boss', 'Too', 'Weight litfing', 'Agree']} ,

{'numb': 806, 'question': 'Ruhsat bermoq', 'answer': 'Allow', 'options': ['House', 'Perfect', 'Allow', 'Line']} ,

{'numb': 807, 'question': 'Bolmoq', 'answer': 'Be', 'options': ['Grandfather', 'Be', 'All', 'First name']} ,

{'numb': 808, 'question': 'Aylanmoq', 'answer': 'Become', 'options': ['Building', 'Put on', 'Cold', 'Become']} ,

{'numb': 809, 'question': 'Boshlanmoq', 'answer': 'Begin', 'options': ['Teach', 'Begin', 'Meal', 'Manager']} ,

{'numb': 810, 'question': 'Sindirmoq', 'answer': 'Break', 'options': ['Arm', 'Theater', 'Break', 'Ironing']} ,

{'numb': 811, 'question': 'Keltirmoq', 'answer': 'Bring', 'options': ['Marathon', 'Walk', 'Train', 'Bring']} ,

{'numb': 812, 'question': 'Sotib olmoq', 'answer': 'Buy', 'options': ['Sleeper', 'Lockout', 'From', 'Buy']} ,

{'numb': 813, 'question': 'Chaqirish', 'answer': 'Call', 'options': ['Too', 'Police officer', 'Borrow', 'Call']} ,

{'numb': 814, 'question': 'Qoldan kelmoq', 'answer': 'Can', 'options': ['Can', 'In a good mood', 'Company', 'Study']} ,

{'numb': 815, 'question': 'Ozgartirmoq', 'answer': 'Change', 'options': ['Tomorrow', 'The uk', 'Outside', 'Change']} ,

{'numb': 816, 'question': 'Yopmoq', 'answer': 'Close', 'options': ['Close', 'Advantages', 'Girl', 'Chop']} ,

{'numb': 817, 'question': 'Kelmoq', 'answer': 'Come', 'options': ['Dull', 'Come', 'Body', 'Tea']} ,

{'numb': 818, 'question': 'Pishirmoq', 'answer': 'Cook', 'options': ['Cook', 'A bottle of', 'Concert hall', 'Blow']} ,

{'numb': 819, 'question': 'Kesmoq', 'answer': 'Cut', 'options': ['Cut', 'Soda', 'Towel', 'Surprising']} ,

{'numb': 820, 'question': 'Qilmoq', 'answer': 'Do', 'options': ['Sheet', 'Do', 'Curd', 'Thought']} ,

{'numb': 821, 'question': 'Tushmoq', 'answer': 'Fall', 'options': ['Like', 'Junkfood', 'Shiny', 'Fall']} ,

{'numb': 822, 'question': 'Topmoq', 'answer': 'Find', 'options': ['Supermarket', 'Find', 'Bowler hat', 'Have']} ,

{'numb': 823, 'question': 'Uchmoq', 'answer': 'Fly', 'options': ['Ago', 'Nephew', 'Fly', 'Cherry']} ,

{'numb': 824, 'question': 'Ergashmoq', 'answer': 'Follow', 'options': ['Also', 'Follow', 'Take up', 'Snack']} ,

{'numb': 825, 'question': 'Olmoq', 'answer': 'Get', 'options': ['Get', 'Maiden name', 'Pan', 'Competitor']} ,

{'numb': 826, 'question': 'Ega bolmoq', 'answer': 'Have', 'options': ['Information', 'Handkerchief', 'Expensive', 'Have']} ,

{'numb': 827, 'question': 'Ushlamoq', 'answer': 'Hold', 'options': ['Weight litfing', 'Hold', 'Twin', 'Parachute']} ,

{'numb': 828, 'question': 'Bilmoq', 'answer': 'Know', 'options': ['Weapon', 'Amazed', 'Know', 'Freeze']} ,

{'numb': 829, 'question': 'Qoldirib ketmoq', 'answer': 'Leave', 'options': ['Hard worker', 'Each', 'Leave', 'Sauce']} ,

{'numb': 830, 'question': 'Qilmoq', 'answer': 'Make', 'options': ['Consumer', 'Make', 'Bright', 'Registration form']} ,

{'numb': 831, 'question': 'May', 'answer': 'May', 'options': ['Experiment', 'Credit card', 'May', 'Mild']} ,

{'numb': 832, 'question': 'Mano bildirmoq', 'answer': 'Mean', 'options': ['Depth', 'Giraffe', 'Mean', 'Designer']} ,

{'numb': 833, 'question': 'Kerak', 'answer': 'Need', 'options': ['Coffee', 'Present', 'Large', 'Need']} ,

{'numb': 834, 'question': 'Ochiq', 'answer': 'Open', 'options': ['Swimming', 'Open', 'Cards', 'Dirty']} ,

{'numb': 835, 'question': 'Oynamoq', 'answer': 'Play', 'options': ['Play', 'Registration form', 'Website', 'Each']} ,

{'numb': 836, 'question': 'Tolamoq', 'answer': 'Pay', 'options': ['Pay', 'Foot', 'Trip', 'Lebanon']} ,

{'numb': 837, 'question': 'Sotmoq', 'answer': 'Sell', 'options': ['Supermarket', 'Food processor', 'Sell', 'Progress']} ,

{'numb': 838, 'question': 'Jonatmoq', 'answer': 'Send', 'options': ['Already', 'Send', 'Remember', 'Outside']} ,

{'numb': 839, 'question': 'Otirmoq', 'answer': 'Sit', 'options': ['Retire', 'Passenger', 'Lonely', 'Sit']} ,

{'numb': 840, 'question': 'Gapirmoq', 'answer': 'Speak', 'options': ['Arabic', 'Speak', 'Against', 'Game']} ,

{'numb': 841, 'question': 'Turmoq', 'answer': 'Stand', 'options': ['What', 'Carpet', 'Theatre', 'Stand']} ,

{'numb': 842, 'question': 'Boshlash', 'answer': 'Start', 'options': ['In my free time', 'Radio', 'Already', 'Start']} ,

{'numb': 843, 'question': 'Gapirmoq', 'answer': 'Talk', 'options': ['Talk', 'Fine', 'Fire', 'Pollution']} ,

{'numb': 844, 'question': 'Aytib bermoq', 'answer': 'Tell', 'options': ['Tongue', 'Animal', 'Tell', 'Algeria']} ,

{'numb': 845, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Travel', 'options': ['Cent', 'Fun', 'Travel', 'Luck']} ,

{'numb': 846, 'question': 'Urinmoq', 'answer': 'Try', 'options': ['Flut', 'Project', 'Jump', 'Try']} ,

{'numb': 847, 'question': 'Tushunmoq', 'answer': 'Understand', 'options': ['Understand', 'Convenient', 'Junkfood', 'Celebrate']} ,

{'numb': 848, 'question': 'Foydalanmoq', 'answer': 'Use', 'options': ['Use', 'Flu', 'Article', 'Repetitivestraininjury']} ,

{'numb': 849, 'question': 'Kutmoq', 'answer': 'Wait', 'options': ['Wait', 'Stove', 'Balance', 'Talk']} ,

{'numb': 850, 'question': 'Tomosha qilmoq', 'answer': 'Watch', 'options': ['Every day', 'Maiden name', 'Fall', 'Watch']} ,

{'numb': 851, 'question': 'Yutmoq', 'answer': 'Win', 'options': ['Plum', 'Download', 'Japan', 'Win']} ,

{'numb': 852, 'question': 'Ishlamoq', 'answer': 'Work', 'options': ['Work', 'Be interested in', 'Spelling', 'Log on']} ,

{'numb': 853, 'question': 'Havotir olmoq', 'answer': 'Worry', 'options': ['Worry', 'Wallet', 'Mug', 'Scarf']} ,

{'numb': 854, 'question': 'Javob bermoq', 'answer': 'Answer', 'options': ['Consistof', 'Answer', 'Address', 'Developing world']} ,

{'numb': 855, 'question': 'Soramoq', 'answer': 'Ask', 'options': ['Leave', 'Hate', 'Outdoors', 'Ask']} ,

{'numb': 856, 'question': 'Ishonmoq', 'answer': 'Believe', 'options': ['Believe', 'Trouser', 'Japanese', 'Cream.']} ,

{'numb': 857, 'question': 'Qarz olmoq', 'answer': 'Borrow', 'options': ['Sandy', 'Eye', 'Borrow', 'Sidewalk']} ,

{'numb': 858, 'question': 'Tashib yurmoq', 'answer': 'Carry', 'options': ['Learn', 'British', 'Carry', 'Tomato']} ,

{'numb': 859, 'question': 'Kochirmoq', 'answer': 'Copy', 'options': ['Copy', 'Equip', 'Round and round', 'Thought']} ,

{'numb': 860, 'question': 'Qaror qilmoq', 'answer': 'Decide', 'options': ['Journey', 'Public transport', 'Decide', 'Bookshop']} ,

{'numb': 861, 'question': 'Muhokama', 'answer': 'Discuss', 'options': ['Discuss', 'Collect', 'Centre', 'Interested in']} ,

{'numb': 862, 'question': 'Yemoq', 'answer': 'Est', 'options': ['Bicycle', 'Wash basin', 'Est', 'March']} ,

{'numb': 863, 'question': 'Tushuntirish', 'answer': 'Explain', 'options': ['Loose', 'Explain', 'Garlic', 'Dead']} ,

{'numb': 864, 'question': 'His qilmoq', 'answer': 'Feel', 'options': ['Dry', 'Dark', 'Feel', 'Blossom']} ,

{'numb': 865, 'question': 'Toldirmoq', 'answer': 'Fill', 'options': ['A piece of', 'Music', 'Fill', 'Social media']} ,

{'numb': 866, 'question': 'Tugatish', 'answer': 'Finish', 'options': ['Jump', 'Guilty', 'Plain', 'Finish']} ,

{'numb': 867, 'question': 'Esdan chiqarmoq', 'answer': 'Forget', 'options': ['Work', 'Ninth', 'Forget', 'Lebanon']} ,

{'numb': 868, 'question': 'Bermoq', 'answer': 'Give', 'options': ['Make plans', 'Give', 'Husband', 'Above']} ,

{'numb': 869, 'question': 'Ketmoq', 'answer': 'Go', 'options': ['February', 'Go', 'Night', 'Sunny']} ,

{'numb': 870, 'question': 'Sodir bolmoq', 'answer': 'Happen', 'options': ['Winner', 'Clear', 'Worried', 'Happen']} ,

{'numb': 871, 'question': 'Eshitmoq', 'answer': 'Hear', 'options': ['Hear', 'Granddaughter', 'Dry', 'Crowded']} ,

{'numb': 872, 'question': 'Yordam', 'answer': 'Help', 'options': ['Flavour', 'Help', 'Orange juice', 'Running nose']} ,

{'numb': 873, 'question': 'Saqlamoq', 'answer': 'Keep', 'options': ['Keep', 'Vegetables', 'August', 'Tell jokes']} ,

{'numb': 874, 'question': 'Organmoq', 'answer': 'Learn', 'options': ['Cheek', 'Retirement', 'Learn', 'Live']} ,

{'numb': 875, 'question': 'Yoqtirmoq', 'answer': 'Like', 'options': ['Bank account', 'Toe', 'Like', 'Press']} ,

{'numb': 876, 'question': 'Tinglamoq', 'answer': 'Listen', 'options': ['Fuel', 'Tea', 'Listen', 'Napkin']} ,

{'numb': 877, 'question': 'Yashamoq', 'answer': 'Live', 'options': ['Live', 'Saturday', 'Collect', 'Bread']} ,

{'numb': 878, 'question': 'Qaramoq', 'answer': 'Look', 'options': ['Swap', 'Space', 'Look', 'Student']} ,

{'numb': 879, 'question': 'Uchratmoq', 'answer': 'Meet', 'options': ['Suitable', 'Meet', 'Children', 'Complete']} ,

{'numb': 880, 'question': 'Harakat', 'answer': 'Move', 'options': ['Move', 'Code', 'Learning skills', 'Strict']} ,

{'numb': 881, 'question': 'Kerak', 'answer': 'Must', 'options': ['Cinema', 'Vase', 'Must', 'Correctly']} ,

{'numb': 882, 'question': 'Vada bermoq', 'answer': 'Promise', 'options': ['Science', 'Hero', 'Vietnam', 'Promise']} ,

{'numb': 883, 'question': 'Qoymoq', 'answer': 'Put', 'options': ['Destroy', 'Put', 'Rich', 'Noun']} ,

{'numb': 884, 'question': 'Oqimoq', 'answer': 'Read', 'options': ['Naughty', 'Tiring', 'View', 'Read']} ,

{'numb': 885, 'question': 'Eslatmoq', 'answer': 'Remember', 'options': ['Last minute', 'Remember', 'Women', 'Ruins']} ,

{'numb': 886, 'question': 'Yugurmoq', 'answer': 'Run', 'options': ['And', 'Useby', 'Necessary', 'Run']} ,

{'numb': 887, 'question': 'Aytmoq', 'answer': 'Say', 'options': ['Say', 'Duty', 'Place of birth', 'Have lunch']} ,

{'numb': 888, 'question': 'Kormoq', 'answer': 'See', 'options': ['Well-paid', 'Mouse', 'Jeans', 'See']} ,

{'numb': 889, 'question': 'Kerak', 'answer': 'Should', 'options': ['Go out', 'Should', 'Bill', 'Last name']} ,

{'numb': 890, 'question': 'Korsatmoq', 'answer': 'Show', 'options': ['Thumb', 'Damp', 'Get dressed', 'Show']} ,

{'numb': 891, 'question': 'Uxlamoq', 'answer': 'Sleep', 'options': ['Untidy', 'Charge', 'Sleep', 'Athletics']} ,

{'numb': 892, 'question': 'Sarflash', 'answer': 'Spend', 'options': ['Spend', 'Trainee', 'Challenge', 'Early']} ,

{'numb': 893, 'question': 'Organmoq', 'answer': 'Study', 'options': ['Unkind', 'Gap', 'Mixed', 'Study']} ,

{'numb': 894, 'question': 'Soramoq', 'answer': 'Suggest', 'options': ['Knowledge', 'Suggest', 'Tennis', 'Neighbor']} ,

{'numb': 895, 'question': 'Olmoq', 'answer': 'Take', 'options': ['Pay', 'Take', 'Permit', 'Gues house']} ,

{'numb': 896, 'question': 'Oylamoq', 'answer': 'Think', 'options': ['Sell', 'Think', 'Lebanese', 'Informal']} ,

{'numb': 897, 'question': 'Burimoq', 'answer': 'Turn', 'options': ['Hostel', 'Strawberry', 'Turn', 'Above']} ,

{'numb': 898, 'question': 'Up uygonmoq', 'answer': 'Wake', 'options': ['Centre', 'Argentina', 'Link', 'Wake']} ,

{'numb': 899, 'question': 'Piyoda yurmoq', 'answer': 'Walk', 'options': ['Unusual', 'Cycling', 'Chair', 'Walk']} ,

{'numb': 900, 'question': 'Uygoq', 'answer': 'Awake', 'options': ['Awake', 'Tree', 'Stall', 'Kenya']} ,

{'numb': 901, 'question': 'Yomon', 'answer': 'Bad', 'options': ['Have a reservation', 'Bad', 'Congratulate', 'Receipt']} ,

{'numb': 902, 'question': 'Bukilgan', 'answer': 'Bent', 'options': ['Cap', 'Aunt', 'Greeting', 'Bent']} ,

{'numb': 903, 'question': 'Achchiq', 'answer': 'Bitter', 'options': ['Have a baby', 'Ready', 'Bitter', 'Luck']} ,

{'numb': 904, 'question': 'Kok', 'answer': 'Blue', 'options': ['Switzerland', 'Acquaintance', 'Blossom', 'Blue']} ,

{'numb': 905, 'question': 'Sovuq', 'answer': 'Cold', 'options': ['Tooth', 'Sculpture', 'Cold', 'Organize']} ,

{'numb': 906, 'question': 'Zolim', 'answer': 'Cruel', 'options': ['Bad', 'Bed', 'Disorganized', 'Cruel']} ,

{'numb': 907, 'question': 'Qorongu', 'answer': 'Dark', 'options': ['Dark', 'Trainers', 'Save up', 'Seal']} ,

{'numb': 908, 'question': 'Olgan', 'answer': 'Dead', 'options': ['Disappointment', 'Mayor', 'You are welcome', 'Dead']} ,

{'numb': 909, 'question': 'Aziz', 'answer': 'Dear', 'options': ['Divorced', 'Buyer', 'Germs', 'Dear']} ,

{'numb': 910, 'question': 'Farq', 'answer': 'Different', 'options': ['Angrily', 'Name', 'Oven', 'Different']} ,

{'numb': 911, 'question': 'Kir', 'answer': 'Dirty', 'options': ['Quarter to', 'From', 'Polish', 'Dirty']} ,

{'numb': 912, 'question': 'Notogri', 'answer': 'False', 'options': ['Lose', 'Turkish', 'Plum', 'False']} ,

{'numb': 913, 'question': 'Zaif', 'answer': 'Feeble', 'options': ['Be surprised', 'Feeble', 'Jungle', 'Serve']} ,

{'numb': 914, 'question': 'Ahmoq', 'answer': 'Foolish', 'options': ['Tube', 'Worse', 'Foolish', 'Apply']} ,

{'numb': 915, 'question': 'Kelajak', 'answer': 'Future', 'options': ['Ridiculous', 'Future', 'Should', 'Tiny']} ,

{'numb': 916, 'question': 'Yashil', 'answer': 'Green', 'options': ['Change', 'Green', 'Think', 'Discuss']} ,

{'numb': 917, 'question': 'Kasal', 'answer': 'Ill', 'options': ['Hand', 'Sociable', 'Cabbage', 'Ill']} ,

{'numb': 918, 'question': 'Oxirgi', 'answer': 'Last', 'options': ['Last', 'Tap', 'Skin', 'Enjoyable']} ,

{'numb': 919, 'question': 'Chap', 'answer': 'Left', 'options': ['Pan', 'How', 'Left', 'Coast']} ,

{'numb': 920, 'question': 'Erkin', 'answer': 'Loose', 'options': ['Back', 'Loose', 'Again', 'Refreshments']} ,

{'numb': 921, 'question': 'Baland', 'answer': 'Loud', 'options': ['Worth', 'Roast', 'Living room', 'Loud']} ,

{'numb': 922, 'question': 'Past', 'answer': 'Low', 'options': ['Low', 'Checkout', 'Bump', 'Sports']} ,

{'numb': 923, 'question': 'Aralash', 'answer': 'Mixed', 'options': ['Please', 'Blanket', 'Mixed', 'Nightmare']} ,

{'numb': 924, 'question': 'Tor', 'answer': 'Narrow', 'options': ['Dessert', 'Narrow', 'Writer', 'Seafront']} ,

{'numb': 925, 'question': 'Eski', 'answer': 'Old', 'options': ['Tonight', 'Task', 'Old', 'Italy']} ,

{'numb': 926, 'question': 'Qarama-qarshi', 'answer': 'Opposite', 'options': ['Opposite', 'Suggest', 'Case', 'Staff']} ,

{'numb': 927, 'question': 'Qopol', 'answer': 'Rough', 'options': ['Bump', 'Many', 'Rough', 'Concert hall']} ,

{'numb': 928, 'question': 'Gamgin', 'answer': 'Sad', 'options': ['Scissors', 'Sad', 'Diesel', 'Rat']} ,

{'numb': 929, 'question': 'Havfsiz', 'answer': 'Safe', 'options': ['Safe', 'Dream', 'During', 'Have breakfast']} ,

{'numb': 930, 'question': 'Sirli', 'answer': 'Secret', 'options': ['Pleasant', 'Space', 'Secret', 'Tiring']} ,

{'numb': 931, 'question': 'Kalta', 'answer': 'Short', 'options': ['Useful', 'Seldom', 'Short', 'Science']} ,

{'numb': 932, 'question': 'Oddiy', 'answer': 'Simple', 'options': ['Simple', 'Foreign language', 'Miracle', 'Good bye']} ,

{'numb': 933, 'question': 'Sekin', 'answer': 'Slow', 'options': ['In sixties', 'Class', 'Worry', 'Slow']} ,

{'numb': 934, 'question': 'Kichik', 'answer': 'Small', 'options': ['Sick', 'Ugly', 'Canteen', 'Small']} ,

{'numb': 935, 'question': 'Yumshoq', 'answer': 'Soft', 'options': ['Uncle', 'Couple', 'Trunk', 'Soft']} ,

{'numb': 936, 'question': 'Qattiq', 'answer': 'Solid', 'options': ['Solid', 'Location', 'Movie', 'Honest']} ,

{'numb': 937, 'question': 'Maxsus', 'answer': 'Special', 'options': ['Mayor', 'Special', 'Constantly', 'Straw']} ,

{'numb': 938, 'question': 'Notanish', 'answer': 'Strange', 'options': ['Tourist information centre', 'Flut', 'Strange', 'Underwear']} ,

{'numb': 939, 'question': 'Ozgin', 'answer': 'Thin', 'options': ['Thin', 'Creatively', 'Free', 'Girl']} ,

{'numb': 940, 'question': 'Oq', 'answer': 'White', 'options': ['High speed', 'White', 'Brilliant', 'Open']} ,

{'numb': 941, 'question': 'Xato', 'answer': 'Wrong', 'options': ['Runner', 'Thunder', 'Against', 'Wrong']} ,

{'numb': 942, 'question': 'Vaqt', 'answer': 'Time', 'options': ['Transfer', 'Taxi driver', 'Time', 'Second']} ,

{'numb': 943, 'question': 'Ikkinchi', 'answer': 'Second', 'options': ['Second', 'Noodles', 'Hairdresser', 'Constantly']} ,

{'numb': 944, 'question': 'Minut', 'answer': 'Minute', 'options': ['Sleeping bag', 'Come', 'Wine', 'Minute']} ,

{'numb': 945, 'question': 'Soat', 'answer': 'Hour', 'options': ['Tired', 'Australia', 'Return', 'Hour']} ,

{'numb': 946, 'question': 'Kun', 'answer': 'Day', 'options': ['Filling', 'Paint', 'Tie', 'Day']} ,

{'numb': 947, 'question': 'Oy', 'answer': 'Month', 'options': ['Time', 'Month', 'Housework', 'Discount']} ,

{'numb': 948, 'question': 'Yil', 'answer': 'Year', 'options': ['Borrowed', 'Sixth', 'Obviously', 'Year']} ,

{'numb': 949, 'question': 'Kecha', 'answer': 'Yesterday', 'options': ['Maybe', 'Individual', 'New', 'Yesterday']} ,

{'numb': 950, 'question': 'Kechadan oldingi kun', 'answer': 'The day before yesterday', 'options': ['Outside', 'Show', 'The day before yesterday', 'Onion']} ,

{'numb': 951, 'question': 'Bugun', 'answer': 'Today', 'options': ['Pan', 'Designer shoes', 'Today', 'Extrovert']} ,

{'numb': 952, 'question': 'Bugun tunda', 'answer': 'Tonight', 'options': ['Tonight', 'Pepper', 'Arrive', 'Switzerland']} ,

{'numb': 953, 'question': 'Ertaga', 'answer': 'Tomorrow', 'options': ['Tomorrow', 'Similar', 'Extrovert', 'Winner']} ,

{'numb': 954, 'question': 'Ertadan keyin', 'answer': 'The day after tomorrow', 'options': ['The day after tomorrow', 'Science', 'Now', 'Best selling']} ,

{'numb': 955, 'question': 'Tong', 'answer': 'Morning', 'options': ['Plain', 'Hero', 'Morning', 'Very']} ,

{'numb': 956, 'question': 'Tushlik', 'answer': 'Afternoon', 'options': ['Afternoon', 'Kitchen', 'Graduation', 'They']} ,

{'numb': 957, 'question': 'Kechqurun', 'answer': 'Evening', 'options': ['Hair', 'Well', 'Evening', 'Snack']} ,

{'numb': 958, 'question': 'Tun', 'answer': 'Night', 'options': ['Night', 'Orange', 'Aunt', 'Back']} ,

{'numb': 959, 'question': 'Dushanba', 'answer': 'Monday', 'options': ['Monday', 'On theinternet', 'Banana', 'Taste buds']} ,

{'numb': 960, 'question': 'Seshanba', 'answer': 'Tuesday', 'options': ['Tuesday', 'Delicious', 'Hug', 'Experiment']} ,

{'numb': 961, 'question': 'Chorshanba', 'answer': 'Wednesday', 'options': ['Tongue', 'Destroy', 'Wednesday', 'Hug']} ,

{'numb': 962, 'question': 'Payshanba', 'answer': 'Thursday', 'options': ['Millionaire', 'Waitress', 'Door', 'Thursday']} ,

{'numb': 963, 'question': 'Juma', 'answer': 'Friday', 'options': ['Camp', 'Friday', 'Half past', 'Guest']} ,

{'numb': 964, 'question': 'Shanba', 'answer': 'Saturday', 'options': ['Adopt', 'Saturday', 'Long', 'Ready']} ,

{'numb': 965, 'question': 'Yakshanba', 'answer': 'Sunday', 'options': ['Sunday', 'Balcony', 'Somebody', 'Vending machine']} ,

{'numb': 966, 'question': 'Yanvar', 'answer': 'January', 'options': ['Wait', 'January', 'Dry', 'Porridge']} ,

{'numb': 967, 'question': 'Fevral', 'answer': 'February', 'options': ['Grass', 'South africa', 'February', 'Machine']} ,

{'numb': 968, 'question': 'Mart', 'answer': 'March', 'options': ['March', 'Cycle lane', 'Office', 'Parachute']} ,

{'numb': 969, 'question': 'Aprel', 'answer': 'April', 'options': ['April', 'Suitcase', 'Named', 'Mobile phone']} ,

{'numb': 970, 'question': 'Iyun', 'answer': 'June', 'options': ['Sweetcorn', 'Sadness', 'June', 'Volunteer']} ,

{'numb': 971, 'question': 'Iyul', 'answer': 'July', 'options': ['Ready', 'Cabinet', 'July', 'Shorts']} ,

{'numb': 972, 'question': 'Avgust', 'answer': 'August', 'options': ['Diploma', 'These', 'August', 'See']} ,

{'numb': 973, 'question': 'Sentyabr', 'answer': 'September', 'options': ['Much', 'September', 'Employee', 'Sweetcorn']} ,

{'numb': 974, 'question': 'Oktyabr', 'answer': 'October', 'options': ['Rainy', 'Rough', 'Intercom', 'October']} ,

{'numb': 975, 'question': 'Noyabr', 'answer': 'November', 'options': ['Quiet', 'Reduce', 'Pensil', 'November']} ,

{'numb': 976, 'question': 'Dekabr', 'answer': 'December', 'options': ['Work', 'Acquaintance', 'December', 'Diesel']} ,

{'numb': 977, 'question': 'Fasl', 'answer': 'Season', 'options': ['Lazy', 'Season', 'Work', 'Look at']} ,

{'numb': 978, 'question': 'Bahor', 'answer': 'Spring', 'options': ['Spring', 'England', 'Tiny', 'Argentina']} ,

{'numb': 979, 'question': 'Yoz', 'answer': 'Summer', 'options': ['Link', 'Holiday', 'Tired', 'Summer']} ,

{'numb': 980, 'question': 'Kuz', 'answer': 'Autumn', 'options': ['Autumn', 'Map', 'Festival', 'In the week']} ,

{'numb': 981, 'question': 'Qish', 'answer': 'Winter', 'options': ['Skill', 'Cost', 'Where', 'Winter']} ,

{'numb': 982, 'question': 'Kanikul', 'answer': 'Holiday', 'options': ['Common', 'Fine', 'Under', 'Holiday']} ,

{'numb': 983, 'question': 'Tugilgan kun', 'answer': 'Birthday', 'options': ['Birthday', 'Sit', 'Last name', 'Stressful']} ,

{'numb': 984, 'question': 'Rahmat', 'answer': 'Thank you', 'options': ['Save up', 'Thank you', 'Have a baby', 'Enthusiastic']} ,

{'numb': 985, 'question': 'Arzimaydi', 'answer': 'You are welcome', 'options': ['Confused', 'You are welcome', 'Prise', 'Cousin']} ,

{'numb': 986, 'question': 'Afsus', 'answer': 'What a pity', 'options': ['What a pity', 'Maiden name', 'Jeans', 'Mouth']} ,

{'numb': 987, 'question': 'Hayr', 'answer': 'Good bye', 'options': ['Good bye', 'Actress', 'Health', 'Astronaut']} ,

{'numb': 988, 'question': 'Buyuk britaniya', 'answer': 'Great britain', 'options': ['Great britain', 'English', 'Storyteller', 'Task']} ,

{'numb': 989, 'question': 'Angliya', 'answer': 'England', 'options': ['England', 'Password', 'Interested in', 'Partner']} ,

{'numb': 990, 'question': 'Osimlik', 'answer': 'Plant', 'options': ['Plant', 'Depth', 'Sit', 'Log on']} ,

{'numb': 991, 'question': 'House', 'answer': 'Tree', 'options': ['Useful', 'Menu', 'Tree', 'Allow']} ,

{'numb': 992, 'question': 'Ot', 'answer': 'Grass', 'options': ['Health', 'Grass', 'Disease', 'Have dinner']} ,

{'numb': 993, 'question': 'Gul', 'answer': 'Flower', 'options': ['Dull', 'Plant', 'Flower', 'Bitter']} ,

{'numb': 994, 'question': 'Barg', 'answer': 'Leaf', 'options': ['Leaf', 'Nasty', 'Guide', 'Tree']} ,

{'numb': 995, 'question': 'Kvartira', 'answer': 'Flat', 'options': ['Hi', 'Flat', 'Tennis', 'Relaxed']} ,

{'numb': 996, 'question': 'Xona', 'answer': 'Room', 'options': ['Melon', 'Room', 'Seat', 'Outdoors']} ,

{'numb': 997, 'question': 'Mehmonxona', 'answer': 'Living room', 'options': ['Living room', 'Experience', 'Industry', 'Suggest']} ,

{'numb': 998, 'question': 'Yotoqxona', 'answer': 'Bedroom', 'options': ['Bedroom', 'For', 'Second', 'Experience']} ,

{'numb': 999, 'question': 'Dush', 'answer': 'Shower', 'options': ['Send', 'Pay', 'Shower', 'Seat']} ,

{'numb': 1000, 'question': 'Xojatxona', 'answer': 'Toilet', 'options': ['Annoying', 'Toilet', 'Still', 'Life']} ,

{'numb': 1001, 'question': 'Vannaxona', 'answer': 'Bathroom', 'options': ['Discount', 'Towards', 'Advice', 'Bathroom']} ,

{'numb': 1002, 'question': 'Oshxona', 'answer': 'Kitchen', 'options': ['Congratulate', 'Smile', 'Kitchen', 'Runner']} ,

{'numb': 1003, 'question': 'Zal', 'answer': 'Hall', 'options': ['Cupcake', 'Nut', 'Hall', 'Free time']} ,

{'numb': 1004, 'question': 'Balkon', 'answer': 'Balcony', 'options': ['Memory', 'Goose', 'Benefit', 'Balcony']} ,

{'numb': 1005, 'question': 'Pol', 'answer': 'Floor', 'options': ['Floor', 'School', 'Gallant', 'Wine']} ,

{'numb': 1006, 'question': 'Shift', 'answer': 'Ceiling', 'options': ['Economy', 'Spend', 'Hi', 'Ceiling']} ,

{'numb': 1007, 'question': 'Devor', 'answer': 'Wall', 'options': ['Keyboard', 'Feel well', 'Gallant', 'Wall']} ,

{'numb': 1008, 'question': 'Zina', 'answer': 'Stairs', 'options': ['Bank account', 'Untidy', 'Sit', 'Stairs']} ,

{'numb': 1009, 'question': 'Eshik', 'answer': 'Door', 'options': ['Compass', 'Ending', 'Door', 'Pharmacy']} ,

{'numb': 1010, 'question': 'Oyna', 'answer': 'Window', 'options': ['Patient', 'Belongto', 'Window', 'Customs']} ,

{'numb': 1011, 'question': 'Dokcha', 'answer': 'Windowsill', 'options': ['Gues house', 'Windowsill', 'Exit', 'Kettle']} ,

{'numb': 1012, 'question': 'Parda', 'answer': 'Curtain', 'options': ['Curtain', 'Patient', 'False', 'Inside']} ,

{'numb': 1013, 'question': 'Vikluchatel', 'answer': 'Switch', 'options': ['Spicy', 'Quickly', 'Vending machine', 'Switch']} ,

{'numb': 1014, 'question': 'Rozetka', 'answer': 'Socket', 'options': ['Tablet', 'Socket', 'Useby', 'Kilogramm']} ,

{'numb': 1015, 'question': 'Jomrak', 'answer': 'Faucet', 'options': ['Faucet', 'Thunder', 'Minute', 'Drink']} ,

{'numb': 1016, 'question': 'Truba', 'answer': 'Pipe', 'options': ['Expert', 'Tweet', 'Pipe', 'Put on']} ,

{'numb': 1017, 'question': 'Mori', 'answer': 'Chimney', 'options': ['Arrive', 'Chimney', 'Truck', 'Eye contact']} ,

{'numb': 1018, 'question': 'Mebel', 'answer': 'Furniture', 'options': ['Honey', 'Furniture', 'Stockings', 'Over']} ,

{'numb': 1019, 'question': 'Stol', 'answer': 'Table', 'options': ['Something', 'Table', 'Yoghurt', 'Founder']} ,

{'numb': 1020, 'question': 'Stul', 'answer': 'Chair', 'options': ['Quarter past', 'Chair', 'Fist', 'Country']} ,

{'numb': 1021, 'question': 'Kreslo', 'answer': 'Armchair', 'options': ['Death', 'Cheek', 'Soul', 'Armchair']} ,

{'numb': 1022, 'question': 'Divan', 'answer': 'Sofa', 'options': ['Sofa', 'Good bye', 'Portuguese', 'Get']} ,

{'numb': 1023, 'question': 'Karavot', 'answer': 'Bed', 'options': ['Bed', 'Neighbor', 'Fine', 'Fermer']} ,

{'numb': 1024, 'question': 'Garderob', 'answer': 'Wardrobe', 'options': ['Wardrobe', 'Mean', 'Often', 'Advert']} ,

{'numb': 1025, 'question': 'Kabinet', 'answer': 'Cabinet', 'options': ['Deep', 'Cabinet', 'Disappointed', 'Work for']} ,

{'numb': 1026, 'question': 'Raf', 'answer': 'Shelf', 'options': ['Too', 'House swap', 'Shelf', 'Password']} ,

{'numb': 1027, 'question': 'Deraza', 'answer': 'Mirror', 'options': ['Can', 'Possess', 'Mirror', 'In front of']} ,

{'numb': 1028, 'question': 'Gilam', 'answer': 'Carpet', 'options': ['Spend time', 'Leader', 'Unusual', 'Carpet']} ,

{'numb': 1029, 'question': 'Muzlatgich', 'answer': 'Fridge', 'options': ['Pavement artist', 'Fridge', 'Benefit', 'Already']} ,

{'numb': 1030, 'question': 'Mikrotolqinli', 'answer': 'Microwave', 'options': ['Microwave', 'Dry', 'Frightening', 'Social media']} ,

{'numb': 1031, 'question': 'Pechka', 'answer': 'Oven', 'options': ['Paper', 'Less', 'Oven', 'Art gallery']} ,

{'numb': 1032, 'question': 'Pechka', 'answer': 'Stove', 'options': ['Stove', 'April', 'Have breakfast', 'Gallant']} ,

{'numb': 1033, 'question': 'Idish', 'answer': 'Dish', 'options': ['Knee', 'Maiden name', 'Dish', 'Pear']} ,

{'numb': 1034, 'question': 'Piyola', 'answer': 'Cup', 'options': ['Cup', 'Dull', 'Exactly', 'Delivery']} ,

{'numb': 1035, 'question': 'Kozoynak', 'answer': 'Glass', 'options': ['Market place', 'Glass', 'Read', 'Parrot']} ,

{'numb': 1036, 'question': 'Krujka', 'answer': 'Mug', 'options': ['Mug', 'On publictransport', 'Nut', 'Worse']} ,

{'numb': 1037, 'question': 'Tarelka', 'answer': 'Plate', 'options': ['Plate', 'Through', 'Author', 'Thirsty']} ,

{'numb': 1038, 'question': 'Qoshiq', 'answer': 'Spoon', 'options': ['Spoon', 'Passport', 'Railway station', 'Reserve']} ,

{'numb': 1039, 'question': 'Vilka', 'answer': 'Fork', 'options': ['Fork', 'Uncle', 'Rat', 'In fact']} ,

{'numb': 1040, 'question': 'Pichoq', 'answer': 'Knife', 'options': ['Food', 'Look at', 'Knife', 'Nobody']} ,

{'numb': 1041, 'question': 'Likopcha', 'answer': 'Saucer', 'options': ['Chocolate', 'Face', 'Saucer', 'Every day']} ,

{'numb': 1042, 'question': 'Butilka', 'answer': 'Bottle', 'options': ['Frightened', 'Elbow', 'Bottle', 'Literature']} ,

{'numb': 1043, 'question': 'Salfetka', 'answer': 'Napkin', 'options': ['Dive', 'Napkin', 'Help', 'Night']} ,

{'numb': 1044, 'question': 'Skavarodka', 'answer': 'Frying', 'options': ['Backpack', 'These', 'Frying', 'Get ill']} ,

{'numb': 1045, 'question': 'Tova', 'answer': 'Pan', 'options': ['Pan', 'Olive', 'Diploma', 'Tap']} ,

{'numb': 1046, 'question': 'Choynak', 'answer': 'Kettle', 'options': ['Correct', 'Kettle', 'Free', 'Cooker']} ,

{'numb': 1047, 'question': 'Ovqat', 'answer': 'Meal', 'options': ['Member', 'Meal', 'Announcement', 'Repair']} ,

{'numb': 1048, 'question': 'Nonushta', 'answer': 'Breakfast', 'options': ['Write', 'Breakfast', 'Builder', 'Countryside']} ,

{'numb': 1049, 'question': 'Tushlik', 'answer': 'Lunch', 'options': ['Slowly', 'Cofee', 'Question', 'Lunch']} ,

{'numb': 1050, 'question': 'Kechki ovqat', 'answer': 'Dinner', 'options': ['Flavour', 'Message', 'Tourist information centre', 'Dinner']} ,

{'numb': 1051, 'question': 'Transport', 'answer': 'Transport', 'options': ['Second', 'Break', 'Transport', 'Sit']} ,

{'numb': 1052, 'question': 'Samolyot', 'answer': 'Plane', 'options': ['Mountain', 'Plane', 'Low', 'Friday']} ,

{'numb': 1053, 'question': 'Mashina', 'answer': 'Car', 'options': ['Car', 'Terrible', 'Have', 'Best selling']} ,

{'numb': 1054, 'question': 'Tramvay', 'answer': 'Tram', 'options': ['Tram', 'In the week', 'Change jobs', 'Rainforest']} ,

{'numb': 1055, 'question': 'Avtobus', 'answer': 'Bus', 'options': ['Strong', 'Bus', 'Parents', 'Retirement']} ,

{'numb': 1056, 'question': 'Poyezd', 'answer': 'Train', 'options': ['Class', 'Jump', 'Cherry', 'Train']} ,

{'numb': 1057, 'question': 'Korabl', 'answer': 'Ship', 'options': ['Polish', 'Special', 'Motorbike', 'Ship']} ,

{'numb': 1058, 'question': 'Velosiped', 'answer': 'Bicycle', 'options': ['Fork', 'Bicycle', 'Planner', 'Buy a house']} ,

{'numb': 1059, 'question': 'Sinf', 'answer': 'Form', 'options': ['Play area', 'Again', 'Form', 'Japanese']} ,

{'numb': 1060, 'question': 'Ism', 'answer': 'Name', 'options': ['Name', 'Learn a new language', 'Vacant', 'Go to the cinema']} ,

{'numb': 1061, 'question': 'Ism', 'answer': 'First name', 'options': ['Handkerchief', 'Colorful', 'Box', 'First name']} ,

{'numb': 1062, 'question': 'Familiya', 'answer': 'Surname', 'options': ['Eighth', 'Surname', 'Case', 'Worst']} ,

{'numb': 1063, 'question': 'Qizlik familiyasi', 'answer': 'Maiden name', 'options': ['Journey', 'Mobile phone', 'Maiden name', 'Popular']} ,

{'numb': 1064, 'question': 'Tugilgan sana', 'answer': 'Birth date', 'options': ['Mark', 'Birth date', 'In front of', 'Hungry']} ,

{'numb': 1065, 'question': 'Tugilgan shahar', 'answer': 'Place of birth', 'options': ['Place of birth', 'Thirsty', 'Castle', 'Reduce']} ,

{'numb': 1066, 'question': 'Manzil', 'answer': 'Address', 'options': ['Safe', 'Handkerchief', 'Address', 'Have a baby']} ,

{'numb': 1067, 'question': 'Turmush qurgan', 'answer': 'Married', 'options': ['Start', 'Behaviour', 'Runner', 'Married']} ,

{'numb': 1068, 'question': 'Ajrashgan', 'answer': 'Divorced', 'options': ['Maiden name', 'Swap', 'Divorced', 'Nicely']} ,

{'numb': 1069, 'question': 'Beva', 'answer': 'Widowed', 'options': ['Read', 'Effort', 'Widowed', 'Videocamera']} ,

{'numb': 1070, 'question': 'Narsa', 'answer': 'Thing', 'options': ['Green', 'South', 'Thing', 'Traffic']} ,

{'numb': 1071, 'question': 'Ruchka', 'answer': 'Pen', 'options': ['Mistake', 'Pen', 'Wardrobe', 'Have dinner']} ,

{'numb': 1072, 'question': 'Qalam', 'answer': 'Pensil', 'options': ['Texture', 'Calendar', 'Pensil', 'Signal']} ,

{'numb': 1073, 'question': 'Kitob', 'answer': 'Book', 'options': ['Agree', 'Carpet', 'Several', 'Book']} ,

{'numb': 1074, 'question': 'Daftar', 'answer': 'Copybook', 'options': ['Graduation', 'Sickness', 'Diet', 'Copybook']} ,

{'numb': 1075, 'question': 'Qayd yozuv', 'answer': 'Note', 'options': ['Tidy', 'Note', 'Nobody', 'Eye contact']} ,

{'numb': 1076, 'question': 'Xat', 'answer': 'Letter', 'options': ['Letter', 'Argument', 'Ship', 'Tube']} ,

{'numb': 1077, 'question': 'Konvert', 'answer': 'Envelope', 'options': ['Or', 'Volunteer', 'Alone', 'Envelope']} ,

{'numb': 1078, 'question': 'Qogoz', 'answer': 'Paper', 'options': ['Science', 'Education', 'Paper', 'Storyteller']} ,

{'numb': 1079, 'question': 'Gazeta', 'answer': 'Newspaper', 'options': ['Newspaper', 'Tomato', 'The usa', 'Nail']} ,

{'numb': 1080, 'question': 'Jurnal', 'answer': 'Magazine', 'options': ['Solve', 'Magazine', 'Want', 'Convenient']} ,

{'numb': 1081, 'question': 'Telefon', 'answer': 'Telephone', 'options': ['Oven', 'Health', 'Excuse', 'Telephone']} ,

{'numb': 1082, 'question': 'Soat', 'answer': 'Clock', 'options': ['Post', 'Start', 'Gym', 'Clock']} ,

{'numb': 1083, 'question': 'Taroq', 'answer': 'Comb', 'options': ['Comb', 'Connection', 'Mustache', 'Europe']} ,

{'numb': 1084, 'question': 'Televizor', 'answer': 'Tv', 'options': ['Heart', 'Tv', 'Forget', 'Gorilla']} ,

{'numb': 1085, 'question': 'Dazmol', 'answer': 'Iron', 'options': ['Bank account', 'Plain', 'Large', 'Iron']} ,

{'numb': 1086, 'question': 'Sovun', 'answer': 'Soap', 'options': ['Coffee', 'Soap', 'Oclock', 'Furniture']} ,

{'numb': 1087, 'question': 'Radio', 'answer': 'Radio', 'options': ['Radio', 'Practical skills', 'Kilogramm', 'Top']} ,

{'numb': 1088, 'question': 'Sumka', 'answer': 'Bag', 'options': ['Booking', 'Rescue team', 'Bag', 'Per']} ,

{'numb': 1089, 'question': 'Ryukzak', 'answer': 'Backpack', 'options': ['Trend', 'Sick', 'Backpack', 'You are welcome']} ,

{'numb': 1090, 'question': 'Xarita', 'answer': 'Map', 'options': ['Desicion', 'Architect', 'Piece', 'Map']} ,

{'numb': 1091, 'question': 'Karta', 'answer': 'Card', 'options': ['Ready', 'Designer', 'Hospital', 'Card']} ,

{'numb': 1092, 'question': 'Chemadon', 'answer': 'Suitcase', 'options': ['On theinternet', 'Lamb', 'Suitcase', 'Sugar']} ,

{'numb': 1093, 'question': 'Sovga', 'answer': 'Present', 'options': ['Sorry', 'Now', 'Present', 'Promotion']} ,

{'numb': 1094, 'question': 'Kamera', 'answer': 'Camera', 'options': ['Camera', 'Third', 'Pink', 'September']} ,

{'numb': 1095, 'question': 'Guldon', 'answer': 'Vase', 'options': ['Vase', 'Good quality', 'The uk', 'Although']} ,

{'numb': 1096, 'question': 'Romolcha', 'answer': 'Handkerchief', 'options': ['Safe', 'Handkerchief', 'Brother', 'Rope']} ,

{'numb': 1097, 'question': 'Koptok', 'answer': 'Ball', 'options': ['In advance', 'Tax', 'Our', 'Ball']} ,

{'numb': 1098, 'question': 'Shar', 'answer': 'Ballon', 'options': ['Egg', 'Ballon', 'Piano', 'Clean']} ,

{'numb': 1099, 'question': 'Oyinchoq', 'answer': 'Toy', 'options': ['Meeting', 'Scientific', 'Swimming', 'Toy']} ,

{'numb': 1100, 'question': 'Chipta', 'answer': 'Ticket', 'options': ['Keyboard', 'Ticket', 'Land', 'Address']} ,

{'numb': 1101, 'question': 'Bagaj', 'answer': 'Luggage', 'options': ['Gym', 'Luggage', 'Doughnut', 'Market']} ,

{'numb': 1102, 'question': 'Batareya', 'answer': 'Battery', 'options': ['Genetic', 'Battery', 'Log on', 'Depressed']} ,

{'numb': 1103, 'question': 'Chelak', 'answer': 'Bucket', 'options': ['North', 'Niece', 'Bucket', 'Thought']} ,

{'numb': 1104, 'question': 'Arqon', 'answer': 'Rope', 'options': ['Dining room', 'Rope', 'Dear', 'Busy']} ,

{'numb': 1105, 'question': 'Doska', 'answer': 'Board', 'options': ['Board', 'Blog', 'Similar', 'Clever']} ,

{'numb': 1106, 'question': 'Taqvim', 'answer': 'Calendar', 'options': ['Interest', 'Vase', 'Seventh', 'Calendar']} ,

{'numb': 1107, 'question': 'Noutbuk', 'answer': 'Laptop', 'options': ['Laptop', 'Bone', 'Cleaner', 'Revolution']} ,

{'numb': 1108, 'question': 'Chotka', 'answer': 'Brush', 'options': ['Conducter', 'Brush', 'Noodles', 'Simple']} ,

{'numb': 1109, 'question': 'Kalit', 'answer': 'Key', 'options': ['Head', 'Bright', 'Key', 'Rabbit']} ,

{'numb': 1110, 'question': 'Klaviatura', 'answer': 'Keyboard', 'options': ['Keyboard', 'Depend (on)', 'Dream', 'Scientist']} ,

{'numb': 1111, 'question': 'Gildirak', 'answer': 'Wheel', 'options': ['Finger', 'Mouse', 'First', 'Wheel']} ,

{'numb': 1112, 'question': 'Rul', 'answer': 'Steering wheel', 'options': ['Steering wheel', 'Brown', 'Message', 'People']} ,

{'numb': 1113, 'question': 'Chemadon', 'answer': 'Trunk', 'options': ['Dangerous', 'Physical', 'Trunk', 'Chess']} ,

{'numb': 1114, 'question': 'Benzin', 'answer': 'Gasoline', 'options': ['Clear', 'Gasoline', 'Look at', 'Microwave oven']} ,

{'numb': 1115, 'question': 'Hamyon', 'answer': 'Purse', 'options': ['Business management', 'Hate', 'Fun', 'Purse']} ,

{'numb': 1116, 'question': 'Hamyon', 'answer': 'Wallet', 'options': ['Athletics', 'Retirement', 'Wallet', 'Email']} ,

{'numb': 1117, 'question': 'Lampa', 'answer': 'Lamp', 'options': ['Tuesday', 'Lamp', 'Hair', 'Every']} ,

{'numb': 1118, 'question': 'Chizgich', 'answer': 'Ruler', 'options': ['Ruler', 'Dive', 'Development', 'Disease']} ,

{'numb': 1119, 'question': 'Belkurak', 'answer': 'Shovel', 'options': ['Corn', 'Tale', 'Shovel', 'Economy']} ,

{'numb': 1120, 'question': 'Mashina', 'answer': 'Machine', 'options': ['Finish', 'Wet', 'Socks', 'Machine']} ,

{'numb': 1121, 'question': 'Bolga', 'answer': 'Hammer', 'options': ['Hammer', 'Sleeve', 'Fluently', 'Balcony']} ,

{'numb': 1122, 'question': 'Qaychi', 'answer': 'Scissors', 'options': ['Scissors', 'Island', 'Acquaintance', 'Lift']} ,

{'numb': 1123, 'question': 'Posilka tugun', 'answer': 'Package', 'options': ['Solution', 'Package', 'Who', 'Chair']} ,

{'numb': 1124, 'question': 'Tayoq', 'answer': 'Stick', 'options': ['Flatmate', 'Some', 'Thing', 'Stick']} ,

{'numb': 1125, 'question': 'Yelim', 'answer': 'Glue', 'options': ['Move house or flat', 'Realize', 'Glue', 'Tack']} ,

{'numb': 1126, 'question': 'Sovga', 'answer': 'Gift', 'options': ['Gift', 'Queue', 'Quite', 'Exciting']} ,

{'numb': 1127, 'question': 'Sochiq', 'answer': 'Towel', 'options': ['Sit', 'Towel', 'Emotion', 'Flour']} ,

{'numb': 1128, 'question': 'Pochta', 'answer': 'Mail', 'options': ['Annoyed', 'Try', 'Breakfast', 'Mail']} ,

{'numb': 1129, 'question': 'Sim', 'answer': 'Wire', 'options': ['Basic', 'Cake', 'Thin', 'Wire']} ,

{'numb': 1130, 'question': 'Sahifa', 'answer': 'Page', 'options': ['Page', 'Give', 'Joy', 'Granddaughter']} ,

{'numb': 1131, 'question': 'Fonar', 'answer': 'Torch', 'options': ['Long', 'Length', 'Torch', 'East']} ,

{'numb': 1132, 'question': 'Quti', 'answer': 'Box', 'options': ['Modern art', 'Factory', 'Box', 'Ban']} ,

{'numb': 1133, 'question': 'Adyol', 'answer': 'Blanket', 'options': ['Blanket', 'Thick', 'Go to work', 'Sick']} ,

{'numb': 1134, 'question': 'Choyshab', 'answer': 'Sheet', 'options': ['Backwards', 'Sheet', 'Annual', 'May']} ,

{'numb': 1135, 'question': 'Yostiq', 'answer': 'Pillow', 'options': ['Hotel', 'Husband', 'Pillow', 'Record']} ,

{'numb': 1136, 'question': 'Kiyim', 'answer': 'Clothes', 'options': ['Clothes', 'Broken', 'Economics', 'Map reading']} ,

{'numb': 1137, 'question': 'Tufli', 'answer': 'Shoes', 'options': ['Long', 'Challenge', 'Shoes', 'Opal']} ,

{'numb': 1138, 'question': 'Etik', 'answer': 'Boot', 'options': ['Boot', 'Far', 'Cycle', 'Development']} ,

{'numb': 1139, 'question': 'Oyoq kiyimi', 'answer': 'Sneakers sport', 'options': ['Sneakers sport', 'Learn to swim', 'Ticket', 'Disease']} ,

{'numb': 1140, 'question': 'Palto', 'answer': 'Coat', 'options': ['Coat', 'Foundation', 'English', 'Fully qualified']} ,

{'numb': 1141, 'question': 'Koylak', 'answer': 'Dress', 'options': ['Dress', 'March', 'Never', 'Probably']} ,

{'numb': 1142, 'question': 'Kostyum', 'answer': 'Suit', 'options': ['Penguin', 'Forehead', 'Suit', 'Home']} ,

{'numb': 1143, 'question': 'Koylak', 'answer': 'Shirt', 'options': ['Lab', 'Shirt', 'Copy', 'Vacant']} ,

{'numb': 1144, 'question': 'Bluzka', 'answer': 'Blouse', 'options': ['Blouse', 'Under', 'Still', 'Annoyed']} ,

{'numb': 1145, 'question': 'Qolqop', 'answer': 'Glove', 'options': ['Hire', 'Glove', 'April', 'Designer']} ,

{'numb': 1146, 'question': 'Boshmaldoqli qolqop', 'answer': 'Mitten', 'options': ['Mitten', 'Photo', 'Match', 'Nephew']} ,

{'numb': 1147, 'question': 'Yubka', 'answer': 'Skirt', 'options': ['Speed', 'Skirt', 'Special', 'Acquaintance']} ,

{'numb': 1148, 'question': 'Shlyapa', 'answer': 'Hat', 'options': ['Hat', 'Tie', 'Chinese', 'Buy']} ,

{'numb': 1149, 'question': 'Kepka', 'answer': 'Cap', 'options': ['Vase', 'Cap', 'Ear', 'Country']} ,

{'numb': 1150, 'question': 'Pidjak', 'answer': 'Jacket', 'options': ['Cow', 'Jacket', 'Next to', 'Follow']} ,

{'numb': 1151, 'question': 'Kardigan', 'answer': 'Cardigan', 'options': ['Foundation', 'Take photos', 'Literature', 'Cardigan']} ,

{'numb': 1152, 'question': 'Sharf', 'answer': 'Scarf', 'options': ['Hot', 'Scarf', 'Means', 'Go fishing']} ,

{'numb': 1153, 'question': 'Paypoq', 'answer': 'Sock', 'options': ['Fall', 'Bike', 'Sock', 'Crazy']} ,

{'numb': 1154, 'question': 'Sviter', 'answer': 'Sweater', 'options': ['Its', 'Partner', 'Cheek', 'Sweater']} ,

{'numb': 1155, 'question': 'Futbolka', 'answer': 'T-shirt', 'options': ['Herb', 'Delicious', 'Chimney', 'T-shirt']} ,

{'numb': 1156, 'question': 'Galstuk', 'answer': 'Tie', 'options': ['Delivery', 'Shop online', 'Bitter', 'Tie']} ,

{'numb': 1157, 'question': 'Shim', 'answer': 'Trouser', 'options': ['Place of birth', 'Film', 'Friendly', 'Trouser']} ,

{'numb': 1158, 'question': 'Shortilar', 'answer': 'Shorts', 'options': ['Entrance', 'Fish', 'Shorts', 'Obviously']} ,

{'numb': 1159, 'question': 'Triko', 'answer': 'Tights', 'options': ['Journey', 'Alcoholic drinks', 'Advice', 'Tights']} ,

{'numb': 1160, 'question': 'Paypoq', 'answer': 'Stockings', 'options': ['Worth', 'Good morning', 'Natural', 'Stockings']} ,

{'numb': 1161, 'question': 'Jinsilar', 'answer': 'Jeans', 'options': ['Alcoholic drinks', 'Jeans', 'Email', 'Rat']} ,

{'numb': 1162, 'question': 'Tasma', 'answer': 'Belt', 'options': ['Towel', 'Belt', 'Housemate', 'Restaurant']} ,

{'numb': 1163, 'question': 'Kapushyon', 'answer': 'Hood', 'options': ['Cabbage', 'Hood', 'Relaxing', 'Perfect']} ,

{'numb': 1164, 'question': 'Ich kiyim', 'answer': 'Underwear', 'options': ['Underwear', 'The usa', 'Swimming', 'Sweater']} ,

{'numb': 1165, 'question': 'Tana', 'answer': 'Body', 'options': ['Nobody', 'Match', 'Body', 'Burger']} ,

{'numb': 1166, 'question': 'Bosh', 'answer': 'Head', 'options': ['Discuss', 'Tea', 'Head', 'Trunk']} ,

{'numb': 1167, 'question': 'Yuz', 'answer': 'Face', 'options': ['Grape', 'Switzerland', 'Face', 'Summer']} ,

{'numb': 1168, 'question': 'Peshona', 'answer': 'Forehead', 'options': ['Hot dog', 'Forehead', 'Bake', 'Tooth']} ,

{'numb': 1169, 'question': 'Burun', 'answer': 'Nose', 'options': ['Type', 'Nose', 'Do online banking', 'Balcony']} ,

{'numb': 1170, 'question': 'Quloq', 'answer': 'Ear', 'options': ['Traffic', 'Euro', 'Ear', 'Rice']} ,

{'numb': 1171, 'question': 'Ogiz', 'answer': 'Mouth', 'options': ['Mouth', 'Research', 'Sink', 'Uncle']} ,

{'numb': 1172, 'question': 'Tomog', 'answer': 'Throat', 'options': ['Money', 'Throat', 'Outside', 'Transport']} ,

{'numb': 1173, 'question': 'Koz', 'answer': 'Eye', 'options': ['Eye', 'Guide', 'Gym', 'Maybe']} ,

{'numb': 1174, 'question': 'Qosh', 'answer': 'Eyebrow', 'options': ['Borrowed', 'Eyebrow', 'Egg', 'Pay']} ,

{'numb': 1175, 'question': 'Lablar', 'answer': 'Lips', 'options': ['Dancer', 'Butter', 'Lips', 'Rag']} ,

{'numb': 1176, 'question': 'Tish', 'answer': 'Tooth', 'options': ['Tooth', 'Parachute', 'Lift', 'Cheek']} ,

{'numb': 1177, 'question': 'Soch', 'answer': 'Hair', 'options': ['July', 'On publictransport', 'Spend', 'Hair']} ,

{'numb': 1178, 'question': 'Moylov', 'answer': 'Mustache', 'options': ['Mustache', 'Hire', 'Saucepan', 'Dangerously']} ,

{'numb': 1179, 'question': 'Yuz', 'answer': 'Cheek', 'options': ['Cheek', 'Hood', 'Bank', 'Similar']} ,

{'numb': 1180, 'question': 'Iyak', 'answer': 'Chin', 'options': ['Listen', 'Seventh', 'Get dressed', 'Chin']} ,

{'numb': 1181, 'question': 'Boyin', 'answer': 'Neck', 'options': ['Tongue', 'Class', 'Neck', 'Discuss']} ,

{'numb': 1182, 'question': 'Yelka', 'answer': 'Shoulder', 'options': ['Ear', 'Transportation', 'Shoulder', 'Predict']} ,

{'numb': 1183, 'question': 'Kokrak', 'answer': 'Chest', 'options': ['Chest', 'Waiter', 'Trip', 'Flut']} ,

{'numb': 1184, 'question': 'Yurak', 'answer': 'Heart', 'options': ['Heart', 'Statement', 'Bored', 'Address']} ,

{'numb': 1185, 'question': 'Qorin', 'answer': 'Stomach', 'options': ['Public transport', 'Website', 'Stomach', 'Factory']} ,

{'numb': 1186, 'question': 'Bel', 'answer': 'Back', 'options': ['Flower', 'Airport', 'Characteristics', 'Back']} ,

{'numb': 1187, 'question': 'Bilak', 'answer': 'Wrist', 'options': ['Factory', 'Berry', 'Jump', 'Wrist']} ,

{'numb': 1188, 'question': 'Qol', 'answer': 'Hand', 'options': ['Square', 'Effort', 'Forget', 'Hand']} ,

{'numb': 1189, 'question': 'Barmoq', 'answer': 'Finger', 'options': ['Field', 'Finger', 'Sauce', 'Change']} ,

{'numb': 1190, 'question': 'Tirnoq', 'answer': 'Nail', 'options': ['Special', 'Difficult', 'Nail', 'Pe']} ,

{'numb': 1191, 'question': 'Tirsak', 'answer': 'Elbow', 'options': ['Waste', 'Subtropical', 'More', 'Elbow']} ,

{'numb': 1192, 'question': 'Oyoq', 'answer': 'Leg', 'options': ['During', 'Launderette', 'Leg', 'Fly']} ,

{'numb': 1193, 'question': 'Tizza', 'answer': 'Knee', 'options': ['Nurse', 'Police officer', 'Sculpture', 'Knee']} ,

{'numb': 1194, 'question': 'Oyoq', 'answer': 'Foot', 'options': ['You are welcome', 'Radio', 'Foot', 'Nigerian']} ,

{'numb': 1195, 'question': 'Tovon', 'answer': 'Heel', 'options': ['Heel', 'Blow', 'Hire', 'Sandwich']} ,

{'numb': 1196, 'question': 'Oyoq barmogi', 'answer': 'Toe', 'options': ['Art', 'Toe', 'Slowly', 'Swimming pool']} ,

{'numb': 1197, 'question': 'Soqol', 'answer': 'Beard', 'options': ['Newsagentãšâ¼s', 'Swap', 'Beard', 'Stay in']} ,

{'numb': 1198, 'question': 'Suyak', 'answer': 'Bone', 'options': ['Wasteful', 'Also', 'Bone', 'Loud']} ,

{'numb': 1199, 'question': 'Soglik', 'answer': 'Health', 'options': ['Frog', 'Obviously', 'Health', 'For me']} ,

{'numb': 1200, 'question': 'Soglom', 'answer': 'Healthy', 'options': ['Focus', 'Tale', 'Journey', 'Healthy']} ,

{'numb': 1201, 'question': 'Kasal', 'answer': 'Sick', 'options': ['Organization', 'Each', 'Sick', 'Blow']} ,

{'numb': 1202, 'question': 'Kasallik', 'answer': 'Sickness', 'options': ['Language', 'Sickness', 'Shoulder', 'Orange']} ,

{'numb': 1203, 'question': 'Istima', 'answer': 'Fever', 'options': ['Old', 'Athletics', 'Fever', 'Obtains']} ,

{'numb': 1204, 'question': 'Yotal', 'answer': 'Caugh', 'options': ['Caugh', 'Algeria', 'Correct', 'Oclock']} ,

{'numb': 1205, 'question': 'Burundan suv kelishi', 'answer': 'Running nose', 'options': ['Annoying', 'Survive', 'Running nose', 'Below']} ,

{'numb': 1206, 'question': 'Aks urish', 'answer': 'Sneeze', 'options': ['Sneeze', 'Annual', 'Code', 'Easily']} ,

{'numb': 1207, 'question': 'Ogriq', 'answer': 'Pain', 'options': ['Spacesuit', 'Watch', 'Pain', 'Suitable']} ,

{'numb': 1208, 'question': 'Grip', 'answer': 'Flu', 'options': ['Fascinated', 'Flu', 'Code', 'Preserve']} ,

{'numb': 1209, 'question': 'Voqea', 'answer': 'Event', 'options': ['Event', 'Passport', 'Banana', 'Noodles']} ,

{'numb': 1210, 'question': 'Tugulish', 'answer': 'Birth', 'options': ['Couple', 'Usually', 'And', 'Birth']} ,

{'numb': 1211, 'question': 'Oyin', 'answer': 'Game', 'options': ['Game', 'Long', 'Berry', 'Foot']} ,

{'numb': 1212, 'question': 'Dars', 'answer': 'Lesson', 'options': ['Parents', 'Early', 'Exit', 'Lesson']} ,

{'numb': 1213, 'question': 'Kanikul', 'answer': 'Vacation', 'options': ['Those', 'Stranger', 'Vacation', 'Sales']} ,

{'numb': 1214, 'question': 'Ziyofat', 'answer': 'Party', 'options': ['Party', 'Towel', 'Slow', 'Business']} ,

{'numb': 1215, 'question': 'Yigilish', 'answer': 'Meeting', 'options': ['Meeting', 'Label', 'Capital', 'Class']} ,

{'numb': 1216, 'question': 'Toy', 'answer': 'Wedding', 'options': ['Cutlet', 'Wedding', 'Day', 'Woman']} ,

{'numb': 1217, 'question': 'Muhokama', 'answer': 'Negotiation', 'options': ['Sandwich', 'Cake', 'Charity', 'Negotiation']} ,

{'numb': 1218, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Trip', 'options': ['Kettle', 'Trip', 'Fashionable', 'Family']} ,

{'numb': 1219, 'question': 'Olim', 'answer': 'Death', 'options': ['Death', 'Fridge', 'Vietnamese', 'Wake up']} ,

{'numb': 1220, 'question': 'Ob havo', 'answer': 'Weather', 'options': ['Of', 'Weather', 'Literature', 'Railway']} ,

{'numb': 1221, 'question': 'Quyosh', 'answer': 'Sun', 'options': ['Fog', 'Hold', 'Sun', 'High']} ,

{'numb': 1222, 'question': 'Oy', 'answer': 'Moon', 'options': ['Moon', 'Characters', 'Psychologist', 'Monkey']} ,

{'numb': 1223, 'question': 'Shamol', 'answer': 'Wind', 'options': ['Russian', 'Sad', 'Lamp', 'Wind']} ,

{'numb': 1224, 'question': 'Tuman', 'answer': 'Fog', 'options': ['Into', 'Bathroom', 'Ball', 'Fog']} ,

{'numb': 1225, 'question': 'Yomgir', 'answer': 'Rain', 'options': ['Why', 'Battery', 'Rain', 'Golf']} ,

{'numb': 1226, 'question': 'Qor', 'answer': 'Snow', 'options': ['Snow', 'Skirt', 'Sell', 'Password']} ,

{'numb': 1227, 'question': 'Osmon', 'answer': 'Sky', 'options': ['Sky', 'Signal', 'Piano', 'Healthy']} ,

{'numb': 1228, 'question': 'Bulut', 'answer': 'Cloud', 'options': ['Only', 'Cloud', 'Fermer', 'Chips']} ,

{'numb': 1229, 'question': 'Havo', 'answer': 'Air', 'options': ['Glove', 'Tomato', 'Air', 'Porridge']} ,

{'numb': 1230, 'question': 'Harorat', 'answer': 'Temperature', 'options': ['Dustpan and brush', 'Temperature', 'Wallet', 'Outdoors']} ,

{'numb': 1231, 'question': 'Daraja', 'answer': 'Degree', 'options': ['Game', 'Sea', 'Deal with', 'Degree']} ,

{'numb': 1232, 'question': 'Sanat', 'answer': 'Art', 'options': ['Towards', 'Ask', 'Forest', 'Art']} ,

{'numb': 1233, 'question': 'Musiqa', 'answer': 'Music', 'options': ['Music', 'Get dressed', 'Pe', 'Buyer']} ,

{'numb': 1234, 'question': 'Qoshiq', 'answer': 'Song', 'options': ['Headache', 'Song', 'Especially', 'Actress']} ,

{'numb': 1235, 'question': 'Adabiyot', 'answer': 'Literature', 'options': ['Spacesuit', 'Thunder', 'Bakerãšâ¼s', 'Literature']} ,

{'numb': 1236, 'question': 'Ertak', 'answer': 'Story', 'options': ['Story', 'Ham', 'Carrot', 'Chef']} ,

{'numb': 1237, 'question': 'Kino', 'answer': 'Movie', 'options': ['Movie', 'Mental health', 'Probably', 'Second']} ,

{'numb': 1238, 'question': 'Film', 'answer': 'Film', 'options': ['Challenge', 'Film', 'Pain', 'Tell jokes']} ,

{'numb': 1239, 'question': 'Haykaltaroshlik', 'answer': 'Sculpture', 'options': ['Bank', 'Cook', 'Pet', 'Sculpture']} ,

{'numb': 1240, 'question': 'Rasm', 'answer': 'Picture', 'options': ['Picture', 'Bathroom', 'Constantly', 'Judo']} ,

{'numb': 1241, 'question': 'Reklama', 'answer': 'Advertising', 'options': ['Golf', 'Advertising', 'Roof', 'Spend time']} ,

{'numb': 1242, 'question': 'Harid qilish', 'answer': 'Purchase', 'options': ['Sadness', 'Plastic', 'Clap', 'Purchase']} ,

{'numb': 1243, 'question': 'Razmer', 'answer': 'Size', 'options': ['Size', 'Registration form', 'Purse', 'Pink']} ,

{'numb': 1244, 'question': 'Narx', 'answer': 'Prise', 'options': ['Day', 'Prise', 'Tower block', 'Cleaner']} ,

{'numb': 1245, 'question': 'Pul', 'answer': 'Money', 'options': ['Luggage', 'Now', 'Recently', 'Money']} ,

{'numb': 1246, 'question': 'Naqd pul', 'answer': 'Cash', 'options': ['Waste', 'Sociable', 'West', 'Cash']} ,

{'numb': 1247, 'question': 'Chegirma', 'answer': 'Discount', 'options': ['Yard', 'Discount', 'Seal', 'Online']} ,

{'numb': 1248, 'question': 'Hisob', 'answer': 'Account', 'options': ['Account', 'Great', 'Foreign language', 'Nail']} ,

{'numb': 1249, 'question': 'Hisob varogi', 'answer': 'Bill', 'options': ['Flight', 'Bill', 'Fishing', 'Apartment']} ,

{'numb': 1250, 'question': 'Choychaqa', 'answer': 'Tip', 'options': ['Tip', 'Supermarket', 'Spend time', 'Cardigan']} ,

{'numb': 1251, 'question': 'Masofa', 'answer': 'Measure', 'options': ['Measure', 'Yoghurt', 'Narrow', 'Die']} ,

{'numb': 1252, 'question': 'Masofa', 'answer': 'Distance', 'options': ['Education', 'On theway', 'Athletics', 'Distance']} ,

{'numb': 1253, 'question': 'Uzunlik', 'answer': 'Length', 'options': ['Lamp', 'Visitor', 'Length', 'Big']} ,

{'numb': 1254, 'question': 'Boy', 'answer': 'Height', 'options': ['Height', 'Checkout', 'Book', 'Peach']} ,

{'numb': 1255, 'question': 'Chuqurlik', 'answer': 'Depth', 'options': ['Washing machine', 'Salt', 'Depth', 'Under']} ,

{'numb': 1256, 'question': 'Kuch', 'answer': 'Strength', 'options': ['Curtain', 'Strawberry', 'Chemist', 'Strength']} ,

{'numb': 1257, 'question': 'Tezlik', 'answer': 'Speed', 'options': ['Photo', 'Worth', 'Speed', 'Mess']} ,

{'numb': 1258, 'question': 'Kilometr', 'answer': 'Kilometr', 'options': ['Notepad', 'Bathroom', 'Monkey', 'Kilometr']} ,

{'numb': 1259, 'question': 'Kilogramm', 'answer': 'Kilogramm', 'options': ['Field', 'Kilogramm', 'Entrance exam', 'Best']} ,

{'numb': 1260, 'question': 'Funt', 'answer': 'Pound', 'options': ['Shout', 'Pound', 'Stranger', 'Ice cream']} ,

{'numb': 1261, 'question': 'Hissiyot', 'answer': 'Feeling', 'options': ['Musician', 'Village', 'Feeling', 'Introduce']} ,

{'numb': 1262, 'question': 'Oyin kulgu', 'answer': 'Fun', 'options': ['Denmark', 'Death', 'Fun', 'Most']} ,

{'numb': 1263, 'question': 'Hursandchilik', 'answer': 'Joy', 'options': ['Joy', 'Carpet', 'Brand new', 'Sixth']} ,

{'numb': 1264, 'question': 'Qorquv', 'answer': 'Fear', 'options': ['Fear', 'Tiny', 'Experience', 'Interesting']} ,

{'numb': 1265, 'question': 'Gamgin', 'answer': 'Sadness', 'options': ['Oil', 'Trainers', 'Lawyer', 'Sadness']} ,

{'numb': 1266, 'question': 'Ehtiros', 'answer': 'Passion', 'options': ['Plan', 'Passion', 'Surprising', 'Car']} ,

{'numb': 1267, 'question': 'Baxt', 'answer': 'Happiness', 'options': ['Survive', 'Weapon', 'Project', 'Happiness']} ,

{'numb': 1268, 'question': 'Tinch', 'answer': 'Peace', 'options': ['Peace', 'Grape', 'Relax', 'Stick']} ,

{'numb': 1269, 'question': 'Sevgi', 'answer': 'Love', 'options': ['Alphabet', 'Corn', 'Goose', 'Love']} ,

{'numb': 1270, 'question': 'Nafratlanish', 'answer': 'Hate', 'options': ['English', 'Backpack', 'Tv', 'Hate']} ,

{'numb': 1271, 'question': 'Dunyo', 'answer': 'World', 'options': ['Duty', 'Remember', 'Pleasant', 'World']} ,

{'numb': 1272, 'question': 'Qalb', 'answer': 'Soul', 'options': ['Typical', 'Become', 'Soul', 'Inside']} ,

{'numb': 1273, 'question': 'Hayot', 'answer': 'Life', 'options': ['Germs', 'Useby', 'Lamb', 'Life']} ,

{'numb': 1274, 'question': 'Bilim', 'answer': 'Knowledge', 'options': ['Housework', 'Roof', 'Knowledge', 'Person']} ,

{'numb': 1275, 'question': 'Topshiriq', 'answer': 'Task', 'options': ['Task', 'Painter', 'Accommodation', 'Cloudy']} ,

{'numb': 1276, 'question': 'Mashq', 'answer': 'Exercise', 'options': ['Trainers', 'Toothpaste', 'Exercise', 'Fruit']} ,

{'numb': 1277, 'question': 'Omad', 'answer': 'Luck', 'options': ['Luck', 'Duty', 'Birth date', 'Adventure']} ,

{'numb': 1278, 'question': 'Muammo', 'answer': 'Problem', 'options': ['Picture', 'Problem', 'Vegetarian cookbook', 'Neighbor']} ,

{'numb': 1279, 'question': 'Imkoniyat', 'answer': 'Opportunity', 'options': ['Lamp', 'A cup of', 'Opportunity', 'February']} ,

{'numb': 1280, 'question': 'Qobiliyat', 'answer': 'Ability', 'options': ['Ability', 'Goal', 'Tuesday', 'Least']} ,

{'numb': 1281, 'question': 'Chiroy', 'answer': 'Beauty', 'options': ['Habit', 'Machine', 'Badly', 'Beauty']} ,

{'numb': 1282, 'question': 'Xavf', 'answer': 'Denger', 'options': ['Reply', 'Cloudy', 'Wolf', 'Denger']} ,

{'numb': 1283, 'question': 'Tajriba', 'answer': 'Experience', 'options': ['Romantic', 'Experience', 'Knee', 'Vending machine']} ,

{'numb': 1284, 'question': 'Hotira', 'answer': 'Memory', 'options': ['Memory', 'Honey', 'Tired', 'Tenth']} ,

{'numb': 1285, 'question': 'Foyda', 'answer': 'Benefit', 'options': ['Paint', 'Benefit', 'Be afraid of', 'Go to the theatre']} ,

{'numb': 1286, 'question': 'Manfaat', 'answer': 'Advantage', 'options': ['Leave home', 'Finish', 'Advantage', 'Can']} ,

{'numb': 1287, 'question': 'Foyda', 'answer': 'Profit', 'options': ['Profit', 'Bread', 'Mexico', 'Coast']} ,

{'numb': 1288, 'question': 'Odat', 'answer': 'Habit', 'options': ['Parking space', 'Habit', 'Something', 'Text']} ,

{'numb': 1289, 'question': 'Sabab', 'answer': 'Reason', 'options': ['Annual', 'Somebody', 'Reason', 'Simple']} ,

{'numb': 1290, 'question': 'Oqibat', 'answer': 'Consequence', 'options': ['Twin', 'Herb', 'Number', 'Consequence']} ,

{'numb': 1291, 'question': 'Mano', 'answer': 'Meaning', 'options': ['These', 'Accountant', 'Meaning', 'Lip']} ,

{'numb': 1292, 'question': 'Usul', 'answer': 'Means', 'options': ['Means', 'Learn to swim', 'Fist', 'Eye']} ,

{'numb': 1293, 'question': 'Say harakat', 'answer': 'Effort', 'options': ['Boss', 'Apple juice', 'Effort', 'Restaurant']} ,

{'numb': 1294, 'question': 'Muvaffaqiyat', 'answer': 'Success', 'options': ['Road', 'Lie', 'Collect', 'Success']} ,

{'numb': 1295, 'question': 'Maqsad', 'answer': 'Goal', 'options': ['Goal', 'Mark', 'Fast lane', 'Text']} ,

{'numb': 1296, 'question': 'Mojiza', 'answer': 'Miracle', 'options': ['Mid', 'Planner', 'Miracle', 'Gloves']} ,

{'numb': 1297, 'question': 'Fan', 'answer': 'Science', 'options': ['Science', 'Compare', 'Shower', 'Kitchen']} ,

{'numb': 1298, 'question': 'Til', 'answer': 'Language', 'options': ['Eat', 'Gloves', 'Language', 'Opportunity']} ,

{'numb': 1299, 'question': 'Soz', 'answer': 'Word', 'options': ['Word', 'Shower', 'Clothes', 'Watermelon']} ,

{'numb': 1300, 'question': 'Olov', 'answer': 'Fire', 'options': ['Fire', 'Travel', 'Forest', 'Autumn']} ,

{'numb': 1301, 'question': 'Holat', 'answer': 'Case', 'options': ['Lemonade', 'Must', 'Case', 'Above']} ,

{'numb': 1302, 'question': 'Vaziyat', 'answer': 'Circumstances', 'options': ['Fist', 'Circumstances', 'Tack', 'Peach']} ,

{'numb': 1303, 'question': 'Hayol', 'answer': 'Thought', 'options': ['Thought', 'Vase', 'Businessman', 'Calendar']} ,

{'numb': 1304, 'question': 'Tanlov', 'answer': 'Choise', 'options': ['Potatoes', 'Choise', 'Solid', 'Economy']} ,

{'numb': 1305, 'question': 'Ruhsat', 'answer': 'Permit', 'options': ['Eat', 'Permit', 'Rope', 'Filling']} ,

{'numb': 1306, 'question': 'Yetkazib berish', 'answer': 'Delivery', 'options': ['Theater', 'Connection', 'Graduation', 'Delivery']} ,

{'numb': 1307, 'question': 'Muvaffaqiyat', 'answer': 'Achievement', 'options': ['Agree', 'Married', 'Achievement', 'Cafe']} ,

{'numb': 1308, 'question': 'Burch', 'answer': 'Duty', 'options': ['Flat', 'Duty', 'Frying pan', 'Last']} ,

{'numb': 1309, 'question': 'Kechikish', 'answer': 'Delay', 'options': ['Cook', 'Delay', 'Friendly', 'Review']} ,

{'numb': 1310, 'question': 'Munosabat', 'answer': 'Relationship', 'options': ['Relationship', 'Save up', 'Food', 'Winter']} ,

{'numb': 1311, 'question': 'Belgi', 'answer': 'Mark', 'options': ['Pe', 'Mark', 'Bridge', 'Tea']} ,

{'numb': 1312, 'question': 'Xato', 'answer': 'Mistake', 'options': ['Casual', 'Grey', 'Annoying', 'Mistake']} ,

{'numb': 1313, 'question': 'Hulq', 'answer': 'Behavior', 'options': ['Chicken', 'Least', 'Number', 'Behavior']} ,

{'numb': 1314, 'question': 'Taklifnoma', 'answer': 'Invitation', 'options': ['Go to the theatre', 'Useful', 'Invitation', 'Leave']} ,

{'numb': 1315, 'question': 'Rivojlantirish', 'answer': 'Development', 'options': ['Russia', 'Knowledge', 'Development', 'Russian']} ,

{'numb': 1316, 'question': 'Qaror', 'answer': 'Decision', 'options': ['Card games', 'Useby', 'Decision', 'Hello']} ,

{'numb': 1317, 'question': 'Yechim', 'answer': 'Solution', 'options': ['Equip', 'Wall', 'Tell', 'Solution']} ,

{'numb': 1318, 'question': 'Maslahat', 'answer': 'Advice', 'options': ['Decision', 'Present', 'Advice', 'Station']} ,

{'numb': 1319, 'question': 'Rozilik', 'answer': 'Agreement', 'options': ['Agreement', 'Sink', 'Cupcake', 'Eighth']} ,

{'numb': 1320, 'question': 'Royxat', 'answer': 'List', 'options': ['List', 'Look', 'Float', 'Predict']} ,

{'numb': 1321, 'question': 'Bahs', 'answer': 'Argument', 'options': ['Lend', 'Argument', 'Rainy', 'Corn']} ,

{'numb': 1322, 'question': 'Tekshirish', 'answer': 'Test', 'options': ['Fry', 'Granddaughter', 'Test', 'Often']} ,

{'numb': 1323, 'question': 'Qadam', 'answer': 'Step', 'options': ['Table', 'Lebanese', 'Best', 'Step']} ,

{'numb': 1324, 'question': 'Parcha', 'answer': 'Piece', 'options': ['Have a reservation', 'Door', 'Heart', 'Piece']} ,

{'numb': 1325, 'question': 'Hudud', 'answer': 'Area', 'options': ['Damp', 'Tobacco', 'Area', 'Ability']} ,

{'numb': 1326, 'question': 'Juft', 'answer': 'Pair', 'options': ['Flower stall', 'Pair', 'Decision', 'Chair']} ,

{'numb': 1327, 'question': 'Juftlik', 'answer': 'Couple', 'options': ['Couple', 'Ill', 'Lake', 'Season']} ,

{'numb': 1328, 'question': 'Tartibsizlik', 'answer': 'Mess', 'options': ['Packet', 'Mess', 'Pay', 'Towel']} ,

{'numb': 1329, 'question': 'Yuza', 'answer': 'Surface', 'options': ['Surface', 'Mine', 'Capital', 'Fever']} ,

{'numb': 1330, 'question': 'Savol', 'answer': 'Question', 'options': ['Credit card', 'Waterfall', 'Question', 'Weather']} ,

{'numb': 1331, 'question': '...dan', 'answer': 'From', 'options': ['Get around', 'Athletics', 'From', 'Update']} ,

{'numb': 1332, 'question': '...ning', 'answer': 'Of', 'options': ['Pretty', 'His', 'Of', 'Bring']} ,

{'numb': 1333, 'question': '...ga', 'answer': 'To', 'options': ['To', 'Lamb', 'Basic', 'Perhaps']} ,

{'numb': 1334, 'question': '...da', 'answer': 'In', 'options': ['Death', 'In', 'Challenge', 'Postcard']} ,

{'numb': 1335, 'question': '...da', 'answer': 'On', 'options': ['Flower', 'Tennis', 'On', 'Plum']} ,

{'numb': 1336, 'question': 'Tagida', 'answer': 'Under', 'options': ['Ending', 'Have', 'Under', 'Cook']} ,

{'numb': 1337, 'question': 'Orqasida', 'answer': 'Behind', 'options': ['When', 'Behind', 'Hold', 'Smart']} ,

{'numb': 1338, 'question': 'Bilan', 'answer': 'With', 'options': ['You are welcome', 'Chat', 'Urdu', 'With']} ,

{'numb': 1339, 'question': '...siz', 'answer': 'Without', 'options': ['Spinach', 'Without', 'Object', 'Mountain']} ,

{'numb': 1340, 'question': 'Old tarafda', 'answer': 'In front of', 'options': ['In front of', 'Friend', 'Theater', 'Consumer']} ,

{'numb': 1341, 'question': 'Oldin', 'answer': 'Before', 'options': ['Before', 'Bobsleigh', 'Lift', 'Cloth']} ,

{'numb': 1342, 'question': 'Keyin', 'answer': 'After', 'options': ['Shawl', 'Special', 'Valuable', 'After']} ,

{'numb': 1343, 'question': 'Ortasiga', 'answer': 'Between', 'options': ['Booking', 'Between', 'Chin', 'Living']} ,

{'numb': 1344, 'question': 'Yaqinida', 'answer': 'Near', 'options': ['Fall', 'Near', 'Relationship', 'Russian']} ,

{'numb': 1345, 'question': 'Uchun', 'answer': 'For', 'options': ['Happy', 'For', 'Play', 'Smart']} ,

{'numb': 1346, 'question': 'Dan buyon', 'answer': 'Since', 'options': ['Since', 'Negotiation', 'Class', 'Behaviour']} ,

{'numb': 1347, 'question': 'Davomida', 'answer': 'During', 'options': ['Waterfall', 'During', 'How', 'Talk']} ,

{'numb': 1348, 'question': 'Atrofida', 'answer': 'Around', 'options': ['Good bye', 'Good morning', 'Around', 'Strength']} ,

{'numb': 1349, 'question': 'Chunki', 'answer': 'Because', 'options': ['Tie', 'Candle', 'Romantic', 'Because']} ,

{'numb': 1350, 'question': 'Haqida', 'answer': 'About', 'options': ['Play', 'About', 'Denmark', 'Facility']} ,

{'numb': 1351, 'question': 'Qarshi', 'answer': 'Against', 'options': ['Since', 'Against', 'Shovel', 'Success']} ,

{'numb': 1352, 'question': 'Ichida', 'answer': 'Among', 'options': ['Among', 'Carpenter', 'Lonely', 'Fantastic']} ,

{'numb': 1353, 'question': 'Orqali', 'answer': 'Through', 'options': ['Chin', 'Denmark', 'Through', 'Go']} ,

{'numb': 1354, 'question': 'Ga(soatiga 100 km)', 'answer': 'Per', 'options': ['Per', 'Melon', 'Digital', 'Lovely']} ,

{'numb': 1355, 'question': 'Tepasida', 'answer': 'Above', 'options': ['Calendar', 'Above', 'Swimming', 'Lamb']} ,

{'numb': 1356, 'question': 'Pastida', 'answer': 'Below', 'options': ['Stove', 'Environment', 'Below', 'Work']} ,

{'numb': 1357, 'question': 'Rang', 'answer': 'Colour', 'options': ['Shame', 'Colour', 'Ability', 'Airline']} ,

{'numb': 1358, 'question': 'Qora', 'answer': 'Black', 'options': ['A lot', 'Discount', 'Black', 'Photocopy']} ,

{'numb': 1359, 'question': 'Jigarrang', 'answer': 'Brown', 'options': ['Repellent', 'Brown', 'Socket', 'Pay']} ,

{'numb': 1360, 'question': 'Kulrang', 'answer': 'Grey', 'options': ['Grey', 'Ruler', 'Finger', 'Cloudy']} ,

{'numb': 1361, 'question': 'Qizil', 'answer': 'Red', 'options': ['Cheek', 'Red', 'Cheese', 'Busy']} ,

{'numb': 1362, 'question': 'Sariq', 'answer': 'Yellow', 'options': ['Cereal', 'Yellow', 'Survey', 'Land']} ,

{'numb': 1363, 'question': 'Pushti', 'answer': 'Pink', 'options': ['Pink', 'Blanket', 'Department store', 'Passport']} ,

{'numb': 1364, 'question': 'Siyohrang', 'answer': 'Purple', 'options': ['Purple', 'Repair', 'Grow up', 'Move']} ,

{'numb': 1365, 'question': 'Yaxshiroq', 'answer': 'Better', 'options': ['Sweet', 'Office worker', 'Better', 'Shy']} ,

{'numb': 1366, 'question': 'Zor', 'answer': 'Best', 'options': ['Computer game', 'Best', 'Have', 'Amazed']} ,

{'numb': 1367, 'question': 'Yomonroq', 'answer': 'Worse', 'options': ['Worse', 'Repair', 'Between', 'Sweater']} ,

{'numb': 1368, 'question': 'Eng yomon', 'answer': 'Worst', 'options': ['Worst', 'These', 'Businessman', 'Germs']} ,

{'numb': 1369, 'question': 'Koproq', 'answer': 'More', 'options': ['Wood', 'More', 'Work freelance', 'Chess']} ,

{'numb': 1370, 'question': 'Eng kop', 'answer': 'Most', 'options': ['Practical skills', 'Most', 'Parking space', 'Leave']} ,

{'numb': 1371, 'question': 'Kamroq', 'answer': 'Less', 'options': ['Top', 'Less', 'City', 'Argument']} ,

{'numb': 1372, 'question': 'Eng kam', 'answer': 'Least', 'options': ['Least', 'Only', 'Shorts', 'Put']} ,

{'numb': 1373, 'question': 'Bazan', 'answer': 'Sometimes', 'options': ['Room', 'Architect', 'Sometimes', 'Buy a house']} ,

{'numb': 1374, 'question': 'Hech qachon', 'answer': 'Never', 'options': ['Golf', 'Studio flat', 'Never', 'Song']} ,

{'numb': 1375, 'question': 'Kamdan kam', 'answer': 'Seldom', 'options': ['Painter', 'Land', 'Seldom', 'Before']} ,

{'numb': 1376, 'question': 'Odatda', 'answer': 'Usually', 'options': ['Usually', 'Check in', 'Indonesia', 'Pe']} ,

{'numb': 1377, 'question': 'Tez tez', 'answer': 'Often', 'options': ['Meaning', 'Often', 'Cafe', 'Spoon']} ,

{'numb': 1378, 'question': 'Har doim', 'answer': 'Always', 'options': ['Always', 'Professor', 'Train', 'Wood']} ,

{'numb': 1379, 'question': 'Tez orada', 'answer': 'Soon', 'options': ['Consumer', 'Soon', 'Individual', 'Kitchen']} ,

{'numb': 1380, 'question': 'Yaqinda', 'answer': 'Recently', 'options': ['Recently', 'Receive', 'Save up', 'Tropical']} ,

{'numb': 1381, 'question': 'Yaxshi', 'answer': 'Well', 'options': ['Perhaps', 'Aerobics', 'Communicate', 'Well']} ,

{'numb': 1382, 'question': 'Uzoq', 'answer': 'Far', 'options': ['Pie', 'Early', 'Start work', 'Far']} ,

{'numb': 1383, 'question': 'Aniq', 'answer': 'Exactly', 'options': ['Bottle', 'Disease', 'Exactly', 'Guilty']} ,

{'numb': 1384, 'question': 'Balki', 'answer': 'Probably', 'options': ['Probably', 'Spell', 'Travel', 'Reply']} ,

{'numb': 1385, 'question': 'Balki', 'answer': 'Maybe', 'options': ['Problem', 'Maybe', 'Label', 'Watch tv']} ,

{'numb': 1386, 'question': 'Balki', 'answer': 'Perhaps', 'options': ['Diabetes', 'Place of work', 'Say', 'Perhaps']} ,

{'numb': 1387, 'question': 'Haqiqatdan', 'answer': 'Really', 'options': ['Use', 'Tonight', 'Really', 'Hand']} ,

{'numb': 1388, 'question': 'Albatta', 'answer': 'Of course', 'options': ['Apply', 'Of course', 'Stress', 'Destroy']} ,

{'numb': 1389, 'question': 'Albatta', 'answer': 'Certainly', 'options': ['Certainly', 'Chest', 'Ticket', 'Learn a new language']} ,

{'numb': 1390, 'question': 'Ochiq oydin', 'answer': 'Obviously', 'options': ['Question', 'Ceiling', 'Ridiculous', 'Obviously']} ,

{'numb': 1391, 'question': 'Ayniqsa', 'answer': 'Especially', 'options': ['Nurse', 'Especially', 'Traveller', 'Orange']} ,

{'numb': 1392, 'question': 'Bu', 'answer': 'This', 'options': ['Outside', 'Frog', 'Lift', 'This']} ,

{'numb': 1393, 'question': 'Anavi', 'answer': 'That', 'options': ['Go to bed', 'Radio', 'That', 'Medical']} ,

{'numb': 1394, 'question': 'Bular', 'answer': 'These', 'options': ['Goodbye', 'Blow', 'These', 'Hi']} ,

{'numb': 1395, 'question': 'Anavilar', 'answer': 'Those', 'options': ['Turkish', 'Solve', 'Text', 'Those']} ,

{'numb': 1396, 'question': 'Birga', 'answer': 'Together', 'options': ['Together', 'Map reading', 'Unlucky', 'Vase']} ,

{'numb': 1397, 'question': 'Oldinga', 'answer': 'Forward', 'options': ['Bank account', 'Forward', 'Shop online', 'Elbow']} ,

{'numb': 1398, 'question': 'Hatto', 'answer': 'Even', 'options': ['Meet', 'A cup of', 'Scissors', 'Even']} ,

{'numb': 1399, 'question': 'Yetarli', 'answer': 'Enough', 'options': ['Relaxed', 'Enough', 'Behind', 'Type']} ,

{'numb': 1400, 'question': 'Ham', 'answer': 'Also', 'options': ['Typist', 'Between', 'Also', 'Stepfather']} ,

{'numb': 1401, 'question': 'Ham', 'answer': 'Too', 'options': ['Too', 'Free', 'Local', 'Mug']} ,

{'numb': 1402, 'question': 'Faqat', 'answer': 'Only', 'options': ['Password', 'Equipment', 'Countryside', 'Only']} ,

{'numb': 1403, 'question': 'Yoki', 'answer': 'Or', 'options': ['Window', 'Cupboard', 'Or', 'Depth']} ,

{'numb': 1404, 'question': 'Lekin', 'answer': 'But', 'options': ['Helmet', 'But', 'Teach', 'Jeans']} ,

{'numb': 1405, 'question': 'Har qanday holatda', 'answer': 'However', 'options': ['Aerobics', 'However', 'Bridge', 'Garbage']} ,

{'numb': 1406, 'question': 'Agar', 'answer': 'If', 'options': ['Lovely', 'If', 'Community', 'Sandwich']} ,

{'numb': 1407, 'question': '...ga qaramay', 'answer': 'Although', 'options': ['Time', 'Best friend', 'Although', 'Free']} ,

{'numb': 1408, 'question': 'Qorqmoq', 'answer': 'Be afraid of', 'options': ['Stick', 'Apple juice', 'Be afraid of', 'Tuesday']} ,

{'numb': 1409, 'question': 'Qiziqmoq', 'answer': 'Be interested in', 'options': ['Retire', 'Article', 'Be interested in', 'Forget']} ,

{'numb': 1410, 'question': 'Hayron bolmoq', 'answer': 'Be surprised', 'options': ['Free', 'Be surprised', 'Tale', 'Cash']} ,

{'numb': 1411, 'question': 'Togri kelyapti', 'answer': 'Have to', 'options': ['Have to', 'Poor', 'Happy', 'Nut']} ,

{'numb': 1412, 'question': 'Orindan turish', 'answer': 'Get up', 'options': ['Near', 'Get up', 'House sit', 'Learning skills']} ,

{'numb': 1413, 'question': 'Kiymoq', 'answer': 'Put on', 'options': ['Often', 'Practical skills', 'Class', 'Put on']} ,

{'numb': 1414, 'question': 'Yechmoq', 'answer': 'Take off', 'options': ['Wet', 'Stockings', 'Take off', 'Snack']} ,

{'numb': 1415, 'question': 'Otkir', 'answer': 'Keen', 'options': ['Science', 'Keen', 'Please', 'Designer']} ,

{'numb': 1416, 'question': 'Tark etmoq', 'answer': 'Abandon', 'options': ['Menu', 'Hardship', 'Abandon', 'Bread']} ,

{'numb': 1417, 'question': 'Rashkchi hasadgoy', 'answer': 'Jealous', 'options': ['Jealous', 'Parking space', 'Badly', 'Effort']} ,

{'numb': 1418, 'question': 'Andisha', 'answer': 'Tack', 'options': ['Tack', 'Curry', 'Behaviour', 'Builder']} ,

{'numb': 1419, 'question': 'Qasam', 'answer': 'Oath', 'options': ['Oath', 'In advance', 'House swap', 'Lips']} ,

{'numb': 1420, 'question': 'Bosh', 'answer': 'Vacant', 'options': ['Smartly', 'Vacant', 'Mother', 'Twenty third']} ,

{'numb': 1421, 'question': 'Qiyinchilik', 'answer': 'Hardship', 'options': ['Live', 'Hardship', 'Sweet', 'Communication skills']} ,

{'numb': 1422, 'question': 'Jasur muloyim', 'answer': 'Gallant', 'options': ['Handshake', 'Gallant', 'Touch', 'Abandon']} ,

{'numb': 1423, 'question': 'Malumotlar', 'answer': 'Data', 'options': ['Son', 'Carefully', 'Data', 'Cutlet']} ,

{'numb': 1424, 'question': 'Kop', 'answer': 'Many', 'options': ['Miss', 'Many', 'Sofa', 'Cup']} ,

{'numb': 1425, 'question': 'Kop', 'answer': 'Much', 'options': ['Collect', 'Park', 'Much', 'Temperature']} ,

{'numb': 1426, 'question': 'Kam', 'answer': 'Few', 'options': ['A bottle of', 'Grandson', 'Restaurant', 'Few']} ,

{'numb': 1427, 'question': 'Kam', 'answer': 'Little', 'options': ['Depth', 'Little', 'Teacher', 'Dessert']} ,

{'numb': 1428, 'question': 'Bir qancha', 'answer': 'Some', 'options': ['Message', 'Some', 'Summer', 'Abandon']} ,

{'numb': 1429, 'question': 'Har qanday', 'answer': 'Any', 'options': ['Storyteller', 'Funny', 'Interested in', 'Any']} ,

{'numb': 1430, 'question': 'Kimdir', 'answer': 'Somebody', 'options': ['Noodles', 'Office worker', 'Somebody', 'Duvet']} ,

{'numb': 1431, 'question': 'Nimadir', 'answer': 'Something', 'options': ['Rat', 'Something', 'Straw', 'Giraffe']} ,

{'numb': 1432, 'question': 'Har kim', 'answer': 'Anybody', 'options': ['Go to work', 'Anxious', 'Anybody', 'Magazine']} ,

{'numb': 1433, 'question': 'Har nima', 'answer': 'Anything', 'options': ['Anything', 'Tuesday', 'Disappointed', 'All']} ,

{'numb': 1434, 'question': 'Hech kim', 'answer': 'Nobody', 'options': ['Log on', 'Weapon', 'Nobody', 'Clap']} ,

{'numb': 1435, 'question': 'Hech nima', 'answer': 'Nothing', 'options': ['Starter', 'Nothing', 'Daughter', 'Great']} ,

{'numb': 1436, 'question': 'Bu yerda', 'answer': 'Here', 'options': ['Boss', 'Ingredient', 'Here', 'Behaviour']} ,

{'numb': 1437, 'question': 'U yerda', 'answer': 'There', 'options': ['Retire', 'Practice', 'Capsule', 'There']} ,

{'numb': 1438, 'question': 'Hozir', 'answer': 'Now', 'options': ['Second', 'Now', 'Soft', 'Sleeve']} ,

{'numb': 1439, 'question': 'Yana', 'answer': 'Again', 'options': ['Again', 'Lebanese', 'Sit', 'Festival']} ,

{'numb': 1440, 'question': 'Keyin', 'answer': 'Then', 'options': ['Then', 'Shower', 'Delicious', 'Hand']} ,

{'numb': 1441, 'question': 'Hozirgina', 'answer': 'Just', 'options': ['Launderette', 'Mobile phone', 'Euro', 'Just']} ,

{'numb': 1442, 'question': 'Hali ham', 'answer': 'Still', 'options': ['Flavour', 'Clean', 'All', 'Still']} ,

{'numb': 1443, 'question': 'Hali', 'answer': 'Yet', 'options': ['Change jobs', 'Yet', 'Apply', 'Music']} ,

{'numb': 1444, 'question': 'Deyarli', 'answer': 'Almost', 'options': ['Another', 'Forehead', 'Change jobs', 'Almost']} ,

{'numb': 1445, 'question': 'Juda', 'answer': 'Very', 'options': ['Chance career', 'Very', 'Electric piano', 'Become']} ,

{'numb': 1446, 'question': 'Har bir', 'answer': 'Every', 'options': ['Rent', 'Every', 'Tourist information centre', 'Usual']} ,

{'numb': 1447, 'question': 'Har qaysi', 'answer': 'Each', 'options': ['Text', 'Cloth', 'Each', 'Already']} ,

{'numb': 1448, 'question': 'Hamma', 'answer': 'All', 'options': ['Light', 'Foggy', 'Natural', 'All']} ,

{'numb': 1449, 'question': 'Bunday', 'answer': 'Suchã‚', 'options': ['Fever', 'Suchã‚', 'Boss', 'Dirty']} ,

{'numb': 1450, 'question': 'Tepa', 'answer': 'Up', 'options': ['Discount', 'Soup', 'Up', 'Microwave']} ,

{'numb': 1451, 'question': 'Past', 'answer': 'Down', 'options': ['Repetitivestraininjury', 'Down', 'False', 'Have lunch']} ,

{'numb': 1452, 'question': 'Amerikalik', 'answer': 'American', 'options': ['Code', 'American', 'Mp3 player', 'Dishonest']} ,

{'numb': 1453, 'question': 'Arabcha', 'answer': 'Arabic', 'options': ['Stick', 'Fluent', 'Arabic', 'Usually']} ,

{'numb': 1454, 'question': 'Rassom', 'answer': 'Artist', 'options': ['Knowledge', 'Algeria', 'Move house or flat', 'Artist']} ,

{'numb': 1455, 'question': 'Xola', 'answer': 'Aunt', 'options': ['Lie', 'Pupil', 'Railway', 'Aunt']} ,

{'numb': 1456, 'question': 'Xojayin', 'answer': 'Boss', 'options': ['Often', 'Fox', 'Boss', 'Bring']} ,

{'numb': 1457, 'question': 'Britaniya', 'answer': 'British', 'options': ['Russia', 'His', 'British', 'Beautiful']} ,

{'numb': 1458, 'question': 'Aka uka', 'answer': 'Brother', 'options': ['August', 'Brother', 'Registration form', 'Text']} ,

{'numb': 1459, 'question': 'Kuyov pochcha', 'answer': 'Brother in law', 'options': ['Repetitivestraininjury', 'Hostel', 'Flight', 'Brother in law']} ,

{'numb': 1460, 'question': 'Biznes boshqaruvi', 'answer': 'Business management', 'options': ['Business management', 'Pleased', 'Class', 'Backpack']} ,

{'numb': 1461, 'question': 'Avtomobil mexanik', 'answer': 'Car mechanic', 'options': ['Lockout', 'Car mechanic', 'Rainwater', 'Children']} ,

{'numb': 1462, 'question': 'Bola', 'answer': 'Child', 'options': ['Practical skills', 'Astronaut', 'Child', 'Even']} ,

{'numb': 1463, 'question': 'Bolalar', 'answer': 'Children', 'options': ['In late twenties', 'Sports', 'Yet', 'Children']} ,

{'numb': 1464, 'question': 'Xitoylik', 'answer': 'Chinese', 'options': ['High', 'Tooth', 'Magazine', 'Chinese']} ,

{'numb': 1465, 'question': 'Muloqot qilish', 'answer': 'Communicate', 'options': ['Piece', 'Communicate', 'England', 'Competitor']} ,

{'numb': 1466, 'question': 'Mamlakat', 'answer': 'Country', 'options': ['Country', 'Tomato', 'Object', 'Trip']} ,

{'numb': 1467, 'question': 'Amakivachcha', 'answer': 'Cousin', 'options': ['Kilometr', 'Yard', 'Miss', 'Cousin']} ,

{'numb': 1468, 'question': 'Qiz', 'answer': 'Daughter', 'options': ['Daughter', 'Physical', 'Sheet', 'Saucer']} ,

{'numb': 1469, 'question': 'Dizayner', 'answer': 'Designer', 'options': ['Designer', 'Eyesight', 'Walk', 'Shy']} ,

{'numb': 1470, 'question': 'Amirlik', 'answer': 'Emirate', 'options': ['Diet', 'Should', 'Perfect', 'Emirate']} ,

{'numb': 1471, 'question': 'Oyila ismi', 'answer': 'Family name', 'options': ['Go out with friends', 'Pay', 'Plant', 'Family name']} ,

{'numb': 1472, 'question': 'Dada', 'answer': 'Father', 'options': ['Father', 'Listen', 'Scooter', 'Leather']} ,

{'numb': 1473, 'question': 'Ravon', 'answer': 'Fluent', 'options': ['Education', 'Fluent', 'Body', 'If']} ,

{'numb': 1474, 'question': 'Fransuz', 'answer': 'French', 'options': ['French', 'If', 'Weight litfing', 'Tweet']} ,

{'numb': 1475, 'question': 'Genetik', 'answer': 'Genetic', 'options': ['Designer shoes', 'Painter', 'Genetic', 'Hot']} ,

{'numb': 1476, 'question': 'Nevarasi', 'answer': 'Granddaughter', 'options': ['Statistic', 'Early', 'Go on facebook', 'Granddaughter']} ,

{'numb': 1477, 'question': 'Bobo', 'answer': 'Grandfather', 'options': ['Hire', 'Journey', 'Public transport', 'Grandfather']} ,

{'numb': 1478, 'question': 'Buvi', 'answer': 'Grandmother', 'options': ['Grandmother', 'Bake', 'Theatre', 'Cruel']} ,

{'numb': 1479, 'question': 'Nabirasi', 'answer': 'Grandson', 'options': ['Genetic', 'Nobody', 'Camera', 'Grandson']} ,

{'numb': 1480, 'question': 'Grek', 'answer': 'Grek', 'options': ['Choose', 'City', 'Keen', 'Grek']} ,

{'numb': 1481, 'question': 'Venger', 'answer': 'Hungarian', 'options': ['Suggest', 'Complete', 'Learn to swim', 'Hungarian']} ,

{'numb': 1482, 'question': 'Er', 'answer': 'Husband', 'options': ['Oclock', 'Husband', 'New zealand', 'Iron']} ,

{'numb': 1483, 'question': 'Tanishtirish', 'answer': 'Introduce', 'options': ['Special', 'Shop assistant', 'Industry', 'Introduce']} ,

{'numb': 1484, 'question': 'Italyan', 'answer': 'Italian', 'options': ['Italian', 'Yet', 'Happen', 'Dog']} ,

{'numb': 1485, 'question': 'Yapon', 'answer': 'Japanese', 'options': ['Dance', 'Drink', 'Japanese', 'Chin']} ,

{'numb': 1486, 'question': 'Familiya', 'answer': 'Last name', 'options': ['Checkout', 'Science', 'Last name', 'Flour']} ,

{'numb': 1487, 'question': 'Livan', 'answer': 'Lebanese', 'options': ['Lebanese', 'Boot', 'Improve', 'Thirtieth']} ,

{'numb': 1488, 'question': 'Uylangan', 'answer': 'Married', 'options': ['Measure', 'Tobacco', 'Cheek', 'Married']} ,

{'numb': 1489, 'question': 'Meksikan', 'answer': 'Mexican', 'options': ['Cancer', 'Mp3 player', 'Mexican', 'Toast']} ,

{'numb': 1490, 'question': 'Ona', 'answer': 'Mother', 'options': ['Realize', 'Mother', 'Architect', 'Contact']} ,

{'numb': 1491, 'question': 'Millati', 'answer': 'Nationality', 'options': ['Theme', 'Ship', 'Between', 'Nationality']} ,

{'numb': 1492, 'question': 'Qoshni', 'answer': 'Neighbor', 'options': ['Neighbor', 'Survey', 'Minut', 'Wake up']} ,

{'numb': 1493, 'question': 'Jiyani', 'answer': 'Nephew', 'options': ['Mobile phone', 'Nephew', 'Fine', 'Agree']} ,

{'numb': 1494, 'question': 'Jiyan', 'answer': 'Niece', 'options': ['Sandwich', 'Fine', 'Old', 'Niece']} ,

{'numb': 1495, 'question': 'Nigeriyalik', 'answer': 'Nigerian', 'options': ['Nigerian', 'Lightning', 'Download', 'Arrive']} ,

{'numb': 1496, 'question': 'Pokiston', 'answer': 'Pakistani', 'options': ['Heavy', 'Climate', 'Pakistani', 'Get']} ,

{'numb': 1497, 'question': 'Polyak', 'answer': 'Polish', 'options': ['Collection', 'Read', 'Paint', 'Polish']} ,

{'numb': 1498, 'question': 'Portugal', 'answer': 'Portuguese', 'options': ['Portuguese', 'Retired', 'Who', 'For me']} ,

{'numb': 1499, 'question': 'Restarant', 'answer': 'Restaurant', 'options': ['Restaurant', 'Jeans', 'Carpet', 'Turn']} ,

{'numb': 1500, 'question': 'Rus', 'answer': 'Russian', 'options': ['November', 'Cancer', 'Russian', 'Above']} ,

{'numb': 1501, 'question': 'Saksafon', 'answer': 'Saxophone', 'options': ['Chance career', 'Now', 'Magazine', 'Saxophone']} ,

{'numb': 1502, 'question': 'Yagona', 'answer': 'Single', 'options': ['Boiled', 'Creative', 'Single', 'Mess']} ,

{'numb': 1503, 'question': 'Singil', 'answer': 'Sister', 'options': ['Tagine', 'Cancer', 'Sister', 'Too']} ,

{'numb': 1504, 'question': 'Ogil', 'answer': 'Son', 'options': ['Chance', 'Marathon', 'Touch', 'Son']} ,

{'numb': 1505, 'question': 'Ispan', 'answer': 'Spanish', 'options': ['Map', 'Spanish', 'Partner', 'Interested in']} ,

{'numb': 1506, 'question': 'Ogay ota', 'answer': 'Stepfather', 'options': ['Ice cream', 'Yellow', 'Stepfather', 'Cup']} ,

{'numb': 1507, 'question': 'Supermarket', 'answer': 'Supermarket', 'options': ['Supermarket', 'Password', 'Interest', 'Quickly']} ,

{'numb': 1508, 'question': 'Turk', 'answer': 'Turkish', 'options': ['Cruel', 'Worse', 'Alone', 'Turkish']} ,

{'numb': 1509, 'question': 'Egizak', 'answer': 'Twin', 'options': ['Work long hours', 'Horse', 'Twin', 'The day before yesterday']} ,

{'numb': 1510, 'question': 'Tipik', 'answer': 'Typical', 'options': ['Too', 'Period', 'Parking space', 'Typical']} ,

{'numb': 1511, 'question': 'Amaki', 'answer': 'Uncle', 'options': ['Walk', 'Uncle', 'Jar', 'Safe']} ,

{'numb': 1512, 'question': 'Ishsiz', 'answer': 'Unemployed', 'options': ['At the weekend', 'Travel', 'Unemployed', 'Never']} ,

{'numb': 1513, 'question': 'Urdu', 'answer': 'Urdu', 'options': ['Urdu', 'Mark', 'Interesting', 'Kilogramm']} ,

{'numb': 1514, 'question': 'Vetnam', 'answer': 'Vietnamese', 'options': ['Vietnamese', 'Strength', 'Listen', 'Ferry']} ,

{'numb': 1515, 'question': 'Xotin', 'answer': 'Wife', 'options': ['Tie', 'Wife', 'Squirrel', 'Good bye']} ,

{'numb': 1516, 'question': 'Fikriga qoshilmoq', 'answer': 'Agree', 'options': ['Several', 'Artist', 'Go to bed', 'Agree']} ,

{'numb': 1517, 'question': 'Yolgiz', 'answer': 'Alone', 'options': ['Backpack', 'Stick', 'Bored', 'Alone']} ,

{'numb': 1518, 'question': 'Sorang', 'answer': 'Ask', 'options': ['Ask', 'Say', 'Area', 'History']} ,

{'numb': 1519, 'question': 'Astronavt', 'answer': 'Astronaut', 'options': ['Nightmare', 'Astronaut', 'Takeof', 'On theinternet']} ,

{'numb': 1520, 'question': 'Plyaj', 'answer': 'Beach', 'options': ['Spice', 'In', 'Save up', 'Beach']} ,

{'numb': 1521, 'question': 'Tana soati', 'answer': 'Body clock', 'options': ['Body clock', 'Tired', 'Fascinated', 'Electronics shop']} ,

{'numb': 1522, 'question': 'Tanaffus', 'answer': 'Break', 'options': ['Small', 'Condition', 'Break', 'Hate']} ,

{'numb': 1523, 'question': 'Nonushta', 'answer': 'Breakfast', 'options': ['Just', 'Breakfast', 'Adopt', 'Spring']} ,

{'numb': 1524, 'question': 'Oshxona', 'answer': 'Canteen', 'options': ['Statue', 'Married', 'Rainforest', 'Canteen']} ,

{'numb': 1525, 'question': 'Don', 'answer': 'Cereal', 'options': ['Season', 'Beach', 'Accent', 'Cereal']} ,

{'numb': 1526, 'question': 'Sinf', 'answer': 'Class', 'options': ['Air', 'Class', 'Bakerãšâ¼s', 'Famous']} ,

{'numb': 1527, 'question': 'Xavfli', 'answer': 'Dangerous', 'options': ['Collection', 'Although', 'Take off', 'Dangerous']} ,

{'numb': 1528, 'question': 'Iflos', 'answer': 'Dirty', 'options': ['Bored', 'Dirty', 'Put on', 'Mine']} ,

{'numb': 1529, 'question': 'Chegirma', 'answer': 'Discount', 'options': ['Scientist', 'Trousers', 'Discount', 'Meeting']} ,

{'numb': 1530, 'question': 'Mutaxassis', 'answer': 'Expert', 'options': ['Course', 'Alone', 'Expert', 'Comics']} ,

{'numb': 1531, 'question': 'Korish', 'answer': 'Eyesight', 'options': ['Eyesight', 'Pollution', 'Advice', 'In late twenties']} ,

{'numb': 1532, 'question': 'Yaxshi his qilish', 'answer': 'Feel well', 'options': ['Number', 'Work freelance', 'Feel well', 'Share']} ,

{'numb': 1533, 'question': 'Ozod', 'answer': 'Free', 'options': ['Client', 'Hard', 'Each other', 'Free']} ,

{'numb': 1534, 'question': 'Bosh vaqt', 'answer': 'Free time', 'options': ['Free time', 'Scientific', 'Why', 'Calmly']} ,

{'numb': 1535, 'question': 'Toza havo', 'answer': 'Fresh air', 'options': ['April', 'Fresh air', 'Smart', 'Dog']} ,

{'numb': 1536, 'question': 'Bormoq', 'answer': 'Go', 'options': ['Stress', 'Parents', 'Maiden name', 'Go']} ,

{'numb': 1537, 'question': 'Klubga borish', 'answer': 'Go clubbing', 'options': ['Pet', 'Envelope', 'Go clubbing', 'Brush']} ,

{'numb': 1538, 'question': 'Yarim otdi', 'answer': 'Half past', 'options': ['Several', 'Expensive', 'Area', 'Half past']} ,

{'numb': 1539, 'question': 'Kechki ovqat', 'answer': 'Have dinner', 'options': ['Son', 'Update', 'Now', 'Have dinner']} ,

{'numb': 1540, 'question': 'Tushlik qiling', 'answer': 'Have lunch', 'options': ['Have lunch', 'Postcard', 'Electronics shop', 'Cereal']} ,

{'numb': 1541, 'question': 'Och', 'answer': 'Hungry', 'options': ['Comb', 'Good bye', 'Chin', 'Hungry']} ,

{'numb': 1542, 'question': 'Fikr', 'answer': 'Idea', 'options': ['Idea', 'Economics', 'Next', 'Nervous']} ,

{'numb': 1543, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Journey', 'options': ['Running', 'Tired', 'Journey', 'This']} ,

{'numb': 1544, 'question': 'Laboratoriya', 'answer': 'Lab', 'options': ['Lab', 'Hand', 'Telephone', 'Shine']} ,

{'numb': 1545, 'question': 'Tingla', 'answer': 'Listen', 'options': ['Videocamera', 'Garlic', 'Nationality', 'Listen']} ,

{'numb': 1546, 'question': 'Uchrashish', 'answer': 'Meeting', 'options': ['Hello', 'Meeting', 'Washing machine', 'Crowded']} ,

{'numb': 1547, 'question': 'Shovqinli', 'answer': 'Noisy', 'options': ['Rise', 'Achievement', 'Waterfall', 'Noisy']} ,

{'numb': 1548, 'question': 'Tashqarida', 'answer': 'Outside', 'options': ['Outside', 'Lonely', 'Hood', 'Ban']} ,

{'numb': 1549, 'question': 'Tolash', 'answer': 'Pay', 'options': ['Pay', 'Far', 'Usual', 'Fast lane']} ,

{'numb': 1550, 'question': 'Pingvin', 'answer': 'Penguin', 'options': ['Dessert', 'Yard', 'Airline', 'Penguin']} ,

{'numb': 1551, 'question': 'Mukammal', 'answer': 'Perfect', 'options': ['Running', 'Somebody', 'Perfect', 'Tongue']} ,

{'numb': 1552, 'question': 'Jismoniy', 'answer': 'Physical', 'options': ['October', 'Have lunch', 'Physical', 'Expensive']} ,

{'numb': 1553, 'question': 'Reja', 'answer': 'Plan', 'options': ['Book', 'Desicion', 'Fruit', 'Plan']} ,

{'numb': 1554, 'question': 'Professor', 'answer': 'Professor', 'options': ['Heater', 'Professor', 'Yogurt', 'Guy']} ,

{'numb': 1555, 'question': 'Jamoat transporti', 'answer': 'Public transport', 'options': ['Work in the garden', 'Public transport', 'Boss', 'Nurse']} ,

{'numb': 1556, 'question': 'Chorak otgan', 'answer': 'Quarter past', 'options': ['Can', 'Quarter past', 'Fine', 'Economy']} ,

{'numb': 1557, 'question': 'Chorakgacha', 'answer': 'Quarter to', 'options': ['Young', 'Say', 'Calmly', 'Quarter to']} ,

{'numb': 1558, 'question': 'Oqimoq', 'answer': 'Read', 'options': ['Amazing', 'Messy', 'Between', 'Read']} ,

{'numb': 1559, 'question': 'Javob bermoq', 'answer': 'Reply', 'options': ['Newspaper', 'Indian', 'Reply', 'Alphabet']} ,

{'numb': 1560, 'question': 'Kotarilish', 'answer': 'Rise', 'options': ['Pedestrian area', 'Rise', 'Fine', 'Listen to music']} ,

{'numb': 1561, 'question': 'Sendvich', 'answer': 'Sandwich', 'options': ['Advantages', 'Tourist', 'Bank account', 'Sandwich']} ,

{'numb': 1562, 'question': 'Ilmiy', 'answer': 'Scientific', 'options': ['Scientific', 'Swimming pool', 'Office', 'Masters degree']} ,

{'numb': 1563, 'question': 'Olim', 'answer': 'Scientist', 'options': ['Border', 'Scientist', 'Crucial', 'Airline']} ,

{'numb': 1564, 'question': 'Muhr', 'answer': 'Seal', 'options': ['Computer game', 'Friend', 'Your', 'Seal']} ,

{'numb': 1565, 'question': 'Dokon', 'answer': 'Shop', 'options': ['Hotel', 'Clock', 'Shop', 'Goal']} ,

{'numb': 1566, 'question': 'Dush', 'answer': 'Shower', 'options': ['Desicion', 'Meaning', 'Shower', 'Roof']} ,

{'numb': 1567, 'question': 'Kasallik', 'answer': 'Sickness', 'options': ['Photograph', 'Sickness', 'Great britain', 'Literature']} ,

{'numb': 1568, 'question': 'Qopkorpa', 'answer': 'Sleeping bag', 'options': ['Father', 'Sleeping bag', 'Holiday', 'Fascinated']} ,

{'numb': 1569, 'question': 'Shorva', 'answer': 'Soup', 'options': ['Nephew', 'Down', 'Soup', 'Orange']} ,

{'numb': 1570, 'question': 'Bosh joy', 'answer': 'Space', 'options': ['Cabbage', 'Body', 'Space', 'Bank account']} ,

{'numb': 1571, 'question': 'Skafandr', 'answer': 'Spacesuit', 'options': ['Get merried', 'Capsule', 'Capital', 'Spacesuit']} ,

{'numb': 1572, 'question': 'Boshlash', 'answer': 'Start', 'options': ['Fence', 'Revolution', 'Start', 'Wasteful']} ,

{'numb': 1573, 'question': 'Toxta', 'answer': 'Stop', 'options': ['Friendly', 'Stop', 'Beautiful', 'South korea']} ,

{'numb': 1574, 'question': 'Talaba kartasi', 'answer': 'Student card', 'options': ['Ingredient', 'Newspaper', 'Still', 'Student card']} ,

{'numb': 1575, 'question': 'Oylash', 'answer': 'Think', 'options': ['Explain', 'Think', 'Hi', 'Bark']} ,

{'numb': 1576, 'question': 'Charchagan', 'answer': 'Tired', 'options': ['Journey', 'Cup', 'Chat', 'Tired']} ,

{'numb': 1577, 'question': 'Sarlavha', 'answer': 'Title', 'options': ['Headache', 'Take care of', 'Thunder', 'Title']} ,

{'numb': 1578, 'question': 'Tushdi', 'answer': 'Toast', 'options': ['Development', 'Enthusiastic', 'Toast', 'Sociable']} ,

{'numb': 1579, 'question': 'Stajyor', 'answer': 'Trainee', 'options': ['Code', 'Trainee', 'Banana', 'Australia']} ,

{'numb': 1580, 'question': 'Vulqon', 'answer': 'Volcano', 'options': ['Building', 'Lunch', 'Volcano', 'Red']} ,

{'numb': 1581, 'question': 'Kutmoq', 'answer': 'Wait', 'options': ['Visitor', 'Solution', 'Wait', 'Economics']} ,

{'numb': 1582, 'question': 'Uygoning', 'answer': 'Wake up', 'options': ['Coffee', 'Wake up', 'Arrive', 'Wasteful']} ,

{'numb': 1583, 'question': 'Yaxshi', 'answer': 'Well', 'options': ['Well', 'Purse', 'Impatient', 'Experiment']} ,

{'numb': 1584, 'question': 'Film tomosha qiling', 'answer': 'Watch a film', 'options': ['Red', 'Effort', 'Again', 'Watch a film']} ,

{'numb': 1585, 'question': 'Tv korish', 'answer': 'Watch tv', 'options': ['Mix', 'Debt', 'Watch tv', 'Win']} ,

{'numb': 1586, 'question': 'Zoologiya', 'answer': 'Zoology', 'options': ['Worried', 'Shoulder', 'Zoology', 'Online']} ,

{'numb': 1587, 'question': 'Manzil', 'answer': 'Address', 'options': ['Steering wheel', 'Just', 'Ear', 'Address']} ,

{'numb': 1588, 'question': 'Aviakompaniya', 'answer': 'Airline', 'options': ['Comb', 'Airline', 'Souvenir seller', 'Learn to swim']} ,

{'numb': 1589, 'question': 'Muallif', 'answer': 'Author', 'options': ['Field', 'First name', 'Comics', 'Author']} ,

{'numb': 1590, 'question': 'Javob', 'answer': 'Answer', 'options': ['Sauce', 'Ship', 'Answer', 'Rich']} ,

{'numb': 1591, 'question': 'Nonvoy', 'answer': 'Baker', 'options': ['Cloudy', 'Headphones', 'Party', 'Baker']} ,

{'numb': 1592, 'question': 'Boshlovchi', 'answer': 'Beginner', 'options': ['Magazine', 'Beginner', 'Gues house', 'Pizza']} ,

{'numb': 1593, 'question': 'Quruvchi', 'answer': 'Builder', 'options': ['Builder', 'Petrol', 'Miss', 'Group']} ,

{'numb': 1594, 'question': 'Aftobus haydovchisi', 'answer': 'Bus driver', 'options': ['Tiring', 'Why', 'Accommodation', 'Bus driver']} ,

{'numb': 1595, 'question': 'Biznesmen (erkak)', 'answer': 'Businessman', 'options': ['Quickly', 'Businessman', 'Mustache', 'Cent']} ,

{'numb': 1596, 'question': 'Biznesmen (ayol)', 'answer': 'Businesswoman', 'options': ['Businesswoman', 'Nightmare', 'Good', 'High speed']} ,

{'numb': 1597, 'question': 'Sokin', 'answer': 'Calm', 'options': ['Around', 'Calm', 'Arrive', 'Professor']} ,

{'numb': 1598, 'question': 'Oshpaz', 'answer': 'Chef', 'options': ['Mark', 'Experience', 'Chef', 'False']} ,

{'numb': 1599, 'question': 'Tozalovchi', 'answer': 'Cleaner', 'options': ['Become', 'Window', 'Cleaner', 'Economy']} ,

{'numb': 1600, 'question': 'Aqlli', 'answer': 'Clever', 'options': ['Cheek', 'Clever', 'Classroom', 'Exhausted']} ,

{'numb': 1601, 'question': 'Hamkasb', 'answer': 'Colleague', 'options': ['Record', 'Vending machine', 'Colleague', 'Per']} ,

{'numb': 1602, 'question': 'Kompaniya', 'answer': 'Company', 'options': ['Those', 'Company', 'Magazine', 'Pair']} ,

{'numb': 1603, 'question': 'Raqqos', 'answer': 'Dancer', 'options': ['Aunt', 'False', 'Package', 'Dancer']} ,

{'numb': 1604, 'question': 'Tish shifokori', 'answer': 'Dentist', 'options': ['Fascinated', 'Easy', 'Dentist', 'Have to']} ,

{'numb': 1605, 'question': 'Havdovchi', 'answer': 'Driver', 'options': ['Driver', 'Come', 'Get dressed', 'Notepad']} ,

{'numb': 1606, 'question': 'Zavod', 'answer': 'Factory', 'options': ['Piece', 'Saturday', 'Aunt', 'Factory']} ,

{'numb': 1607, 'question': 'Fermer', 'answer': 'Fermer', 'options': ['Fermer', 'Pen', 'Instructions', 'Author']} ,

{'numb': 1608, 'question': 'Tuzatish', 'answer': 'Fix', 'options': ['Ocean', 'Special', 'Railway', 'Fix']} ,

{'numb': 1609, 'question': 'Oãšâ»rmon', 'answer': 'Forest', 'options': ['Buy', 'Casual', 'Forest', 'Backpack']} ,

{'numb': 1610, 'question': 'Unutmoq', 'answer': 'Forget', 'options': ['Gallant', 'Exit', 'Congratulate', 'Forget']} ,

{'numb': 1611, 'question': 'Sartarosh', 'answer': 'Hairdresser', 'options': ['Sparklingwater', 'Hairdresser', 'Married', 'Comb']} ,

{'numb': 1612, 'question': 'Muhim', 'answer': 'Important', 'options': ['Important', 'Island', 'Meal', 'Ready']} ,

{'numb': 1613, 'question': 'Ichida', 'answer': 'Inside', 'options': ['Inside', 'Lose', 'Call', 'Reading glasses']} ,

{'numb': 1614, 'question': 'Jurnalist', 'answer': 'Journalist', 'options': ['Journalist', 'Lie', 'Run', 'Advice']} ,

{'numb': 1615, 'question': 'Keyinroq', 'answer': 'Later', 'options': ['Amazed', 'Eyebrow', 'Worker', 'Later']} ,

{'numb': 1616, 'question': 'Yolgiz', 'answer': 'Lonely', 'options': ['Lonely', 'Speed', 'Best selling', 'Goldfish']} ,

{'numb': 1617, 'question': 'Blokirovka', 'answer': 'Lockout', 'options': ['Euro', 'Certainly', 'Day', 'Lockout']} ,

{'numb': 1618, 'question': 'Omadli', 'answer': 'Lucky', 'options': ['Lucky', 'Musician', 'Must', 'The uk']} ,

{'numb': 1619, 'question': 'Jurnal', 'answer': 'Magazine', 'options': ['Quarter past', 'Napkin', 'Refund', 'Magazine']} ,

{'numb': 1620, 'question': 'Menejer', 'answer': 'Manager', 'options': ['Nobody', 'Manager', 'Eggplant', 'Love']} ,

{'numb': 1621, 'question': 'Pul', 'answer': 'Money', 'options': ['Agree', 'Money', 'House', 'Literature']} ,

{'numb': 1622, 'question': 'Mp3 pleer', 'answer': 'Mp3 player', 'options': ['Development', 'His', 'Mp3 player', 'Outside']} ,

{'numb': 1623, 'question': 'Musiqachi', 'answer': 'Musician', 'options': ['Health', 'Musician', 'A cup of', 'Lucky']} ,

{'numb': 1624, 'question': 'Hamshira', 'answer': 'Nurse', 'options': ['Perfect', 'Partner', 'Nurse', 'Paper']} ,

{'numb': 1625, 'question': 'Ofis xodimi', 'answer': 'Office worker', 'options': ['Office worker', 'Wake up', 'Repellent', 'Spacesuit']} ,

{'numb': 1626, 'question': 'Rassom', 'answer': 'Painter', 'options': ['Painter', 'Read', 'Wife', 'Soul']} ,

{'numb': 1627, 'question': 'Pianino', 'answer': 'Piano', 'options': ['Quietly', 'Smartly', 'Math', 'Piano']} ,

{'numb': 1628, 'question': 'Uchuvchi', 'answer': 'Pilot', 'options': ['Development', 'Elephant', 'Pilot', 'Ban']} ,

{'numb': 1629, 'question': 'Ish joyi', 'answer': 'Place of work', 'options': ['Garage', 'Equal', 'Place of work', 'Trip']} ,

{'numb': 1630, 'question': 'Militsiya hodimi', 'answer': 'Police officer', 'options': ['Police officer', 'Currency', 'Dining room', 'Prise']} ,

{'numb': 1631, 'question': 'Nafaqaga chiqqan', 'answer': 'Retired', 'options': ['Lovely', 'Retired', 'Vacant', 'Explain']} ,

{'numb': 1632, 'question': 'Ish haqi', 'answer': 'Salary', 'options': ['Lie in', 'Salary', 'Prise', 'Stall']} ,

{'numb': 1633, 'question': 'Jim', 'answer': 'Silent', 'options': ['Silent', 'Plane', 'Hire', 'House']} ,

{'numb': 1634, 'question': 'Ashulachi', 'answer': 'Singer', 'options': ['Singer', 'Great britain', 'House', 'The day before yesterday']} ,

{'numb': 1635, 'question': 'Talaba', 'answer': 'Student', 'options': ['Student', 'Apartment', 'Even', 'Stress']} ,

{'numb': 1636, 'question': 'Chipta', 'answer': 'Ticket', 'options': ['Cheap', 'Wind', 'Behaviour', 'Ticket']} ,

{'numb': 1637, 'question': 'Minora', 'answer': 'Tower', 'options': ['See', 'Tower', 'Talk', 'Discuss']} ,

{'numb': 1638, 'question': 'Forma', 'answer': 'Uniform', 'options': ['Uniform', 'Start', 'Progress', 'Chips']} ,

{'numb': 1639, 'question': 'Gayrioddiy', 'answer': 'Unusual', 'options': ['Student accommodation', 'Vacation', 'Lovely', 'Unusual']} ,

{'numb': 1640, 'question': 'Yaxshi tolangan', 'answer': 'Well-paid', 'options': ['Review', 'Early', 'Well-paid', 'Karate']} ,

{'numb': 1641, 'question': 'Golib', 'answer': 'Winner', 'options': ['Winner', 'Massive', 'Good', 'Small']} ,

{'numb': 1642, 'question': 'Mustaqil ishlash', 'answer': 'Work freelance', 'options': ['Record', 'Tram', 'Stepfather', 'Work freelance']} ,

{'numb': 1643, 'question': 'Uzoq vaqt ishlash', 'answer': 'Work long hours', 'options': ['Student card', 'Work long hours', 'Emotion', 'Navigation']} ,

{'numb': 1644, 'question': 'Yozuvchi', 'answer': 'Writer', 'options': ['Daughter', 'A bit', 'Writer', 'Stop']} ,

{'numb': 1645, 'question': 'Dangasa', 'answer': 'Lazy', 'options': ['Divorced', 'Lazy', 'Vase', 'Comment']} ,

{'numb': 1646, 'question': 'Kutubxona', 'answer': 'Library', 'options': ['Celebrate', 'Library', 'Watch', 'Subtropical']} ,

{'numb': 1647, 'question': 'Yoruglik', 'answer': 'Light', 'options': ['Unlucky', 'Hoodie', 'Light', 'Education']} ,

{'numb': 1648, 'question': 'Tartibsiz', 'answer': 'Messy', 'options': ['Advantages', 'Equip', 'Messy', 'Myth']} ,

{'numb': 1649, 'question': 'Meniki', 'answer': 'Mine', 'options': ['Serious', 'Finish', 'Mine', 'Mosquito']} ,

{'numb': 1650, 'question': 'Muzey', 'answer': 'Museum', 'options': ['Border', 'Careful', 'Shoulder', 'Museum']} ,

{'numb': 1651, 'question': 'Yonidagi', 'answer': 'Next to', 'options': ['Mirror', 'Sparklingwater', 'Fish', 'Next to']} ,

{'numb': 1652, 'question': 'Opal', 'answer': 'Opal', 'options': ['Toothpaste', 'Transport', 'Interested in', 'Opal']} ,

{'numb': 1653, 'question': 'Tashkil etilgan', 'answer': 'Organized', 'options': ['Apply', 'Lamp', 'Organized', 'Extrovert']} ,

{'numb': 1654, 'question': 'Saroy', 'answer': 'Palace', 'options': ['Designer', 'Palace', 'Who', 'Soap']} ,

{'numb': 1655, 'question': 'Pasport', 'answer': 'Passport', 'options': ['Unkind', 'Goal', 'Passport', 'Bus pass']} ,

{'numb': 1656, 'question': 'Politsiya idorasi', 'answer': 'Post office', 'options': ['Wife', 'During', 'Post office', 'Greener']} ,

{'numb': 1657, 'question': 'Temir yol stansiyasi', 'answer': 'Railway station', 'options': ['Argentina', 'Railway station', 'Tower', 'Carton']} ,

{'numb': 1658, 'question': 'Chokmoq', 'answer': 'Sink', 'options': ['Piece', 'Jewellery', 'Start', 'Sink']} ,

{'numb': 1659, 'question': 'Studiya kvartirasi', 'answer': 'Studio flat', 'options': ['Promise', 'Studio flat', 'Wood', 'This evening']} ,

{'numb': 1660, 'question': 'Suzish havzasi', 'answer': 'Swimming pool', 'options': ['Swimming pool', 'Event', 'Text', 'Feature']} ,

{'numb': 1661, 'question': 'Dahshatli', 'answer': 'Terrible', 'options': ['Souvenir', 'Fermer', 'Center', 'Terrible']} ,

{'numb': 1662, 'question': 'Teatr', 'answer': 'Theatre', 'options': ['Colleague', 'Computer game', 'Theatre', 'Ruins']} ,

{'numb': 1663, 'question': 'Toza', 'answer': 'Tidy', 'options': ['Fist', 'Our', 'Tidy', 'Too']} ,

{'numb': 1664, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Tour', 'options': ['Tour', 'Happiness', 'Finger', 'Excited']} ,

{'numb': 1665, 'question': 'Turist', 'answer': 'Tourist', 'options': ['Shocking', 'Tourist', 'Indonesia', 'Forest']} ,

{'numb': 1666, 'question': 'Turistik axborot markazi', 'answer': 'Tourist information centre', 'options': ['Father in law', 'Score', 'Tourist information centre', 'Painter']} ,

{'numb': 1667, 'question': 'Shahar', 'answer': 'Town', 'options': ['Town', 'Chin', 'Running', 'Fluently']} ,

{'numb': 1668, 'question': 'Xunuk', 'answer': 'Ugly', 'options': ['Cleaner', 'Underwear', 'Active', 'Ugly']} ,

{'numb': 1669, 'question': 'Yer osti', 'answer': 'Underground', 'options': ['Underground', 'Swap', 'Film', 'Debt']} ,

{'numb': 1670, 'question': 'Tashrif buyurmoq', 'answer': 'Visit', 'options': ['Team', 'State school', 'Curd', 'Visit']} ,

{'numb': 1671, 'question': 'Kir yuvish mashinasi', 'answer': 'Washing machine', 'options': ['Washing machine', 'Physical', 'Chips', 'Garage']} ,

{'numb': 1672, 'question': 'Ozgina', 'answer': 'A bit', 'options': ['In a good mood', 'A bit', 'Sleep', 'Disease']} ,

{'numb': 1673, 'question': 'Bobsley', 'answer': 'Bobsleigh', 'options': ['Bear', 'Horse', 'Bobsleigh', 'Fly']} ,

{'numb': 1674, 'question': 'Sinfxona', 'answer': 'Classroom', 'options': ['Get', 'Classroom', 'Public transport', 'Toe']} ,

{'numb': 1675, 'question': 'Tolamoq', 'answer': 'Collect', 'options': ['Collect', 'Prepare', 'Plan', 'Solution']} ,

{'numb': 1676, 'question': 'Kod', 'answer': 'Code', 'options': ['Myth', 'Change', 'Code', 'Boil']} ,

{'numb': 1677, 'question': 'Moda dizayneri', 'answer': 'Fashion designer', 'options': ['Fashion designer', 'Consequence', 'Bag', 'Journey']} ,

{'numb': 1678, 'question': 'Asoschi', 'answer': 'Founder', 'options': ['Founder', 'Especially', 'Behind', 'Email']} ,

{'numb': 1679, 'question': 'Konkida uchish', 'answer': 'Ice skater', 'options': ['River', 'Indonesia', 'Ice skater', 'Frozen']} ,

{'numb': 1680, 'question': 'Qiziqarli', 'answer': 'Interesting', 'options': ['After school', 'Urdu', 'Arrive', 'Interesting']} ,

{'numb': 1681, 'question': 'Yorliq', 'answer': 'Label', 'options': ['Sports', 'Fare', 'Label', 'Practical skills']} ,

{'numb': 1682, 'question': 'Zamonaviy sanat', 'answer': 'Modern art', 'options': ['Scissors', 'Cheap', 'Boil', 'Modern art']} ,

{'numb': 1683, 'question': 'Shox', 'answer': 'Naughty', 'options': ['Name', 'Naughty', 'Musician', 'Bathroom']} ,

{'numb': 1684, 'question': 'Sezmoq', 'answer': 'Notice', 'options': ['Thank', 'Several', 'Happen', 'Notice']} ,

{'numb': 1685, 'question': 'Mashhur', 'answer': 'Popular', 'options': ['Through', 'Stick', 'Popular', 'Chess']} ,

{'numb': 1686, 'question': 'Tayyorlamoq', 'answer': 'Prepare', 'options': ['Prepare', 'Put', 'Log on', 'Active']} ,

{'numb': 1687, 'question': 'Mahsulot', 'answer': 'Product', 'options': ['Suchã‚', 'Product', 'Tenth', 'On']} ,

{'numb': 1688, 'question': 'Juda', 'answer': 'Quite', 'options': ['Hoodie', 'Quite', 'Electronics shop', 'Tobacco']} ,

{'numb': 1689, 'question': 'Olmoq', 'answer': 'Receive', 'options': ['Receive', 'Above', 'Purse', 'Play area']} ,

{'numb': 1690, 'question': 'Qaytarish', 'answer': 'Return', 'options': ['Scientist', 'Place', 'Bathroom', 'Return']} ,

{'numb': 1691, 'question': 'Hayqiriq', 'answer': 'Shout', 'options': ['Thick', 'Eighth', 'Sorry', 'Shout']} ,

{'numb': 1692, 'question': 'Omadli', 'answer': 'Successful', 'options': ['Successful', 'Chips', 'Warm', 'Week']} ,

{'numb': 1693, 'question': 'Rahmat', 'answer': 'Thank', 'options': ['Chief', 'Thank', 'Actress', 'Introduce']} ,

{'numb': 1694, 'question': 'Juda', 'answer': 'Very', 'options': ['Apartment', 'Space', 'Answer', 'Very']} ,

{'numb': 1695, 'question': 'Xohlamoq', 'answer': 'Want', 'options': ['Want', 'Married', 'Lovely', 'Fridge']} ,

{'numb': 1696, 'question': 'Ilova', 'answer': 'App', 'options': ['Ask', 'A cup of', 'Valuable', 'App']} ,

{'numb': 1697, 'question': 'Yengil atletika', 'answer': 'Athletics', 'options': ['Noodles', 'Focus', 'Take', 'Athletics']} ,

{'numb': 1698, 'question': 'Taqiqlamoq', 'answer': 'Ban', 'options': ['Ham', 'Website', 'Ban', 'Reader']} ,

{'numb': 1699, 'question': 'Basketbol', 'answer': 'Basketball', 'options': ['Twentieth', 'Keen', 'Basketball', 'Feel well']} ,

{'numb': 1700, 'question': 'Ichmoq', 'answer': 'Drink', 'options': ['Drink', 'Mess', 'Pull out', 'Designer']} ,

{'numb': 1701, 'question': 'Yemoq', 'answer': 'Eat', 'options': ['Italy', 'Today', 'Eat', 'Survive']} ,

{'numb': 1702, 'question': 'Mos', 'answer': 'Fit', 'options': ['On', 'Fit', 'Tower', 'Pull out']} ,

{'numb': 1703, 'question': 'Futbol', 'answer': 'Football', 'options': ['Bread', 'Fish', 'Football', 'Shawl']} ,

{'numb': 1704, 'question': 'Gadjet', 'answer': 'Gadget', 'options': ['Possible', 'Gadget', 'Facility', 'August']} ,

{'numb': 1705, 'question': 'Baliq ovlashga bormoq', 'answer': 'Go fishing', 'options': ['Great britain', 'Music', 'Go fishing', 'Sometimes']} ,

{'numb': 1706, 'question': 'Gimnastika zali', 'answer': 'Gym', 'options': ['Luggage', 'Gym', 'Go', 'Read to the news']} ,

{'numb': 1707, 'question': 'Qahramon', 'answer': 'Hero', 'options': ['Hero', 'Elephant', 'Stress', 'Have a baby']} ,

{'numb': 1708, 'question': 'Turtmoq', 'answer': 'Jog', 'options': ['Quarter to', 'Emirate', 'Jog', 'Grape']} ,

{'numb': 1709, 'question': 'Judon', 'answer': 'Judo', 'options': ['Paper clip', 'Judo', 'That', 'Bowler hat']} ,

{'numb': 1710, 'question': 'Qarz bermoq', 'answer': 'Lend', 'options': ['Emirate', 'Lend', 'Help', 'Finish school']} ,

{'numb': 1711, 'question': 'Kotarmoq', 'answer': 'Lift', 'options': ['But', 'Bright', 'Lift', 'Opposite']} ,

{'numb': 1712, 'question': 'Chaqmoq', 'answer': 'Lightning', 'options': ['Actor', 'Sister', 'Lightning', 'Be afraid of']} ,

{'numb': 1713, 'question': 'Mahalliy', 'answer': 'Local', 'options': ['Blouse', 'Salt', 'Local', 'Kindof']} ,

{'numb': 1714, 'question': 'Marafon', 'answer': 'Marathon', 'options': ['Strong', 'Ice skater', 'Flour', 'Marathon']} ,

{'numb': 1715, 'question': 'Mer', 'answer': 'Mayor', 'options': ['Mayor', 'Thin', 'Organization', 'Float']} ,

{'numb': 1716, 'question': 'Fikr', 'answer': 'Opinion', 'options': ['Strength', 'Statistic', 'Seventh', 'Opinion']} ,

{'numb': 1717, 'question': 'Jismoniy', 'answer': 'Physical', 'options': ['Physical', 'Around', 'Curd', 'Married']} ,

{'numb': 1718, 'question': 'Taraqqiyot', 'answer': 'Progress', 'options': ['Olives', 'Progress', 'Down', 'Elderly']} ,

{'numb': 1719, 'question': 'Qisqartirmoq', 'answer': 'Reduce', 'options': ['Belt', 'Reduce', 'Sell', 'Talk']} ,

{'numb': 1720, 'question': 'Nonvoyxona', 'answer': 'Bakerãšâ¼s', 'options': ['Student', 'Twelfth', 'Bakerãšâ¼s', 'Cash']} ,

{'numb': 1721, 'question': 'Zerikarli', 'answer': 'Boring', 'options': ['Economy', 'Boring', 'Biscuit', 'Photocopy']} ,

{'numb': 1722, 'question': 'Qassoblar', 'answer': 'Butcherãšâ¼s', 'options': ['Ruins', 'Flower stall', 'Languages', 'Butcherãšâ¼s']} ,

{'numb': 1723, 'question': 'Ehtiyotkor', 'answer': 'Careful', 'options': ['Careful', 'Advice', 'Account', 'Stressed']} ,

{'numb': 1724, 'question': 'Ehtiyotkorlik bilan', 'answer': 'Carefully', 'options': ['Carefully', 'Cake', 'Car mechanic', 'Massive']} ,

{'numb': 1725, 'question': 'Kiyim almashtirish xonasi', 'answer': 'Changing room', 'options': ['Body', 'Changing room', 'Song', 'Red']} ,

{'numb': 1726, 'question': 'Aniq', 'answer': 'Clear', 'options': ['Knowledge', 'Tropical', 'Clear', 'Lebanon']} ,

{'numb': 1727, 'question': 'Aniq', 'answer': 'Clearly', 'options': ['Niece', 'Clearly', 'Hot dog', 'Music']} ,

{'numb': 1728, 'question': 'Togri', 'answer': 'Correct', 'options': ['Anybody', 'Time', 'Ballon', 'Correct']} ,

{'numb': 1729, 'question': 'Togri', 'answer': 'Correctly', 'options': ['Clap', 'Correctly', 'Bowl', 'Athletic']} ,

{'numb': 1730, 'question': 'Xavfli', 'answer': 'Dangerously', 'options': ['Dangerously', 'Potatoes', 'Celebrate', 'Apply']} ,

{'numb': 1731, 'question': 'Dizayner poyabzali', 'answer': 'Designer shoes', 'options': ['Pe', 'Hot', 'Designer shoes', 'Special']} ,

{'numb': 1732, 'question': 'Hafsalasi pir boldi', 'answer': 'Disappointed', 'options': ['Word', 'Roof', 'Window', 'Disappointed']} ,

{'numb': 1733, 'question': 'Qolqop', 'answer': 'Gloves', 'options': ['Comics', 'Gloves', 'Toilet', 'Sink']} ,

{'numb': 1734, 'question': 'Yaxshi', 'answer': 'Good', 'options': ['Good', 'Passport', 'Bicycle', 'Pineapple']} ,

{'numb': 1735, 'question': 'Buyuk', 'answer': 'Great', 'options': ['Sneeze', 'Dollar', 'Great', 'Apricot']} ,

{'numb': 1736, 'question': 'Ogir', 'answer': 'Heavy', 'options': ['Chocolate', 'Say', 'Bookshop', 'Heavy']} ,

{'numb': 1737, 'question': 'Qaytarma qalpoqli kiyim', 'answer': 'Hoodie', 'options': ['Wedding', 'Free', 'Hoodie', 'Conversation']} ,

{'numb': 1738, 'question': 'Taqinchoq', 'answer': 'Jewellery', 'options': ['Foggy', 'Headphones', 'Humid', 'Jewellery']} ,

{'numb': 1739, 'question': 'Gazeta dokonlari', 'answer': 'Newsagentãšâ¼s', 'options': ['Shop', 'Newsagentãšâ¼s', 'Mountain', 'Black']} ,

{'numb': 1740, 'question': 'Onlayn', 'answer': 'Online', 'options': ['Nose', 'Disease', 'Online', 'Saucer']} ,

{'numb': 1741, 'question': 'Kambagal', 'answer': 'Poor', 'options': ['Love', 'Poor', 'Tomorrow', 'Monday']} ,

{'numb': 1742, 'question': 'Pochta varaqasi', 'answer': 'Postcard', 'options': ['Reply', 'Indoors', 'Postcard', 'Chair']} ,

{'numb': 1743, 'question': 'Sekin', 'answer': 'Quietly', 'options': ['Much', 'Notepad', 'Quietly', 'Thunder']} ,

{'numb': 1744, 'question': 'Yomgir suvi', 'answer': 'Rainwater', 'options': ['Rainwater', 'Watch', 'Bus', 'Soup']} ,

{'numb': 1745, 'question': 'Oqish kozoynaklari', 'answer': 'Reading glasses', 'options': ['Brother in law', 'Reading glasses', 'Hotel', 'Miracle']} ,

{'numb': 1746, 'question': 'Retsept', 'answer': 'Receipt', 'options': ['Mandarin', 'Message', 'Receipt', 'Few']} ,

{'numb': 1747, 'question': 'Tavsiya etmoq', 'answer': 'Recommend', 'options': ['Driver', 'Use', 'Track', 'Recommend']} ,

{'numb': 1748, 'question': 'Dam olish', 'answer': 'Relax', 'options': ['Stick', 'Travel', 'Relax', 'Active']} ,

{'numb': 1749, 'question': 'Sotish', 'answer': 'Sales', 'options': ['Chips', 'Department store', 'Sales', 'Soul']} ,

{'numb': 1750, 'question': 'Jiddiy', 'answer': 'Serious', 'options': ['Musician', 'Sneakers sport', 'Serious', 'Comb']} ,

{'numb': 1751, 'question': 'Savdo markazi', 'answer': 'Shopping centre', 'options': ['Quarter to', 'Philosophy', 'Shopping centre', 'Use']} ,

{'numb': 1752, 'question': 'Sekin', 'answer': 'Slowly', 'options': ['Slowly', 'Psychologist', 'Curry', 'Piece']} ,

{'numb': 1753, 'question': 'Paypoqlar', 'answer': 'Socks', 'options': ['Scooter', 'Chance', 'Dinner', 'Socks']} ,

{'numb': 1754, 'question': 'Kuchli', 'answer': 'Strong', 'options': ['Make things', 'Opal', 'Death', 'Strong']} ,

{'numb': 1755, 'question': 'Murabbiylar', 'answer': 'Trainers', 'options': ['Watch tv', 'Reliable', 'Trainers', 'Sand']} ,

{'numb': 1756, 'question': 'Shim', 'answer': 'Trousers', 'options': ['Fruit', 'Trousers', 'River', 'Bake']} ,

{'numb': 1757, 'question': 'Qiymat', 'answer': 'Value', 'options': ['Shy', 'Goal', 'Value', 'Location']} ,

{'numb': 1758, 'question': 'Savdo avtomati', 'answer': 'Vending machine', 'options': ['Thin', 'Country', 'Salad', 'Vending machine']} ,

{'numb': 1759, 'question': 'Virtual', 'answer': 'Virtual', 'options': ['Grass', 'Virtual', 'Coffee', 'Fashion']} ,

{'numb': 1760, 'question': 'Qiymat', 'answer': 'Worth', 'options': ['Typist', 'Present', 'Journalist', 'Worth']} ,

{'numb': 1761, 'question': 'Yuqorida', 'answer': 'Above', 'options': ['Condition', 'Although', 'Office', 'Above']} ,

{'numb': 1762, 'question': 'Aeroport', 'answer': 'Airport', 'options': ['Airport', 'Backpack', 'They', 'Public transport']} ,

{'numb': 1763, 'question': 'Kreslo', 'answer': 'Armchair', 'options': ['Best selling', 'Task', 'Armchair', 'Believein']} ,

{'numb': 1764, 'question': 'Bank', 'answer': 'Bank', 'options': ['Mild', 'Shop', 'Bank', 'Writer']} ,

{'numb': 1765, 'question': 'Hammom', 'answer': 'Bathroom', 'options': ['Debt', 'Bathroom', 'Body clock', 'Large']} ,

{'numb': 1766, 'question': 'Yotoq', 'answer': 'Bed', 'options': ['Bed', 'Subtropical', 'Grandmother', 'Concert hall']} ,

{'numb': 1767, 'question': 'Yotoqxona', 'answer': 'Bedroom', 'options': ['Refreshments', 'Bedroom', 'Blouse', 'Dessert']} ,

{'numb': 1768, 'question': 'Orqasida', 'answer': 'Behind', 'options': ['Behind', 'Forget', 'Backpack', 'Put on']} ,

{'numb': 1769, 'question': 'Orasida', 'answer': 'Between', 'options': ['Crucial', 'Italian', 'Meeting', 'Between']} ,

{'numb': 1770, 'question': 'Katta', 'answer': 'Big', 'options': ['Later', 'Big', 'Seat', 'Believe']} ,

{'numb': 1771, 'question': 'From', 'answer': 'Booking', 'options': ['Dancer', 'Booking', 'Tap', 'Parachute']} ,

{'numb': 1772, 'question': 'Poytaxt', 'answer': 'Capital', 'options': ['Ago', 'Capital', 'Traditional', 'Talk']} ,

{'numb': 1773, 'question': 'Gilam', 'answer': 'Carpet', 'options': ['Keep', 'Founder', 'Narrow', 'Carpet']} ,

{'numb': 1774, 'question': 'Arzon', 'answer': 'Cheap', 'options': ['Cheap', 'Note', 'Car', 'Experience']} ,

{'numb': 1775, 'question': 'Kimyogar', 'answer': 'Chemist', 'options': ['Chemist', 'Thirty first', 'Get up', 'First name']} ,

{'numb': 1776, 'question': 'Kino', 'answer': 'Cinema', 'options': ['Cinema', 'Wasteful', 'Angry', 'Try']} ,

{'numb': 1777, 'question': 'Toza', 'answer': 'Clean', 'options': ['Nephew', 'Clean', 'Amazing', 'Strawberry']} ,

{'numb': 1778, 'question': 'Pishirgich', 'answer': 'Cooker', 'options': ['Free parking', 'Fluent', 'Cooker', 'Safe']} ,

{'numb': 1779, 'question': 'Ovqatlanish joyi', 'answer': 'Dining room', 'options': ['Habit', 'Organized', 'Dining room', 'Successful']} ,

{'numb': 1780, 'question': 'Idish yuvish mashinasi', 'answer': 'Dishwasher', 'options': ['My', 'Diabetes', 'Climb', 'Dishwasher']} ,

{'numb': 1781, 'question': 'Qimmat', 'answer': 'Expensive', 'options': ['Timecapsule', 'Paint', 'Expensive', 'Social media']} ,

{'numb': 1782, 'question': 'Fantastik', 'answer': 'Fantastic', 'options': ['Soap', 'Advice', 'Data', 'Fantastic']} ,

{'numb': 1783, 'question': 'Nay', 'answer': 'Flut', 'options': ['Flut', 'Slow', 'Surface', 'Hug']} ,

{'numb': 1784, 'question': 'Muzlatgich', 'answer': 'Fridge', 'options': ['Cube', 'Fridge', 'Brazil', 'Tie']} ,

{'numb': 1785, 'question': 'Mebel', 'answer': 'Furniture', 'options': ['Destroy', 'Furniture', 'Fear', 'Document']} ,

{'numb': 1786, 'question': 'Garaj', 'answer': 'Garage', 'options': ['Nurse', 'This', 'Garage', 'Improve']} ,

{'numb': 1787, 'question': 'Sartaroshxona', 'answer': 'Hairdresserãšâ¼s', 'options': ['Vegetarian cookbook', 'Hairdresserãšâ¼s', 'Use', 'Friday']} ,

{'numb': 1788, 'question': 'Kasalxona', 'answer': 'Hospital', 'options': ['Predict', 'Flat', 'Tie', 'Hospital']} ,

{'numb': 1789, 'question': 'Uydosh', 'answer': 'Housemate', 'options': ['Consistof', 'Class', 'Housemate', 'Argument']} ,

{'numb': 1790, 'question': '...ning oldida', 'answer': 'In front of', 'options': ['Dark', 'Post', 'Box', 'In front of']} ,

{'numb': 1791, 'question': 'Korsatmalar', 'answer': 'Instructions', 'options': ['International', 'Cup', 'Instructions', 'Handshake']} ,

{'numb': 1792, 'question': 'Oshxona', 'answer': 'Kitchen', 'options': ['Jeans', 'Newspaper', 'Revolution', 'Kitchen']} ,

{'numb': 1793, 'question': 'Kir yuvishxona', 'answer': 'Launderette', 'options': ['Somebody', 'Difficult', 'Gallant', 'Launderette']} ,

{'numb': 1794, 'question': 'Moda', 'answer': 'Fashion', 'options': ['Apple juice', 'Around', 'Fashion', 'Move']} ,

{'numb': 1795, 'question': 'Zamonaviy', 'answer': 'Modern', 'options': ['Aunt', 'Modern', 'Business management', 'Change jobs']} ,

{'numb': 1796, 'question': 'Atletika', 'answer': 'Athletic', 'options': ['Athletic', 'Uncle', 'Battery', 'Behind']} ,

{'numb': 1797, 'question': 'Yoqotmoq', 'answer': 'Lose', 'options': ['Traffic lights', 'Lose', 'Benefit', 'Chin']} ,

{'numb': 1798, 'question': 'Qogoz qisqichi', 'answer': 'Paper clip', 'options': ['Garbage', 'Paper clip', 'Stockings', 'Plane']} ,

{'numb': 1799, 'question': 'Konditsionerli', 'answer': 'Air conditioned', 'options': ['After school', 'May', 'Unlucky', 'Air conditioned']} ,

{'numb': 1800, 'question': 'Hayratlanarli', 'answer': 'Amazing', 'options': ['Science', 'Amazing', 'Birth', 'Carpet']} ,

{'numb': 1801, 'question': 'Xovli', 'answer': 'Apartment', 'options': ['Apartment', 'Wind', 'Flower stall', 'Satellite dish']} ,

{'numb': 1802, 'question': 'Sanat galereyasi', 'answer': 'Art gallery', 'options': ['Shop assistant', 'Art gallery', 'Socks', 'Great']} ,

{'numb': 1803, 'question': 'Velosiped', 'answer': 'Bike', 'options': ['Similar', 'Battery', 'Nod', 'Bike']} ,

{'numb': 1804, 'question': 'Qishloq joy', 'answer': 'Countryside', 'options': ['Countryside', 'Watch', 'Chest', 'Crowded']} ,

{'numb': 1805, 'question': 'Madaniyat', 'answer': 'Culture', 'options': ['Bank', 'Life', 'Changing room', 'Culture']} ,

{'numb': 1806, 'question': 'Xodim', 'answer': 'Employee', 'options': ['Relax', 'Record', 'Take', 'Employee']} ,

{'numb': 1807, 'question': 'Muhit', 'answer': 'Environment', 'options': ['Tell', 'Environment', 'Behind', 'Train']} ,

{'numb': 1808, 'question': 'Aylanib chiqmoq', 'answer': 'Get around', 'options': ['Tights', 'Work long hours', 'Old', 'Get around']} ,

{'numb': 1809, 'question': 'Guruh', 'answer': 'Group', 'options': ['Excited', 'Group', 'Meeting', 'Father']} ,

{'numb': 1810, 'question': 'Mehmonxona', 'answer': 'Gues house', 'options': ['Gues house', 'Windy', 'Washing machine', 'Shirt']} ,

{'numb': 1811, 'question': 'Yolboshchi', 'answer': 'Guide', 'options': ['Guide', 'Put', 'Pie', 'Light']} ,

{'numb': 1812, 'question': 'Dubulga', 'answer': 'Helmet', 'options': ['Shiny', 'Helmet', 'Watch a film', 'Damp']} ,

{'numb': 1813, 'question': 'Aldamoq', 'answer': 'Lie', 'options': ['Baseball', 'Lie', 'Tomato', 'Shop online']} ,

{'numb': 1814, 'question': 'Yolovchi', 'answer': 'Passenger', 'options': ['Post', 'Jump', 'Compass', 'Passenger']} ,

{'numb': 1815, 'question': 'Platforma', 'answer': 'Platform', 'options': ['Platform', 'Impolite', 'Ride', 'History']} ,

{'numb': 1816, 'question': 'Navbat', 'answer': 'Queue', 'options': ['Curtain', 'Astronaut', 'Queue', 'Tower block']} ,

{'numb': 1817, 'question': 'Temir yol', 'answer': 'Railway', 'options': ['Pen', 'Artist', 'Online', 'Railway']} ,

{'numb': 1818, 'question': 'Yomgirli ormon', 'answer': 'Rainforest', 'options': ['Rainforest', 'Organize', 'Reviewer', 'Loud']} ,

{'numb': 1819, 'question': 'Ijara haqi', 'answer': 'Rent', 'options': ['Gentle', 'Sausage', 'Thought', 'Rent']} ,

{'numb': 1820, 'question': 'Xaroba', 'answer': 'Ruins', 'options': ['Ruins', 'Noun', 'Good quality', 'Junkfood']} ,

{'numb': 1821, 'question': 'Xavfsizlik kamari', 'answer': 'Seat belt', 'options': ['Discount', 'Road', 'Leader', 'Seat belt']} ,

{'numb': 1822, 'question': 'Non yopmoq', 'answer': 'Bake', 'options': ['Bake', 'Metal', 'Cafe', 'Unkind']} ,

{'numb': 1823, 'question': 'Qaynash', 'answer': 'Boil', 'options': ['Breakfast', 'Sales', 'Paint', 'Boil']} ,

{'numb': 1824, 'question': 'Kosa', 'answer': 'Bowl', 'options': ['Dress', 'Bowl', 'Mouse', 'Really']} ,

{'numb': 1825, 'question': 'Qasr', 'answer': 'Castle', 'options': ['Cardigan', 'Castle', 'From', 'Rag']} ,

{'numb': 1826, 'question': 'Kesmoq', 'answer': 'Chop', 'options': ['Pipe', 'Grandmother', 'Chop', 'Bank account']} ,

{'numb': 1827, 'question': 'Kub', 'answer': 'Cube', 'options': ['Cube', 'Greeting', 'Shiny', 'Kindof']} ,

{'numb': 1828, 'question': 'Mazali', 'answer': 'Delicious', 'options': ['Think', 'Garbage', 'Separate', 'Delicious']} ,

{'numb': 1829, 'question': 'Oziq-ovqat protsessori', 'answer': 'Food processor', 'options': ['Perhaps', 'Touch', 'Food processor', 'Fun']} ,

{'numb': 1830, 'question': 'Qovurmoq', 'answer': 'Fry', 'options': ['Depth', 'Melon', 'Brilliant', 'Fry']} ,

{'numb': 1831, 'question': 'Tova', 'answer': 'Frying pan', 'options': ['Mountain', 'Number', 'House sit', 'Frying pan']} ,

{'numb': 1832, 'question': 'Tarkib', 'answer': 'Ingredient', 'options': ['Meet', 'Ingredient', 'On time', 'Pie']} ,

{'numb': 1833, 'question': 'Murabbo', 'answer': 'Jam', 'options': ['Windowsill', 'Play area', 'Jam', 'Email']} ,

{'numb': 1834, 'question': 'Limonad', 'answer': 'Lemonade', 'options': ['Slow', 'Lemonade', 'Pipe', 'Ball']} ,

{'numb': 1835, 'question': 'Asosiy kurs', 'answer': 'Main course', 'options': ['Keyboard', 'Client', 'Main course', 'Behind']} ,

{'numb': 1836, 'question': 'Aralashish', 'answer': 'Mix', 'options': ['Helmet', 'Go to bed', 'Clear', 'Mix']} ,

{'numb': 1837, 'question': 'Oliviya', 'answer': 'Olive', 'options': ['Dark', 'Practical skills', 'Listen', 'Olive']} ,

{'numb': 1838, 'question': 'Makaron', 'answer': 'Pasta', 'options': ['Eleventh', 'Own', 'Pasta', 'Stepmother/father']} ,

{'numb': 1839, 'question': 'Tayyor', 'answer': 'Ready', 'options': ['Terrible', 'Ready', 'Elbow', 'Experiment']} ,

{'numb': 1840, 'question': 'Qovurilgan', 'answer': 'Roast', 'options': ['Roast', 'Ceiling', 'Rag', 'Check in']} ,

{'numb': 1841, 'question': 'Uyingizda', 'answer': 'Rooftop', 'options': ['Worried', 'Rooftop', 'Cards', 'Platform']} ,

{'numb': 1842, 'question': 'Idish', 'answer': 'Saucepan', 'options': ['Saucepan', 'Fine', 'Niece', 'Especially']} ,

{'numb': 1843, 'question': 'Boshlovchi', 'answer': 'Starter', 'options': ['Fitness', 'Starter', 'Since', 'In front of']} ,

{'numb': 1844, 'question': 'Tadqiqot', 'answer': 'Survey', 'options': ['Survey', 'Soap', 'Running nose', 'Purse']} ,

{'numb': 1845, 'question': 'Shirin bodroq', 'answer': 'Sweetcorn', 'options': ['Learn a new language', 'Sweetcorn', 'Opinion', 'Weather']} ,

{'numb': 1846, 'question': 'Olib ketiladigon taom', 'answer': 'Takeaway food', 'options': ['Special', 'Useby', 'Takeaway food', 'Class']} ,

{'numb': 1847, 'question': 'Nosoglom', 'answer': 'Unhealthy', 'options': ['Go on facebook', 'Hospital', 'Unhealthy', 'Nervous']} ,

{'numb': 1848, 'question': 'Qaramoq kormoq', 'answer': 'View', 'options': ['View', 'Colorful', 'Ban', 'Literature']} ,

{'numb': 1849, 'question': 'Ajablanmoq', 'answer': 'Wonderful', 'options': ['Dish', 'Development', 'Wonderful', 'Scooter']} ,

{'numb': 1850, 'question': 'Yogurt', 'answer': 'Yoghurt', 'options': ['Something', 'Painkiller', 'Yoghurt', 'Lie in']} ,

{'numb': 1851, 'question': 'Talaffuz', 'answer': 'Accent', 'options': ['Unlucky', 'Road', 'Passion', 'Accent']} ,

{'numb': 1852, 'question': 'Esmoq', 'answer': 'Blow', 'options': ['Forget', 'Blow', 'Candle', 'Guest']} ,

{'numb': 1853, 'question': 'Band', 'answer': 'Busy', 'options': ['Comb', 'Busy', 'Perhaps', 'Deal with']} ,

{'numb': 1854, 'question': 'Oromgoh', 'answer': 'Camp', 'options': ['Camp', 'Heater', 'Hot', 'Wallet']} ,

{'numb': 1855, 'question': 'Iqlim', 'answer': 'Climate', 'options': ['Climate', 'Fox', 'Possession', 'Fourth']} ,

{'numb': 1856, 'question': 'Bulutli', 'answer': 'Cloudy', 'options': ['Recently', 'Hungry', 'Cloudy', 'Lockout']} ,

{'numb': 1857, 'question': 'Kompas', 'answer': 'Compass', 'options': ['Compass', 'Perform', 'Pass your exams', 'Survive']} ,

{'numb': 1858, 'question': 'Jinni', 'answer': 'Crazy', 'options': ['Health', 'Cereal', 'Pan', 'Crazy']} ,

{'numb': 1859, 'question': 'Chuqur', 'answer': 'Deep', 'options': ['Pink', 'Different', 'Deep', 'Go out with friends']} ,

{'numb': 1860, 'question': 'Desert', 'answer': 'Dessert', 'options': ['There', 'Sun', 'Child', 'Dessert']} ,

{'numb': 1861, 'question': 'Quruq', 'answer': 'Dry', 'options': ['Customer', 'Decide', 'Dry', 'Bad manners']} ,

{'numb': 1862, 'question': 'Sharqiy', 'answer': 'East', 'options': ['East', 'Hello', 'Ask', 'Kettle']} ,

{'numb': 1863, 'question': 'Jihozlash', 'answer': 'Equipment', 'options': ['Orange', 'Reviewer', 'Equipment', 'Lose']} ,

{'numb': 1864, 'question': 'Tumanli', 'answer': 'Foggy', 'options': ['Physical', 'Doggybag', 'Foggy', 'Different']} ,

{'numb': 1865, 'question': 'Sovuq', 'answer': 'Freeze', 'options': ['Vase', 'Dangerous', 'Begin', 'Freeze']} ,

{'numb': 1866, 'question': 'Mehnatkash', 'answer': 'Hard worker', 'options': ['Shower', 'Touch', 'Forest', 'Hard worker']} ,

{'numb': 1867, 'question': 'Yuqori', 'answer': 'High', 'options': ['High', 'Condition', 'Ruler', 'Place']} ,

{'numb': 1868, 'question': 'Issiq', 'answer': 'Hot', 'options': ['Usual', 'Discount', 'Elbow', 'Hot']} ,

{'numb': 1869, 'question': 'Muzli', 'answer': 'Icy', 'options': ['Take care of', 'Icy', 'Smartly', 'South africa']} ,

{'numb': 1870, 'question': 'Orol', 'answer': 'Island', 'options': ['Agreement', 'Island', 'Free time', 'Eggplant']} ,

{'numb': 1871, 'question': 'Chakalakzor', 'answer': 'Jungle', 'options': ['Disease', 'Progress', 'Hero', 'Jungle']} ,

{'numb': 1872, 'question': 'Ulkan', 'answer': 'Large', 'options': ['Kitchen', 'Virus', 'Large', 'Torch']} ,

{'numb': 1873, 'question': 'Muloyim', 'answer': 'Mild', 'options': ['Traditional', 'Nasty', 'Couple', 'Mild']} ,

{'numb': 1874, 'question': 'Shimol', 'answer': 'North', 'options': ['Several', 'North', 'Development', 'Ingredient']} ,

{'numb': 1875, 'question': 'Voha', 'answer': 'Oasis', 'options': ['Sales', 'Oasis', 'Passion', 'Learn to swim']} ,

{'numb': 1876, 'question': 'Qumli', 'answer': 'Sandy', 'options': ['They', 'Sandy', 'Father in law', 'Roast']} ,

{'numb': 1877, 'question': 'Hisob', 'answer': 'Score', 'options': ['Sick', 'Equip', 'Post', 'Score']} ,

{'numb': 1878, 'question': 'Nur taratmoq', 'answer': 'Shine', 'options': ['Ask', 'Hire', 'Shine', 'Lucky']} ,

{'numb': 1879, 'question': 'Uxlab yotgan', 'answer': 'Sleeper', 'options': ['Next', 'Sleeper', 'Dirty', 'Pipe']} ,

{'numb': 1880, 'question': 'Qorli', 'answer': 'Snowy', 'options': ['Electric piano', 'Snowy', 'Social media', 'Bump']} ,

{'numb': 1881, 'question': 'Janub', 'answer': 'South', 'options': ['Man', 'Wedding', 'Self catering', 'South']} ,

{'numb': 1882, 'question': 'Boron', 'answer': 'Storm', 'options': ['Website', 'Storm', 'Belt', 'Book']} ,

{'numb': 1883, 'question': 'Quyoshli', 'answer': 'Sunny', 'options': ['At the weekend', 'Art', 'Sunny', 'Day']} ,

{'numb': 1884, 'question': 'Umr kechirmoq', 'answer': 'Survive', 'options': ['Social media', 'Machine', 'Survive', 'Money']} ,

{'numb': 1885, 'question': 'Omon qolish', 'answer': 'Survival', 'options': ['Key', 'Mild', 'Survival', 'Turkey']} ,

{'numb': 1886, 'question': 'Chodir', 'answer': 'Tent', 'options': ['Tent', 'Down', 'Look', 'Paper']} ,

{'numb': 1887, 'question': 'Momaqaldiroq', 'answer': 'Thunder', 'options': ['Thunder', 'Kitchen', 'Fee', 'Have a reservation']} ,

{'numb': 1888, 'question': 'Harakat', 'answer': 'Traffic', 'options': ['Waitress', 'Carpet', 'Traffic', 'Worse']} ,

{'numb': 1889, 'question': 'Tropik', 'answer': 'Tropical', 'options': ['Actor', 'Chief', 'Tropical', 'Book']} ,

{'numb': 1890, 'question': 'Iliq', 'answer': 'Warm', 'options': ['Dish', 'Sheet', 'Opinion', 'Warm']} ,

{'numb': 1891, 'question': 'Sharshara', 'answer': 'Waterfall', 'options': ['Team', 'Waterfall', 'Pleasure', 'Obviously']} ,

{'numb': 1892, 'question': 'Garb', 'answer': 'West', 'options': ['In fact', 'Armchair', 'Fox', 'West']} ,

{'numb': 1893, 'question': 'Nam', 'answer': 'Wet', 'options': ['Quiet', 'Blanket', 'Wet', 'Toy']} ,

{'numb': 1894, 'question': 'Shamolli', 'answer': 'Windy', 'options': ['Mean', 'Skill', 'Windy', 'Together']} ,

{'numb': 1895, 'question': 'Yillik', 'answer': 'Annual', 'options': ['Adult', 'Why', 'Crime', 'Annual']} ,

{'numb': 1896, 'question': 'Yomon', 'answer': 'Awful', 'options': ['Enough', 'Worried', 'Awful', 'American']} ,

{'numb': 1897, 'question': 'Mukofot', 'answer': 'Award', 'options': ['Read to the news', 'Award', 'Towards', 'Text']} ,

{'numb': 1898, 'question': 'Vovullamoq', 'answer': 'Bark', 'options': ['Fever', 'Apricot', 'Bark', 'Goose']} ,

{'numb': 1899, 'question': 'Ajoyib', 'answer': 'Brilliant', 'options': ['North', 'Grandfather', 'Brilliant', 'Beach']} ,

{'numb': 1900, 'question': 'Nishonlamoq', 'answer': 'Celebrate', 'options': ['Probably', 'Celebrate', 'Exercise', 'Easily']} ,

{'numb': 1901, 'question': 'Xayriya', 'answer': 'Charity', 'options': ['Nationality', 'Uruguay', 'Pipe', 'Charity']} ,

{'numb': 1902, 'question': 'Murabbiy', 'answer': 'Coach', 'options': ['Forget', 'Dolphin', 'Send', 'Coach']} ,

{'numb': 1903, 'question': 'Umumiylik', 'answer': 'Common', 'options': ['Sauce', 'Floor', 'Recommend', 'Common']} ,

{'numb': 1904, 'question': 'Jamoa', 'answer': 'Community', 'options': ['Community', 'Camping', 'Stand', 'Collect']} ,

{'numb': 1905, 'question': 'Doim', 'answer': 'Constantly', 'options': ['Constantly', 'House sit', 'Type', 'Eyesight']} ,

{'numb': 1906, 'question': 'Hal qiluvchi', 'answer': 'Crucial', 'options': ['Plate', 'Answer', 'Crucial', 'Snack']} ,

{'numb': 1907, 'question': 'Keksaygan', 'answer': 'Elderly', 'options': ['Airport', 'Company', 'Sugar', 'Elderly']} ,

{'numb': 1908, 'question': 'Alo', 'answer': 'Excellent', 'options': ['Use', 'Europe', 'Excellent', 'Happiness']} ,

{'numb': 1909, 'question': 'Muvaffaqiyatsizlikka uchramoq', 'answer': 'Fail', 'options': ['Early', 'Machine', 'Fail', 'Cheek']} ,

{'numb': 1910, 'question': 'Diqqatini qaratish', 'answer': 'Focus', 'options': ['Football', 'Focus', 'Coffee', 'Online']} ,

{'numb': 1911, 'question': 'Uysiz', 'answer': 'Homeless', 'options': ['Homeless', 'Pull out', 'Damp', 'Hotel']} ,

{'numb': 1912, 'question': 'Katta', 'answer': 'Huge', 'options': ['In the week', 'Period', 'Moment', 'Huge']} ,

{'numb': 1913, 'question': 'Yaxshilamoq', 'answer': 'Improve', 'options': ['Thirsty', 'Cook', 'Improve', 'Finish school']} ,

{'numb': 1914, 'question': 'Kishi', 'answer': 'Individual', 'options': ['Tweet', 'Film', 'Individual', 'Umbrella']} ,

{'numb': 1915, 'question': 'Gamxorlik qilish', 'answer': 'Look after', 'options': ['Computer skills', 'Watch', 'Look after', 'Against']} ,

{'numb': 1916, 'question': 'Katta', 'answer': 'Massive', 'options': ['Massive', 'Apple juice', 'Karate', 'Student']} ,

{'numb': 1917, 'question': 'Maksumum', 'answer': 'Maximum', 'options': ['Maximum', 'Too', 'Italy', 'Consequence']} ,

{'numb': 1918, 'question': 'Azo', 'answer': 'Member', 'options': ['Meal', 'Journey', 'Possession', 'Member']} ,

{'numb': 1919, 'question': 'Tashkil qilmoq', 'answer': 'Organize', 'options': ['Organize', 'Go to bed', 'Local', 'Hospital']} ,

{'numb': 1920, 'question': 'Boyoq', 'answer': 'Paint', 'options': ['Workplace', 'Crucial', 'Paint', 'Apple']} ,

{'numb': 1921, 'question': 'Oyinchi', 'answer': 'Player', 'options': ['Fluently', 'Player', 'Again', 'Live with']} ,

{'numb': 1922, 'question': 'Tuzatmoq', 'answer': 'Repair', 'options': ['Centre', 'Outside', 'First', 'Repair']} ,

{'numb': 1923, 'question': 'Muayyan yashamoq', 'answer': 'Resident', 'options': ['Buy', 'Resident', 'Turn', 'Fishing']} ,

{'numb': 1924, 'question': 'Tuproq', 'answer': 'Soil', 'options': ['Swap', 'Fox', 'Notice', 'Soil']} ,

{'numb': 1925, 'question': 'Soliq', 'answer': 'Tax', 'options': ['Sad', 'Feeble', 'Good', 'Tax']} ,

{'numb': 1926, 'question': 'Jamoa', 'answer': 'Team', 'options': ['Statistic', 'Team', 'Naughty', 'Suitcase']} ,

{'numb': 1927, 'question': 'Kichkina', 'answer': 'Tiny', 'options': ['Vacation', 'Food processor', 'Conversation', 'Tiny']} ,

{'numb': 1928, 'question': 'Havotirlangan', 'answer': 'Worried', 'options': ['Worried', 'Nurse', 'Soda', 'Ill']} ,

{'numb': 1929, 'question': 'Musiqa tinglamoq', 'answer': 'Listen to music', 'options': ['Solution', 'Confused', 'Listen to music', 'Luggage']} ,

{'numb': 1930, 'question': 'Narsa yasamoq', 'answer': 'Make things', 'options': ['Bad manners', 'Physical', 'Make things', 'Essential']} ,

{'numb': 1931, 'question': 'Hechkim', 'answer': 'Nobody', 'options': ['Medical', 'Nobody', 'Soup', 'Successful']} ,

{'numb': 1932, 'question': 'Moyqalam', 'answer': 'Paintbrush', 'options': ['Paintbrush', 'Portuguese', 'Family', 'Every day']} ,

{'numb': 1933, 'question': 'Totiqush', 'answer': 'Parrot', 'options': ['Loose', 'Wedding', 'Listen', 'Parrot']} ,

{'numb': 1934, 'question': 'Vidyooyinlar oynamoq', 'answer': 'Play video games', 'options': ['Broken', 'Play video games', 'Mistake', 'Foggy']} ,

{'numb': 1935, 'question': 'Baxtsiz hodisa', 'answer': 'Accident', 'options': ['Accident', 'Saucepan', 'Big', 'They']} ,

{'numb': 1936, 'question': 'Aktrisa', 'answer': 'Actress', 'options': ['Throat', 'Actress', 'Text', 'Yesterday']} ,

{'numb': 1937, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Adventure', 'options': ['Adventure', 'Painter', 'Badly', 'Lesson']} ,

{'numb': 1938, 'question': 'Maqola', 'answer': 'Article', 'options': ['Article', 'Conversation', 'On theinternet', 'Stop']} ,

{'numb': 1939, 'question': 'Astanaut', 'answer': 'Astronaut', 'options': ['Astronaut', 'Flat', 'Comics', 'Bathroom']} ,

{'numb': 1940, 'question': 'Duradgor', 'answer': 'Carpenter', 'options': ['Too', 'Carpenter', 'Rainy', 'Denmark']} ,

{'numb': 1941, 'question': '100 yillik', 'answer': 'Century', 'options': ['Century', 'Thick', 'Bank', 'Wardrobe']} ,

{'numb': 1942, 'question': 'Belgilar', 'answer': 'Characters', 'options': ['Guitar', 'Even', 'Noisy', 'Characters']} ,

{'numb': 1943, 'question': 'Olmoq', 'answer': 'Die', 'options': ['Niece', 'Die', 'Answer', 'Meeting']} ,

{'numb': 1944, 'question': 'Xujjat', 'answer': 'Document', 'options': ['Online', 'Balloon', 'Decide', 'Document']} ,

{'numb': 1945, 'question': 'Orzu', 'answer': 'Dream', 'options': ['Animal', 'Dream', 'Loose', 'Saturday']} ,

{'numb': 1946, 'question': 'Fundament', 'answer': 'Foundation', 'options': ['Foundation', 'Fog', 'Graduation', 'Wet']} ,

{'numb': 1947, 'question': 'Osmoq', 'answer': 'Grow up', 'options': ['Grow up', 'Frying pan', 'Garbage', 'Statue']} ,

{'numb': 1948, 'question': 'Yetakchi', 'answer': 'Leader', 'options': ['Waiter', 'Centre', 'Camp', 'Leader']} ,

{'numb': 1949, 'question': 'Haqiqiy', 'answer': 'Real', 'options': ['Diabetes', 'Grandmother', 'Real', 'Reserve']} ,

{'numb': 1950, 'question': 'Olim', 'answer': 'Scientist', 'options': ['Scientist', 'Customer', 'Wife', 'Airport']} ,

{'numb': 1951, 'question': 'Hikoyachi', 'answer': 'Storyteller', 'options': ['Theme', 'Hospital', 'Storyteller', 'Angrily']} ,

{'numb': 1952, 'question': 'Hikoya', 'answer': 'Tale', 'options': ['Tale', 'Women', 'Fascinated', 'Shop online']} ,

{'numb': 1953, 'question': 'Birinchi', 'answer': 'First', 'options': ['Thing', 'Nothing', 'First', 'Waste']} ,

{'numb': 1954, 'question': 'Uchinchi', 'answer': 'Third', 'options': ['Perhaps', 'Shame', 'Lie', 'Third']} ,

{'numb': 1955, 'question': 'Tortinchi', 'answer': 'Fourth', 'options': ['Supermarket', 'Fourth', 'Kindof', 'Survive']} ,

{'numb': 1956, 'question': 'Beshinchi', 'answer': 'Fifth', 'options': ['Famous', 'Fifth', 'Minimalist', 'Near']} ,

{'numb': 1957, 'question': 'Oltinchi', 'answer': 'Sixth', 'options': ['Anybody', 'Hospital', 'Soil', 'Sixth']} ,

{'numb': 1958, 'question': 'Yettinchi', 'answer': 'Seventh', 'options': ['Partner', 'Address', 'Mobile phone', 'Seventh']} ,

{'numb': 1959, 'question': 'Sakkizinchi', 'answer': 'Eighth', 'options': ['Sick', 'Steering wheel', 'Eighth', 'Tell']} ,

{'numb': 1960, 'question': 'Toqqizinchi', 'answer': 'Ninth', 'options': ['Sauce', 'Ninth', 'Stressful', 'Changing room']} ,

{'numb': 1961, 'question': 'Oninchi', 'answer': 'Tenth', 'options': ['Get divorced', 'These', 'Tenth', 'Pale']} ,

{'numb': 1962, 'question': 'On birinchi', 'answer': 'Eleventh', 'options': ['Eleventh', 'Narrow', 'Kitchen', 'Exercise']} ,

{'numb': 1963, 'question': 'On ikkinchi', 'answer': 'Twelfth', 'options': ['Chin', 'Twelfth', 'Dead', 'Satellite dish']} ,

{'numb': 1964, 'question': 'Yigirmanchi', 'answer': 'Twentieth', 'options': ['Twentieth', 'Bowl', 'Switzerland', 'Confusing']} ,

{'numb': 1965, 'question': 'Yigirma birinchi', 'answer': 'Twenty first', 'options': ['Excited', 'Hairdresser', 'Exciting', 'Twenty first']} ,

{'numb': 1966, 'question': 'Yigirma uchinchi', 'answer': 'Twenty third', 'options': ['Socks', 'Friend', 'Recently', 'Twenty third']} ,

{'numb': 1967, 'question': 'Ottizinchi', 'answer': 'Thirtieth', 'options': ['Thirtieth', 'Near', 'Tap', 'Jump']} ,

{'numb': 1968, 'question': 'Ottiz birinchi', 'answer': 'Thirty first', 'options': ['Weather', 'Worst', 'Rainwater', 'Thirty first']} ,

{'numb': 1969, 'question': 'Dam olish kuni', 'answer': 'A day off', 'options': ['Health', 'Towel', 'A day off', 'Toilet']} ,

{'numb': 1970, 'question': 'Ilgari', 'answer': 'Ago', 'options': ['Eleventh', 'Men', 'Cloud', 'Ago']} ,

{'numb': 1971, 'question': 'Atmosfera', 'answer': 'Atmosphere', 'options': ['Entrance', 'Arm', 'Atmosphere', 'Example']} ,

{'numb': 1972, 'question': 'Komediya', 'answer': 'Comedian', 'options': ['Thermometer', 'Comedian', 'Free time', 'Related']} ,

{'numb': 1973, 'question': 'Narx', 'answer': 'Cost', 'options': ['Australia', 'Orange juice', 'Cost', 'Magazine']} ,

{'numb': 1974, 'question': 'Qiyin', 'answer': 'Difficult', 'options': ['Difficult', 'Book your flight', 'Boss', 'Fear']} ,

{'numb': 1975, 'question': 'Tugatish', 'answer': 'Ending', 'options': ['Extrovert', 'Ending', 'Colorful', 'Wake']} ,

{'numb': 1976, 'question': 'Uzur kechirim', 'answer': 'Excuse', 'options': ['Hard', 'Excuse', 'Improve', 'Curtain']} ,

{'numb': 1977, 'question': 'Kasal bolmoq', 'answer': 'Get ill', 'options': ['Get ill', 'Souvenir', 'Watch', 'Camera']} ,

{'numb': 1978, 'question': 'Bosh ogrigi', 'answer': 'Headache', 'options': ['Shop', 'Headache', 'Forward', 'For']} ,

{'numb': 1979, 'question': 'Qorqinchli film', 'answer': 'Horror film', 'options': ['Horror film', 'Fist', 'Cap', 'Typist']} ,

{'numb': 1980, 'question': 'Kasallik', 'answer': 'Illnes', 'options': ['Illnes', 'Careful', 'Snowy', 'Smart']} ,

{'numb': 1981, 'question': 'Aslida', 'answer': 'In fact', 'options': ['Carrot', 'Cabbage', 'In fact', 'Believein']} ,

{'numb': 1982, 'question': 'Soginmoq', 'answer': 'Miss', 'options': ['Swimming', 'Europe', 'Later', 'Miss']} ,

{'numb': 1983, 'question': 'Millioner', 'answer': 'Millionaire', 'options': ['Daughter', 'Desicion', 'Customer', 'Millionaire']} ,

{'numb': 1984, 'question': 'Yomgirli', 'answer': 'Rainy', 'options': ['Rainy', 'Learn', 'Strength', 'Information']} ,

{'numb': 1985, 'question': 'Tasavvur qilish', 'answer': 'Realize', 'options': ['Philosophy', 'Answer', 'Realize', 'Clap']} ,

{'numb': 1986, 'question': 'Istefoga chiqmoq', 'answer': 'Retirement', 'options': ['Tent', 'Eye', 'Retirement', 'Abandon']} ,

{'numb': 1987, 'question': 'Xizmat korsatish', 'answer': 'Service', 'options': ['Service', 'Join', 'Text', 'You are welcome']} ,

{'numb': 1988, 'question': 'Subtropik', 'answer': 'Subtropical', 'options': ['Travel', 'Subtropical', 'Good bye', 'In front of']} ,

{'numb': 1989, 'question': 'Irgitmoq', 'answer': 'Throw', 'options': ['Eater', 'Nephew', 'Throw', 'Basic']} ,

{'numb': 1990, 'question': 'Ofitsiant', 'answer': 'Waitress', 'options': ['Wonderful', 'Waitress', 'Location', 'Characters']} ,

{'numb': 1991, 'question': 'Bir finjon', 'answer': 'A cup of', 'options': ['New zealand', 'A cup of', 'Fill', 'Choose']} ,

{'numb': 1992, 'question': 'Olmali sharbat', 'answer': 'Apple juice', 'options': ['Chef', 'Less', 'Style', 'Apple juice']} ,

{'numb': 1993, 'question': 'Pechenye', 'answer': 'Biscuit', 'options': ['Elbow', 'Fantastic', 'Biscuit', 'Payback']} ,

{'numb': 1994, 'question': 'Burger', 'answer': 'Burger', 'options': ['Digit', 'Block', 'Burger', 'Cards']} ,

{'numb': 1995, 'question': 'Uy sotib olmoq', 'answer': 'Buy a house', 'options': ['Buy a house', 'Gasoline', 'Pound', 'Basketball']} ,

{'numb': 1996, 'question': 'Imkoniyat', 'answer': 'Chance', 'options': ['Herb', 'Nice', 'Chance', 'Driver']} ,

{'numb': 1997, 'question': 'Kasbini ozgartirmoq', 'answer': 'Change jobs', 'options': ['Salary', 'Household possessioins', 'Travel', 'Change jobs']} ,

{'numb': 1998, 'question': 'Chips', 'answer': 'Chips', 'options': ['Red', 'Large', 'Stranger', 'Chips']} ,

{'numb': 1999, 'question': 'Kofe', 'answer': 'Cofee', 'options': ['Hall', 'Cofee', 'Husband', 'Active']} ,

{'numb': 2000, 'question': 'Shohsimon bulochka', 'answer': 'Croissant', 'options': ['Between', 'Croissant', 'Give', 'Windowsill']} ,

{'numb': 2001, 'question': 'Keks', 'answer': 'Cupcake', 'options': ['Athletics', 'Tropical', 'Watermelon', 'Cupcake']} ,

{'numb': 2002, 'question': 'Ponchik', 'answer': 'Doughnut', 'options': ['Loose', 'Pasta', 'Vacation', 'Doughnut']} ,

{'numb': 2003, 'question': 'Hissiyot', 'answer': 'Filling', 'options': ['Filling', 'Indoors', 'Local', 'Remember']} ,

{'numb': 2004, 'question': 'Maktabni tugatmoq', 'answer': 'Finish school', 'options': ['Meaning', 'Seventh', 'Finish school', 'Introduce']} ,

{'numb': 2005, 'question': 'Parvoz', 'answer': 'Flight', 'options': ['Lovely', 'Flight', 'High speed', 'Wind']} ,

{'numb': 2006, 'question': 'Ovqat', 'answer': 'Food', 'options': ['Wardrobe', 'Business management', 'Food', 'Twins']} ,

{'numb': 2007, 'question': 'Farzandli bolmoq', 'answer': 'Have a baby', 'options': ['Equal', 'Have a baby', 'Reduce', 'Do online banking']} ,

{'numb': 2008, 'question': 'Hot dog', 'answer': 'Hot dog', 'options': ['Named', 'Free time', 'Hot dog', 'Foundation']} ,

{'numb': 2009, 'question': 'Xalqaro', 'answer': 'International', 'options': ['Leather', 'International', 'Communicate', 'Sour']} ,

{'numb': 2010, 'question': 'Qoshilmoq', 'answer': 'Join', 'options': ['Bump', 'Coffee', 'Cloth', 'Join']} ,

{'numb': 2011, 'question': 'Yangi til organish', 'answer': 'Learn a new language', 'options': ['Women', 'Learn a new language', 'Meeting', 'Circle']} ,

{'numb': 2012, 'question': 'Menyu', 'answer': 'Menu', 'options': ['Caugh', 'Successful', 'Menu', 'Dish']} ,

{'numb': 2013, 'question': 'Chetga kochmoq', 'answer': 'Move abroad', 'options': ['Stockings', 'Excuse', 'Sister', 'Move abroad']} ,

{'numb': 2014, 'question': 'Keyingi', 'answer': 'Next', 'options': ['Pale', 'Share', 'Always', 'Next']} ,

{'numb': 2015, 'question': 'Apelsinli sharbat', 'answer': 'Orange juice', 'options': ['Annoyed', 'Compass', 'Orange juice', 'Cucumber']} ,

{'numb': 2016, 'question': 'Tashkilot', 'answer': 'Organization', 'options': ['Department store', 'Fluent', 'Organization', 'Stick']} ,

{'numb': 2017, 'question': 'Kuylamoq', 'answer': 'Sing', 'options': ['Chief', 'Opinion', 'Sing', 'Cancer']} ,

{'numb': 2018, 'question': 'Gazak', 'answer': 'Snack', 'options': ['Freeze', 'Snack', 'Plum', 'Communication skills']} ,

{'numb': 2019, 'question': 'Bu oqshom', 'answer': 'This evening', 'options': ['Train', 'Consequence', 'This evening', 'Log on']} ,

{'numb': 2020, 'question': 'Xohlamoq', 'answer': 'Would like', 'options': ['Cleaner', 'Would like', 'Purchase', 'Wash basin']} ,

{'numb': 2021, 'question': 'Rekord yozuv', 'answer': 'Record', 'options': ['Illnes', 'Fluent', 'Record', 'Challenge']} ,

{'numb': 2022, 'question': 'Tadqiqot', 'answer': 'Research', 'options': ['Guy', 'Research', 'Melon', 'Expert']} ,

{'numb': 2023, 'question': 'Minmoq', 'answer': 'Ride', 'options': ['Ride', 'Yellow', 'Sea', 'Languages']} ,

{'numb': 2024, 'question': 'Joy', 'answer': 'Seat', 'options': ['Seat', 'Suchã‚', 'Reader', 'Rich']} ,

{'numb': 2025, 'question': 'Onlayn dokon', 'answer': 'Shop online', 'options': ['Rice', 'Shop online', 'Narrow', 'Finish school']} ,

{'numb': 2026, 'question': 'Belgi', 'answer': 'Sign', 'options': ['Sign', 'Look after', 'Serve', 'Cup']} ,

{'numb': 2027, 'question': 'Mahorat', 'answer': 'Skill', 'options': ['Skill', 'Olives', 'Ballon', 'Bookshop']} ,

{'numb': 2028, 'question': 'Ijtimoiy media', 'answer': 'Social media', 'options': ['Social media', 'Family', 'Serious', 'Loudly']} ,

{'numb': 2029, 'question': 'Suzish', 'answer': 'Swim', 'options': ['Sneakers sport', 'Swim', 'Pass your exams', 'Adopt']} ,

{'numb': 2030, 'question': 'Suzuvchi', 'answer': 'Swimmer', 'options': ['Carrot', 'Next to', 'Swimmer', 'Skill']} ,

{'numb': 2031, 'question': 'Rasmga olmoq', 'answer': 'Take photos', 'options': ['Take photos', 'Belongto', 'Can', 'Beach']} ,

{'numb': 2032, 'question': 'Chanqamoq', 'answer': 'Thirsty', 'options': ['Relationship', 'Go on facebook', 'Stressed', 'Thirsty']} ,

{'numb': 2033, 'question': 'Tarjimon', 'answer': 'Translator', 'options': ['Guest', 'Hairdresser', 'Translator', 'Disappointment']} ,

{'numb': 2034, 'question': 'Tur hil', 'answer': 'Type', 'options': ['Thirsty', 'Shop online', 'Type', 'Behavior']} ,

{'numb': 2035, 'question': 'Urugvay', 'answer': 'Uruguay', 'options': ['Outdoors', 'To do list', 'Uruguay', 'Want']} ,

{'numb': 2036, 'question': 'Kongilli', 'answer': 'Volunteer', 'options': ['Volunteer', 'Sick', 'Last name', 'Very']} ,

{'numb': 2037, 'question': 'Vidyo', 'answer': 'Video', 'options': ['Video', 'Noisy', 'Door', 'Hall']} ,

{'numb': 2038, 'question': 'Sport tomosha qilmoq', 'answer': 'Watch sport', 'options': ['Dark', 'Watch sport', 'Backwards', 'Fantastic']} ,

{'numb': 2039, 'question': 'Bogda ishlamoq', 'answer': 'Work in the garden', 'options': ['Trainee', 'Household possessioins', 'Work in the garden', 'Carefully']} ,

{'numb': 2040, 'question': 'Yozmoq', 'answer': 'Write', 'options': ['Write', 'Shopper', 'Genetic', 'Philosophy']} ,

{'numb': 2041, 'question': 'Bir shisha', 'answer': 'A bottle of', 'options': ['Ruins', 'Ticket', 'A bottle of', 'Hard']} ,

{'numb': 2042, 'question': 'Dalil keltirmoq', 'answer': 'Advert', 'options': ['Profit', 'Acquaintance', 'Magazine', 'Advert']} ,

{'numb': 2043, 'question': 'Jazoir', 'answer': 'Algeria', 'options': ['Algeria', 'Scientist', 'Shy', 'Organ']} ,

{'numb': 2044, 'question': 'Hayvon', 'answer': 'Animal', 'options': ['Bank', 'Zoology', 'Convenient', 'Animal']} ,

{'numb': 2045, 'question': 'Yomon', 'answer': 'Badly', 'options': ['Badly', 'Gallant', 'Research', 'Wednesday']} ,

{'numb': 2046, 'question': 'Zerikgan', 'answer': 'Bored', 'options': ['To', 'Bored', 'Season', 'Morning']} ,

{'numb': 2047, 'question': 'Kompyuter bilmi', 'answer': 'Computer skills', 'options': ['Quarter to', 'First name', 'Every day', 'Computer skills']} ,

{'numb': 2048, 'question': 'Aloqa', 'answer': 'Contact', 'options': ['Contact', 'Herb', 'Nail', 'Jog']} ,

{'numb': 2049, 'question': 'Raqs', 'answer': 'Dance', 'options': ['Dull', 'Dance', 'Special', 'Consistof']} ,

{'numb': 2050, 'question': 'Delfin', 'answer': 'Dolphin', 'options': ['Dolphin', 'Country', 'Join', 'Atmosphere']} ,

{'numb': 2051, 'question': 'Bir biri', 'answer': 'Each other', 'options': ['Mobile phone', 'Each other', 'Refund', 'Typical']} ,

{'numb': 2052, 'question': 'Elektron pianino', 'answer': 'Electric piano', 'options': ['Float', 'Worried', 'Couple', 'Electric piano']} ,

{'numb': 2053, 'question': 'Zavqli', 'answer': 'Enthusiastic', 'options': ['Emirate', 'Iron', 'For hours', 'Enthusiastic']} ,

{'numb': 2054, 'question': 'Tez', 'answer': 'Fast', 'options': ['Do online banking', 'Single', 'Bright', 'Fast']} ,

{'numb': 2055, 'question': 'Boshqa til', 'answer': 'Foreign language', 'options': ['Foreign language', 'Also', 'Opportunity', 'Here']} ,

{'numb': 2056, 'question': 'Facebookga kirmoq', 'answer': 'Go on facebook', 'options': ['Usual', 'January', 'Go on facebook', 'Meal']} ,

{'numb': 2057, 'question': 'Dostlar bilan kochaga chiqish', 'answer': 'Go out with friends', 'options': ['Man', 'Spoon', 'Go out with friends', 'Typist']} ,

{'numb': 2058, 'question': 'Kinoga bormoq', 'answer': 'Go to the cinema', 'options': ['Bedroom', 'Good quality', 'Go to the cinema', 'Chimney']} ,

{'numb': 2059, 'question': 'Teatrga bormoq', 'answer': 'Go to the theatre', 'options': ['Good quality', 'Go to the theatre', 'Vase', 'Promise']} ,

{'numb': 2060, 'question': 'Tillabaliq', 'answer': 'Goldfish', 'options': ['Goldfish', 'Ending', 'Where', 'Advert']} ,

{'numb': 2061, 'question': 'Gorilla', 'answer': 'Gorilla', 'options': ['Cloud', 'Tomorrow', 'Gorilla', 'Repetitivestraininjury']} ,

{'numb': 2062, 'question': 'Yoqtirgan mashgulot', 'answer': 'Hobby', 'options': ['Pharmacy', 'Hobby', 'Mini bar', 'Family']} ,

{'numb': 2063, 'question': 'Qiziqmoq', 'answer': 'Interest', 'options': ['Useful', 'Interest', 'Knowledge', 'Ridiculous']} ,

{'numb': 2064, 'question': 'Qiziqish', 'answer': 'Interested in', 'options': ['Very', 'Organize', 'Success', 'Interested in']} ,

{'numb': 2065, 'question': 'Livan', 'answer': 'Lebanon', 'options': ['Go clubbing', 'Lebanon', 'Lie in', 'Husband']} ,

{'numb': 2066, 'question': 'Internet', 'answer': 'Internet', 'options': ['Internet', 'Today', 'In front of', 'Juice']} ,

{'numb': 2067, 'question': 'Board', 'answer': 'Ironing', 'options': ['Shout', 'Ironing', 'Virtual', 'Plan']} ,

{'numb': 2068, 'question': 'Aloqa', 'answer': 'Link', 'options': ['Easy', 'Restaurant', 'Link', 'Compute']} ,

{'numb': 2069, 'question': 'Room', 'answer': 'Living', 'options': ['Remember', 'Community', 'Each other', 'Living']} ,

{'numb': 2070, 'question': 'Omadli', 'answer': 'Lucky', 'options': ['Art', 'Tongue', 'Smart', 'Lucky']} ,

{'numb': 2071, 'question': 'Daqiqa', 'answer': 'Minut', 'options': ['Minut', 'Husband', 'Duvet', 'Jar']} ,

{'numb': 2072, 'question': 'Mini bar', 'answer': 'Mini bar', 'options': ['Mini bar', 'First floor', 'Feeble', 'Get']} ,

{'numb': 2073, 'question': 'Shovqinli', 'answer': 'Noisy', 'options': ['Noisy', 'Sadness', 'Mix', 'Dangerously']} ,

{'numb': 2074, 'question': 'Hususiy', 'answer': 'Own', 'options': ['Monday', 'Advantages', 'Truck', 'Own']} ,

{'numb': 2075, 'question': 'Parol', 'answer': 'Password', 'options': ['Nephew', 'Entrance', 'Frying', 'Password']} ,

{'numb': 2076, 'question': 'Pitsa', 'answer': 'Pizza', 'options': ['Pizza', 'Stress', 'Horror film', 'Journalist']} ,

{'numb': 2077, 'question': 'Sokin tinch', 'answer': 'Quiet', 'options': ['Soon', 'Useful', 'Cloudy', 'Quiet']} ,

{'numb': 2078, 'question': 'Qabul', 'answer': 'Reception', 'options': ['Reception', 'Explain', 'Bone', 'Pear']} ,

{'numb': 2079, 'question': 'Mustahkamlash', 'answer': 'Refreshments', 'options': ['Chief', 'Married', 'Refreshments', 'Main course']} ,

{'numb': 2080, 'question': 'Hodim', 'answer': 'Staff', 'options': ['Benefit', 'Box', 'Toast', 'Staff']} ,

{'numb': 2081, 'question': 'Supermarket', 'answer': 'Supermarket', 'options': ['Stall', 'Sandwich', 'Supermarket', 'City']} ,

{'numb': 2082, 'question': 'Mavzu', 'answer': 'Theme', 'options': ['Card games', 'Neighbor', 'Kitchen', 'Theme']} ,

{'numb': 2083, 'question': 'Mehmon', 'answer': 'Visitor', 'options': ['For me', 'Saturday', 'Herb', 'Visitor']} ,

{'numb': 2084, 'question': 'Veb-sayt', 'answer': 'Website', 'options': ['Website', 'Player', 'Married', 'Fascinating']} ,

{'numb': 2085, 'question': 'Wi-fi', 'answer': 'Wi fi', 'options': ['Hour', 'Wi fi', 'Instructions', 'Flight']} ,

{'numb': 2086, 'question': 'Foydalanish huquqi', 'answer': 'Access', 'options': ['Access', 'Dark', 'Drop', 'Fashion designer']} ,

{'numb': 2087, 'question': 'Havo sovutish', 'answer': 'Air conditioning', 'options': ['Air conditioning', 'Lab', 'Succeed in', 'Thought']} ,

{'numb': 2088, 'question': 'Hamma', 'answer': 'All', 'options': ['Fix', 'Check in', 'All', 'Business']} ,

{'numb': 2089, 'question': 'Boshqa', 'answer': 'Another', 'options': ['Train', 'Another', 'Or', 'Stress']} ,

{'numb': 2090, 'question': 'Yetib kelmoq', 'answer': 'Arrive', 'options': ['Free time', 'Traveller', 'Arrive', 'Trend']} ,

{'numb': 2091, 'question': 'Nonvoyxona', 'answer': 'Bakery', 'options': ['Dive', 'Fry', 'Bakery', 'Parrot']} ,

{'numb': 2092, 'question': 'Vanna', 'answer': 'Bath', 'options': ['Texture', 'Bath', 'Present', 'Early']} ,

{'numb': 2093, 'question': 'Singan', 'answer': 'Broken', 'options': ['Abandon', 'Music', 'Lazy', 'Broken']} ,

{'numb': 2094, 'question': 'Royxatdan otmoq', 'answer': 'Check in', 'options': ['Check in', 'Experiment', 'Mini bar', 'Take up']} ,

{'numb': 2095, 'question': 'Royxatdan ochirilish', 'answer': 'Checkout', 'options': ['Checkout', 'Resident', 'Ear', 'Look after']} ,

{'numb': 2096, 'question': 'Toza', 'answer': 'Clean', 'options': ['Birthday', 'Clean', 'Equal', 'Atmosphere']} ,

{'numb': 2097, 'question': 'Javon', 'answer': 'Cupboard', 'options': ['Cupboard', 'Unkind', 'Sixth', 'Comedian']} ,

{'numb': 2098, 'question': 'Oshxona', 'answer': 'Dining room', 'options': ['Its', 'Writer', 'Dining room', 'Comics']} ,

{'numb': 2099, 'question': 'Har bir', 'answer': 'Each', 'options': ['Organized', 'Rough', 'Thick', 'Each']} ,

{'numb': 2100, 'question': 'Qulaylik', 'answer': 'Facility', 'options': ['Facility', 'Toilet', 'High', 'Conversation']} ,

{'numb': 2101, 'question': 'Festival', 'answer': 'Festival', 'options': ['Festival', 'Twentieth', 'Shawl', 'Carpet']} ,

{'numb': 2102, 'question': 'Baliq ovlash', 'answer': 'Fishing', 'options': ['Raspberry', 'Fishing', 'Stand', 'Well-paid']} ,

{'numb': 2103, 'question': 'Soatlab', 'answer': 'For hours', 'options': ['For hours', 'Card', 'Seat', 'Over there']} ,

{'numb': 2104, 'question': 'Bepul avtoturargoh', 'answer': 'Free parking', 'options': ['Shop', 'Wire', 'Free parking', 'Math']} ,

{'numb': 2105, 'question': 'Bron qilish', 'answer': 'Have a reservation', 'options': ['Can', 'Have a baby', 'Mother', 'Have a reservation']} ,

{'numb': 2106, 'question': 'Isitgich', 'answer': 'Heater', 'options': ['Fall', 'Heater', 'Traditional', 'Aunt']} ,

{'numb': 2107, 'question': 'Korsatmalar', 'answer': 'Instructions', 'options': ['Butter', 'Nurse', 'Instructions', 'Architecture']} ,

{'numb': 2108, 'question': 'Omma', 'answer': 'Public', 'options': ['Pan', 'Mix', 'Public', 'Aunt']} ,

{'numb': 2109, 'question': 'Romol', 'answer': 'Shawl', 'options': ['Why', 'Plastic', 'Sleep', 'Shawl']} ,

{'numb': 2110, 'question': 'Teri', 'answer': 'Skin', 'options': ['Egg', 'Skin', 'Physical', 'Habit']} ,

{'numb': 2111, 'question': 'Aqlli', 'answer': 'Smart', 'options': ['Best', 'Air conditioned', 'Smart', 'Masters degree']} ,

{'numb': 2112, 'question': 'Sport', 'answer': 'Sports', 'options': ['Switzerland', 'Extrovert', 'Top', 'Sports']} ,

{'numb': 2113, 'question': 'Stadion', 'answer': 'Stadium', 'options': ['Stadium', 'Compare', 'Cabinet', 'Tax']} ,

{'numb': 2114, 'question': 'Uslub', 'answer': 'Style', 'options': ['Style', 'Too', 'In front of', 'International']} ,

{'numb': 2115, 'question': 'Pool', 'answer': 'Swimming', 'options': ['Slow', 'Swimming', 'Dry', 'Go fishing']} ,

{'numb': 2116, 'question': 'Eng yuqori', 'answer': 'Top', 'options': ['Top', 'Trouser', 'Strong', 'Sugar']} ,

{'numb': 2117, 'question': 'Ananaviy', 'answer': 'Traditional', 'options': ['Zoology', 'Expensive', 'Tiny', 'Traditional']} ,

{'numb': 2118, 'question': 'Ajoyib noyob', 'answer': 'Unusual', 'options': ['Internet', 'With', 'Unusual', 'Waitress']} ,

{'numb': 2119, 'question': 'Foydali', 'answer': 'Useful', 'options': ['Useful', 'Theater', 'Machine', 'Try']} ,

{'numb': 2120, 'question': 'Kiymoq', 'answer': 'Wear', 'options': ['Wear', 'Look at', 'Olive', 'Fair']} ,

{'numb': 2121, 'question': 'Yogoch', 'answer': 'Wood', 'options': ['Break', 'Wood', 'Raspberry', 'Head']} ,

{'numb': 2122, 'question': 'Xususiyat', 'answer': 'Feature', 'options': ['Loudly', 'Feature', 'On theinternet', 'Left']} ,

{'numb': 2123, 'question': 'Birinchi qavat', 'answer': 'First floor', 'options': ['First floor', 'Cleaner', 'Take off', 'Hug']} ,

{'numb': 2124, 'question': 'Yaxshi sifat', 'answer': 'Good quality', 'options': ['Good quality', 'Apple juice', 'Chimney', 'Bent']} ,

{'numb': 2125, 'question': 'Muhum', 'answer': 'Important', 'options': ['Spend', 'Cherry', 'Important', 'Man']} ,

{'numb': 2126, 'question': 'Haftada', 'answer': 'In the week', 'options': ['Shoes', 'Plain', 'In the week', 'Get dressed']} ,

{'numb': 2127, 'question': 'Hind', 'answer': 'Indian', 'options': ['Play', 'Blossom', 'Best', 'Indian']} ,

{'numb': 2128, 'question': 'Axborot', 'answer': 'Information', 'options': ['Those', 'Kitchen', 'Information', 'Useful']} ,

{'numb': 2129, 'question': 'Jemper', 'answer': 'Jumper', 'options': ['Jumper', 'Since', 'Box', 'Market']} ,

{'numb': 2130, 'question': 'Kech', 'answer': 'Late', 'options': ['Musician', 'Mini bar', 'Late', 'Something']} ,

{'numb': 2131, 'question': 'Charm', 'answer': 'Leather', 'options': ['Link', 'Navigation', 'Coffee', 'Leather']} ,

{'numb': 2132, 'question': 'Joylashuv', 'answer': 'Location', 'options': ['The usa', 'Guitar', 'Location', 'Writer']} ,

{'numb': 2133, 'question': 'Uzun', 'answer': 'Long', 'options': ['Magazine', 'Long', 'Measure', 'White']} ,

{'numb': 2134, 'question': 'Tartibga solish', 'answer': 'Make arrangements', 'options': ['Map reading', 'Certainly', 'Driver', 'Make arrangements']} ,

{'numb': 2135, 'question': 'Peshin', 'answer': 'Midday', 'options': ['Midday', 'Homeless', 'Feel', 'Public transport']} ,

{'numb': 2136, 'question': 'Times', 'answer': 'Opening', 'options': ['Into', 'Watch tv', 'Opening', 'Wall']} ,

{'numb': 2137, 'question': 'Tashqarida', 'answer': 'Outside', 'options': ['Outside', 'Market', 'Class', 'Surface']} ,

{'numb': 2138, 'question': 'Bir parcha', 'answer': 'A piece of', 'options': ['Imagination', 'Tenth', 'Arm', 'A piece of']} ,

{'numb': 2139, 'question': 'Katta yoshli', 'answer': 'Adult', 'options': ['Unusual', 'Even', 'Journey', 'Adult']} ,

{'numb': 2140, 'question': 'Qol', 'answer': 'Arm', 'options': ['Annoying', 'Arm', 'Uncle', 'Deal with']} ,

{'numb': 2141, 'question': 'Elon', 'answer': 'Announcement', 'options': ['Key', 'Announcement', 'Accent', 'Class']} ,

{'numb': 2142, 'question': 'Arxitektura', 'answer': 'Architecture', 'options': ['Tiny', 'Architecture', 'Fall', 'Grade']} ,

{'numb': 2143, 'question': 'Yalang oyoq', 'answer': 'Bare feet', 'options': ['Bare feet', 'Man', 'Ferry', 'Fog']} ,

{'numb': 2144, 'question': 'Oddiy sodda', 'answer': 'Basic', 'options': ['Basic', 'Customs', 'Say', 'Lovely']} ,

{'numb': 2145, 'question': 'Boliviya', 'answer': 'Bolivia', 'options': ['Coin', 'Knee', 'Stepmother/father', 'Bolivia']} ,

{'numb': 2146, 'question': 'Erkaklar shlyapasi', 'answer': 'Bowler hat', 'options': ['Ingredient', 'Bowler hat', 'Terrible', 'Knife']} ,

{'numb': 2147, 'question': 'Tasodifiy', 'answer': 'Casual', 'options': ['Break', 'Event', 'Casual', 'Bridge']} ,

{'numb': 2148, 'question': 'Rangli', 'answer': 'Colorful', 'options': ['Advantages', 'Grandson', 'Look after', 'Colorful']} ,

{'numb': 2149, 'question': 'Izoh', 'answer': 'Comment', 'options': ['Comment', 'House', 'Gorilla', 'Another']} ,

{'numb': 2150, 'question': 'Dizayner', 'answer': 'Designer', 'options': ['Trip', 'Designer', 'Tagine', 'Hear']} ,

{'numb': 2151, 'question': 'Yevropa', 'answer': 'Europe', 'options': ['Office worker', 'Vegetables', 'Europe', 'Boring']} ,

{'numb': 2152, 'question': 'Har kuni', 'answer': 'Every day', 'options': ['Salary', 'Great britain', 'Every day', 'Elderly']} ,

{'numb': 2153, 'question': 'Misol namuna', 'answer': 'Example', 'options': ['Skydiving', 'Hungry', 'Crucial', 'Example']} ,

{'numb': 2154, 'question': 'Hayajonli', 'answer': 'Exciting', 'options': ['Resident', 'Exciting', 'Of course', 'Pleasure']} ,

{'numb': 2155, 'question': 'Mashhur', 'answer': 'Famous', 'options': ['Uncle', 'July', 'Or', 'Famous']} ,

{'numb': 2156, 'question': 'Dush qabul qilmoq', 'answer': 'Have a shower', 'options': ['Capital', 'Listen to music', 'Have a shower', 'Desicion']} ,

{'numb': 2157, 'question': 'Tushlik qilmoq', 'answer': 'Have breakfast', 'options': ['Basic', 'Have breakfast', 'Jumper', 'Cabinet']} ,

{'numb': 2158, 'question': 'Kechki ovqat', 'answer': 'Have dinner', 'options': ['Have dinner', 'Motorbike', 'Pleasure', 'In my free time']} ,

{'numb': 2159, 'question': 'Bosh vaqtimda', 'answer': 'In my free time', 'options': ['In my free time', 'Lie in', 'Nail', 'Businessman']} ,

{'numb': 2160, 'question': 'Sayohat', 'answer': 'Journey', 'options': ['Emirate', 'Efficient', 'Basic', 'Journey']} ,

{'numb': 2161, 'question': 'Kenya', 'answer': 'Kenya', 'options': ['Behind', 'Up', 'Kenya', 'Foolish']} ,

{'numb': 2162, 'question': 'Mototsikl', 'answer': 'Motorbike', 'options': ['Nail', 'Motorbike', 'Famous', 'Video']} ,

{'numb': 2163, 'question': 'Nomlangan', 'answer': 'Named', 'options': ['Leave', 'Remote', 'Sunday', 'Named']} ,

{'numb': 2164, 'question': 'Ana u yerda', 'answer': 'Over there', 'options': ['Place of work', 'Seldom', 'Cupboard', 'Over there']} ,

{'numb': 2165, 'question': 'Pens', 'answer': 'Pence', 'options': ['Pence', 'Man', 'Wrist', 'Answer']} ,

{'numb': 2166, 'question': 'Ommaviy transport', 'answer': 'Public transport', 'options': ['Public transport', 'Umbrella', 'Fee', 'A lot']} ,

{'numb': 2167, 'question': 'Uyat', 'answer': 'Shame', 'options': ['Tuesday', 'Dirty', 'Cruel', 'Shame']} ,

{'numb': 2168, 'question': 'Bir xil', 'answer': 'Similar', 'options': ['Wash basin', 'Duvet', 'Left', 'Similar']} ,

{'numb': 2169, 'question': 'Janubiy afrika', 'answer': 'South africa', 'options': ['South africa', 'Elephant', 'Tidy', 'Finish school']} ,

{'numb': 2170, 'question': 'Janubiy koreya', 'answer': 'South korea', 'options': ['South korea', 'Waste', 'Every', 'Do online banking']} ,

{'numb': 2171, 'question': 'Ishlashni boshlamoq', 'answer': 'Start work', 'options': ['Start work', 'Goodbye', 'Delay', 'Free']} ,

{'numb': 2172, 'question': 'Shveytsariya', 'answer': 'Switzerland', 'options': ['Switzerland', 'Brazil', 'England', 'Back']} ,

{'numb': 2173, 'question': 'Orgatmoq', 'answer': 'Teach', 'options': ['Code', 'A piece of', 'Teach', 'Modern']} ,

{'numb': 2174, 'question': 'Tennis', 'answer': 'Tennis', 'options': ['Tennis', 'June', 'Newsagentãšâ¼s', 'Mug']} ,

{'numb': 2175, 'question': 'Messages', 'answer': 'Text', 'options': ['Text', 'Maximum', 'Our', 'Stressful']} ,

{'numb': 2176, 'question': 'Birga', 'answer': 'Together', 'options': ['Seafront', 'Breakfast', 'Together', 'Eater']} ,

{'numb': 2177, 'question': 'Vyetnam', 'answer': 'Vietnam', 'options': ['System', 'Degree', 'Although', 'Vietnam']} ,

{'numb': 2178, 'question': 'Yozuvch', 'answer': 'Writer', 'options': ['Dish', 'Writer', 'Nigerian', 'Opal']} ,

{'numb': 2179, 'question': 'Kop', 'answer': 'A lot', 'options': ['Olives', 'Art', 'Plan', 'A lot']} ,

{'numb': 2180, 'question': 'Hafta oxirida', 'answer': 'At the weekend', 'options': ['Bring', 'October', 'At the weekend', 'About']} ,

{'numb': 2181, 'question': 'Beysbol', 'answer': 'Baseball', 'options': ['Flower', 'Baseball', 'Unnecessary', 'Take']} ,

{'numb': 2182, 'question': 'Kitob dokoni', 'answer': 'Bookshop', 'options': ['Bookshop', 'Car', 'Thermometer', 'The day after tomorrow']} ,

{'numb': 2183, 'question': 'Karta oyinlari', 'answer': 'Card games', 'options': ['Card games', 'Prepare', 'Mayor', 'Break']} ,

{'numb': 2184, 'question': 'Sent', 'answer': 'Cent', 'options': ['Mother', 'Cent', 'City', 'Granddaughter']} ,

{'numb': 2185, 'question': 'Nazorat', 'answer': 'Check', 'options': ['Theatre', 'Condition', 'Chef', 'Check']} ,

{'numb': 2186, 'question': 'Komikslar', 'answer': 'Comics', 'options': ['Architecture', 'Comics', 'Greener', 'Maybe']} ,

{'numb': 2187, 'question': 'Xaridor', 'answer': 'Customer', 'options': ['Customer', 'Swimming', 'Case', 'Broken']} ,

{'numb': 2188, 'question': 'Davra', 'answer': 'Cycle', 'options': ['Confusing', 'Cycle', 'Retire', 'Lonely']} ,

{'numb': 2189, 'question': 'Daniya', 'answer': 'Denmark', 'options': ['Mosquito', 'Memory', 'Denmark', 'Light']} ,

{'numb': 2190, 'question': 'Dokon', 'answer': 'Department store', 'options': ['Pipe', 'Tidy', 'On time', 'Department store']} ,

{'numb': 2191, 'question': 'Dollar', 'answer': 'Dollar', 'options': ['Business management', 'Hospital', 'Dollar', 'Reserve']} ,

{'numb': 2192, 'question': 'Haydamoq', 'answer': 'Drive', 'options': ['Drive', 'Lebanon', 'Volunteer', 'Forget']} ,

{'numb': 2193, 'question': 'Barvaqt', 'answer': 'Early', 'options': ['Queue', 'Environment', 'Early', 'Argentina']} ,

{'numb': 2194, 'question': 'Bank xisobi', 'answer': 'Bank account', 'options': ['Engineer', 'Bank account', 'Duck', 'Monday']} ,

{'numb': 2195, 'question': 'Chiroyli', 'answer': 'Beautiful', 'options': ['Free time', 'Help', 'Beautiful', 'Careful']} ,

{'numb': 2196, 'question': 'Eng yaxshi dost', 'answer': 'Best friend', 'options': ['Bottle', 'Fist', 'Explain', 'Best friend']} ,

{'numb': 2197, 'question': 'Katta', 'answer': 'Big', 'options': ['Ticket', 'Big', 'Widowed', 'Electric piano']} ,

{'numb': 2198, 'question': 'Ammo', 'answer': 'But', 'options': ['But', 'State school', 'Below', 'Armchair']} ,

{'numb': 2199, 'question': 'Markaz', 'answer': 'Centre', 'options': ['Seldom', 'Enjoyable', 'Jumper', 'Centre']} ,

{'numb': 2200, 'question': 'Arzon', 'answer': 'Cheap', 'options': ['See', 'Cheap', 'Less', 'Near']} ,

{'numb': 2201, 'question': 'Konferensiya', 'answer': 'Conference', 'options': ['Funny', 'Conference', 'Atmosphere', 'Better']} ,

{'numb': 2202, 'question': 'Qimmat', 'answer': 'Expensive', 'options': ['Cheap', 'Expensive', 'Elephant', 'Lemonade']} ,

{'numb': 2203, 'question': 'Men uchun', 'answer': 'For me', 'options': ['Answer', 'For me', 'Thunder', 'Stress']} ,

{'numb': 2204, 'question': 'Dostona', 'answer': 'Friendly', 'options': ['Friendly', 'Saxophone', 'Somebody', 'Guilty']} ,

{'numb': 2205, 'question': 'Quvnoq', 'answer': 'Funny', 'options': ['Coach', 'Up', 'Funny', 'Party']} ,

{'numb': 2206, 'question': 'Hursand', 'answer': 'Happy', 'options': ['Owe', 'Science', 'Happy', 'Queue']} ,

{'numb': 2207, 'question': 'Qattiq', 'answer': 'Hard', 'options': ['Hard', 'Coffee', 'Impolite', 'High speed']} ,

{'numb': 2208, 'question': 'Elektron dokon', 'answer': 'Electronics shop', 'options': ['Dish', 'Birthday', 'Electronics shop', 'Chief']} ,

{'numb': 2209, 'question': 'Yevro', 'answer': 'Euro', 'options': ['Airport', 'Bridge', 'In sixties', 'Euro']} ,

{'numb': 2210, 'question': 'Yoqtirgan', 'answer': 'Favorite', 'options': ['Left', 'Make things', 'Favorite', 'Watch a film']} ,

{'numb': 2211, 'question': 'Olib otmoq', 'answer': 'Ferry', 'options': ['Ridiculous', 'Ferry', 'Married', 'Comfort']} ,

{'numb': 2212, 'question': 'Ishni tugatmoq', 'answer': 'Finish work', 'options': ['Finish school', 'Guest', 'Finish work', 'Sixth']} ,

{'numb': 2213, 'question': 'Kiyinmoq', 'answer': 'Get dressed', 'options': ['Get dressed', 'Make things', 'Fork', 'Obviously']} ,

{'numb': 2214, 'question': 'Uyga qaytmoq', 'answer': 'Get home', 'options': ['Answer', 'Get home', 'Then', 'Become']} ,

{'numb': 2215, 'question': 'Turmoq', 'answer': 'Get up', 'options': ['Convenient', 'Land', 'Get up', 'Miracle']} ,

{'numb': 2216, 'question': 'Tashqariga chiqmoq', 'answer': 'Go out', 'options': ['Keyboard', 'Melon', 'Go out', 'Code']} ,

{'numb': 2217, 'question': 'Uxlamoq', 'answer': 'Go to bed', 'options': ['Go to bed', 'Vietnam', 'Waste', 'Constantly']} ,

{'numb': 2218, 'question': 'Ishga bormoq', 'answer': 'Go to work', 'options': ['Pavement artist', 'Go to work', 'Answer', 'Old']} ,

{'numb': 2219, 'question': 'Gitara', 'answer': 'Guitar', 'options': ['Vegetables', 'Word', 'City', 'Guitar']} ,

{'numb': 2220, 'question': 'Hammom qilmoq', 'answer': 'Have a bath', 'options': ['Ill', 'Australia', 'Plain', 'Have a bath']} ,

{'numb': 2221, 'question': 'Yoqimli', 'answer': 'Lovely', 'options': ['Post office', 'Lovely', 'Mine', 'Niece']} ,

{'numb': 2222, 'question': 'Erkaklar', 'answer': 'Men', 'options': ['Noun', 'Men', 'Jealous', 'Picture']} ,

{'numb': 2223, 'question': 'Xabar', 'answer': 'Message', 'options': ['Dry', 'Put', 'Message', 'Uncomfortable']} ,

{'numb': 2224, 'question': 'Telefon', 'answer': 'Mobile phone', 'options': ['Reply', 'Mobile phone', 'Airport', 'Denmark']} ,

{'numb': 2225, 'question': 'Yangi', 'answer': 'New', 'options': ['Break', 'Centre', 'New', 'Ability']} ,

{'numb': 2226, 'question': 'Yangi zealandiya', 'answer': 'New zealand', 'options': ['Europe', 'New zealand', 'Sidewalk', 'Time']} ,

{'numb': 2227, 'question': 'Rassomlik', 'answer': 'Painting', 'options': ['Painting', 'Shawl', 'Ball', 'Travel']} ,

{'numb': 2228, 'question': 'Kishi', 'answer': 'Person', 'options': ['Celebrate', 'Again', 'Person', 'App']} ,

{'numb': 2229, 'question': 'Erkalamoq', 'answer': 'Pet', 'options': ['Believe', 'Clear', 'Pet', 'Link']} ,

{'numb': 2230, 'question': 'Egalik', 'answer': 'Possession', 'options': ['Napkin', 'Organize', 'Possession', 'Sweet']} ,

{'numb': 2231, 'question': 'Loyiha', 'answer': 'Project', 'options': ['Project', 'Receipt', 'Cherry', 'Project']} ,

{'numb': 2232, 'question': 'Boy', 'answer': 'Rich', 'options': ['Carpet', 'Rich', 'Depth', 'Rabbit']} ,

{'numb': 2233, 'question': 'Ayollar', 'answer': 'Women', 'options': ['Shine', 'Account', 'Women', 'Diesel']} ,

{'numb': 2234, 'question': 'Yosh', 'answer': 'Young', 'options': ['Education', 'Young', 'Pepper', 'Small']} ,

{'numb': 2235, 'question': 'Yana', 'answer': 'Again', 'options': ['Night', 'Announcement', 'Understand', 'Again']} ,

{'numb': 2236, 'question': 'Aylana', 'answer': 'Circle', 'options': ['Calmly', 'Equip', 'Circle', 'Classroom']} ,

{'numb': 2237, 'question': 'Qiyoslamoq', 'answer': 'Compare', 'options': ['Compare', 'Herb', 'Student', 'Tidy']} ,

{'numb': 2238, 'question': 'Toliq', 'answer': 'Complete', 'options': ['Complete', 'September', 'Potatoes', 'Frightened']} ,

{'numb': 2239, 'question': 'Muloqot', 'answer': 'Conversation', 'options': ['Understand', 'Conversation', 'Sleep', 'Example']} ,

{'numb': 2240, 'question': 'Boshloq', 'answer': 'Gap', 'options': ['Photograph', 'Gap', 'Code', 'Mayor']} ,

{'numb': 2241, 'question': 'Ga qaramoq', 'answer': 'Look at', 'options': ['Problem', 'Clurp', 'Look at', 'Aerobics']} ,

{'numb': 2242, 'question': 'Mos kelmoq', 'answer': 'Match', 'options': ['Match', 'Hairdresserãšâ¼s', 'Kiss', 'Trousers']} ,

{'numb': 2243, 'question': 'Ot', 'answer': 'Noun', 'options': ['Country', 'Job', 'Noun', 'Successful']} ,

{'numb': 2244, 'question': 'Buyurtma', 'answer': 'Order', 'options': ['Fashionable', 'Waterfall', 'Order', 'What a pity']} ,

{'numb': 2245, 'question': 'Sherik', 'answer': 'Partner', 'options': ['Eye contact', 'Partner', 'Partner', 'Spinach']} ,

{'numb': 2246, 'question': 'Amaliyot', 'answer': 'Practice', 'options': ['Publisher', 'Repetitivestraininjury', 'Wheel', 'Practice']} ,

{'numb': 2247, 'question': 'Tez', 'answer': 'Prompt', 'options': ['Chance career', 'Payback', 'Prompt', 'Museum']} ,

{'numb': 2248, 'question': 'Tanimoq', 'answer': 'Recognize', 'options': ['Hot', 'Mouth', 'Astronaut', 'Recognize']} ,

{'numb': 2249, 'question': 'Tez', 'answer': 'Rapid', 'options': ['Telephone', 'Progress', 'Pear', 'Rapid']} ,

{'numb': 2250, 'question': 'Javob bermoq', 'answer': 'Respond', 'options': ['Reason', 'Museum', 'River', 'Respond']} ,

{'numb': 2251, 'question': 'Bayonot', 'answer': 'Statement', 'options': ['Statement', 'Balloon', 'Polish', 'Very']} ,

{'numb': 2252, 'question': 'Stress', 'answer': 'Stress', 'options': ['Ceremony', 'Wet', 'Stress', 'Place of birth']} ,

{'numb': 2253, 'question': 'Almashtirmoq', 'answer': 'Swap', 'options': ['Kindof', 'Swap', 'Hair', 'Then']} ,

{'numb': 2254, 'question': 'Alifbo', 'answer': 'Alphabet', 'options': ['Alphabet', 'Unnecessary', 'Blossom', 'Light']} ,

{'numb': 2255, 'question': 'Va', 'answer': 'And', 'options': ['And', 'City', 'Data', 'After']} ,

{'numb': 2256, 'question': 'Biznes', 'answer': 'Business', 'options': ['Business', 'Bathroom', 'Pipe', 'Work']} ,

{'numb': 2257, 'question': 'Mamlakat', 'answer': 'Country', 'options': ['Country', 'Change jobs', 'Figure', 'Informal']} ,

{'numb': 2258, 'question': 'Yaxshi', 'answer': 'Fine', 'options': ['Goal', 'Fine', 'Nurse', 'Permit']} ,

{'numb': 2259, 'question': 'Xayrli tong', 'answer': 'Good morning', 'options': ['Tiny', 'Write', 'Friendly', 'Good morning']} ,

{'numb': 2260, 'question': 'Xayr', 'answer': 'Goodbye', 'options': ['Goodbye', 'Towel', 'In late twenties', 'Depth']} ,

{'numb': 2261, 'question': 'Tanishtirmoq', 'answer': 'Introduce', 'options': ['Arm', 'Introduce', 'Cake', 'House']} ,

{'numb': 2262, 'question': 'Raqam', 'answer': 'Number', 'options': ['Post', 'Number', 'Sock', 'Useful']} ,

{'numb': 2263, 'question': 'Togri', 'answer': 'Right', 'options': ['Right', 'Pig', 'Cupboard', 'Wake']} ,

{'numb': 2264, 'question': 'Telefon raqam', 'answer': 'Phone number', 'options': ['Bone', 'Much', 'Phone number', 'Press']} ,

{'numb': 2265, 'question': 'Talaffuz qilmoq', 'answer': 'Spell', 'options': ['Between', 'Shine', 'Spell', 'Fashion designer']} ,

{'numb': 2266, 'question': 'Minnatdorchilik', 'answer': 'Thanks', 'options': ['Fish', 'Advantages', 'Swimming pool', 'Thanks']} ,

{'numb': 2267, 'question': 'Ham', 'answer': 'Too', 'options': ['Busy', 'Romania', 'Too', 'Bicycle']} ,

{'numb': 2268, 'question': 'Avstraliya', 'answer': 'Australia', 'options': ['Tomorrow', 'Owe', 'The day before yesterday', 'Australia']} ,

{'numb': 2269, 'question': 'Braziliya', 'answer': 'Brazil', 'options': ['Brazil', 'Related', 'Separate', 'Compute']} ,

{'numb': 2270, 'question': 'Xitoy', 'answer': 'China', 'options': ['Download', 'China', 'Project', 'Sales']} ,

{'numb': 2271, 'question': 'Indoneziya', 'answer': 'Indonesia', 'options': ['Indonesia', 'Volunteer', 'Wet', 'Buyer']} ,

{'numb': 2272, 'question': 'Yaponiya', 'answer': 'Japan', 'options': ['Japan', 'Card', 'Class', 'Bike']} ,

{'numb': 2273, 'question': 'Rossiya', 'answer': 'Russia', 'options': ['Trip', 'Office worker', 'Russia', 'Couple']} ,

{'numb': 2274, 'question': 'Ispaniya', 'answer': 'Spain', 'options': ['Company', 'Space', 'Dance', 'Spain']} ,

{'numb': 2275, 'question': 'Turkiya', 'answer': 'Turkey', 'options': ['Hard', 'Ninth', 'Mosquito', 'Turkey']} ,

{'numb': 2276, 'question': 'Buyuk britaniya', 'answer': 'The uk', 'options': ['Clearly', 'The uk', 'Towel', 'Because']} ,

{'numb': 2277, 'question': 'Aqsh', 'answer': 'The usa', 'options': ['Boy', 'Cut', 'Between', 'The usa']} ,

{'numb': 2278, 'question': 'Argentina', 'answer': 'Argentina', 'options': ['Worth', 'Mosquito', 'Argentina', 'Bus']} ,

{'numb': 2279, 'question': 'Bosh oshpaz', 'answer': 'Chef', 'options': ['Huge', 'Shy', 'Chef', 'Yesterday']} ,

{'numb': 2280, 'question': 'Sinf', 'answer': 'Class', 'options': ['Last name', 'Listen', 'Class', 'Refund']} ,

{'numb': 2281, 'question': 'Elektron pochta', 'answer': 'Email', 'options': ['Although', 'Never', 'Email', 'Italian']} ,

{'numb': 2282, 'question': 'Ingliz', 'answer': 'English', 'options': ['Antique', 'English', 'Autumn', 'Finish school']} ,

{'numb': 2283, 'question': 'Italiya', 'answer': 'Italy', 'options': ['Italy', 'Look after', 'Kitchen', 'Socket']} ,

{'numb': 2284, 'question': 'Meksika', 'answer': 'Mexico', 'options': ['Disorganized', 'Homeless', 'Improve', 'Mexico']} ,

{'numb': 2285, 'question': 'Chiroyli', 'answer': 'Nice', 'options': ['Mix', 'Flut', 'Nice', 'Tidy']} ,

{'numb': 2286, 'question': 'Blaknot', 'answer': 'Notepad', 'options': ['Notepad', 'Microwave oven', 'Trend', 'Best selling']} ,

{'numb': 2287, 'question': 'Buyum', 'answer': 'Object', 'options': ['Object', 'Souvenir seller', 'Easily', 'Ice cream']} ,

{'numb': 2288, 'question': 'Soat', 'answer': 'Oclock', 'options': ['Oclock', 'Granddaughter', 'Sandwich', 'Mountain']} ,

{'numb': 2289, 'question': 'Rasm', 'answer': 'Photo', 'options': ['Nail', 'Pianist', 'Lovely', 'Photo']} ,

{'numb': 2290, 'question': 'Yol', 'answer': 'Road', 'options': ['Road', 'Airline', 'Stop', 'Skirt']} ,

{'numb': 2291, 'question': 'Ruminiya', 'answer': 'Romania', 'options': ['Plastic', 'Romania', 'Economy', 'Idea']} ,

{'numb': 2292, 'question': 'Tabletka', 'answer': 'Tablet', 'options': ['Tablet', 'Unlucky', 'Father', 'Condition']} ,

{'numb': 2293, 'question': 'Taksi haydovchisi', 'answer': 'Taxi driver', 'options': ['Ask', 'Hairdresserãšâ¼s', 'Taxi driver', 'Fishing']} ,

{'numb': 2294, 'question': 'Oqituvchi', 'answer': 'Teacher', 'options': ['Birth date', 'Have a baby', 'Teacher', 'Useful']} ,

{'numb': 2295, 'question': 'Tailand', 'answer': 'Thailand', 'options': ['Buy', 'Ceiling', 'Thailand', 'Handkerchief']} ,

{'numb': 2296, 'question': 'Soyabon', 'answer': 'Umbrella', 'options': ['Umbrella', 'Begin', 'Home', 'Better']} ,

{'numb': 2297, 'question': 'Ofitsiant', 'answer': 'Waiter', 'options': ['Dancer', 'Nephew', 'Waiter', 'Day']} ,

{'numb': 2298, 'question': 'Hafta', 'answer': 'Week', 'options': ['Week', 'Name', 'Tobacco', 'Tenth']}
];